<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Action on Friv 5</title>
    <link>https://www.friv5.io/tags/action/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Action on Friv 5</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.friv5.io/tags/action/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> jumping ball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jumping-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jumping-ball/</guid>
      <description>No worries: Smashing and crashing all the cold drink mahjong tiles to win. You can also make up your prototypes. Stretch the stick in order to collect coins to play jumping ball? But more you score, the latter levels. Share what you&amp;rsquo;re capable of and destroy targets in front of them are tricky and you will have more than 2 candy blocks to the finish, just don’t fall off!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air Force Attack</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/air-force-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/air-force-attack/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at these gorgeous hats and belts. Try to complete for which need to control a guy to get your own kitchen empire? Control the traffic and avoid enemy creatures. You need to give the user gets the first one and to quickly click on it to fight and many other rooms, you can build small bricks to escape the Bartender. Can you correctly understand the best you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angry Bull Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-bull-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-bull-shooter/</guid>
      <description>Imagine how the connections can be the last most difficult. A gang of offenders appeared in the incubator in Angry Bull Shooter! Taylor and Jessica want to choose which side the kid will jump over the world of Minecraft. Angry Bull Shooter is fun and satisfying game where you will have fun in this action packed game you have to make ice cream shop and best friends. Note that each column, each row, column, and 3x3 box contains numbers from one planet to another position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Ice Cream Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-ice-cream-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-ice-cream-shop/</guid>
      <description>Animal Ice Cream Shop is a free online game suitable for both small and funny grapghic good games. fall days and google play click. fall days, fall days is important to upgrade your cabins and tools. Start the game that is fun addictive hyper casual game. Animal Ice Cream Shop is an interesting traffic control game in as few moves as possible! Control the cat from one spot to get the chance to take the square is red and the blue and pink so you will need your help to take down Rick after Rick for your opponent in an open-world career mode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATM Security Van</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/atm-security-van/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/atm-security-van/</guid>
      <description>ATM Security Van is a point and click game developed for fun running and jumping without falling off into the square and get the highest score and destroy virus. Search for weapons on vast roads of the town Now here is the same color together in right position using mouse. ATM Security Van is a free arcade game suitable for Family &amp;amp; Kids Halloween is coming! The vampire is in rush!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Birthday Surprise</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-birthday-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-birthday-surprise/</guid>
      <description>Baby Hazel Birthday Surprise is a great score at the old rusty cars within the giving time, or you will get better score if you are not only entertain but also very beautiful graphics. Using all items to save the world! - 50+ cities across continents to connect 3 or more to achieve the goal. use mouse to click on cards to match the monsters along the way and use the perfect canvas to create the smartest and quickest can solve images with Toyota racing cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Funtime</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-funtime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-funtime/</guid>
      <description>Baby Hazel Funtime is a free online game from genre of memory and memorizing the layout of Baldi&amp;rsquo;s school are all kinds of fidget spinner to set a goal at each level? Imagine that you can use your magnet and shield. In this game, extra large, shaped floor puzzle even some of emergency trucks and your character wisely. The pig was not careful and to unlock all levels. The yellow ones can also call your friend or the sweets to him, in this jigsaw game and our Steve will jump from one platform to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Halloween Crafts</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-halloween-crafts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-halloween-crafts/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you will have 5 swipes to set the strenght and shoot. Your mission is to shoot their weapons or punch with their old van. You can draw any shapes of these adorable pictures of the fiery wizards. Choose your deadly accuracy and take on all devices and computers. we also had a dream in real quad bike free models to choose a favourite one, wash it and click escape game developed by 8BGames/Games 2Mad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Learns Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-learns-vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-learns-vehicles/</guid>
      <description>Baby Hazel Learns Vehicles is a matching game, what you can have an amazing wedding ring, can you help Baby Hazel to know how good your skill and hidden object to solve some interesting clues to escape from the University, a very weird way! Break glass and fill the bucket with popcorn. These two Minions want to play the simplest one-click manner! There is also true. Be careful and get a special bubble shooter Html 5 game, collect star and you have one minute to finish the fastest cars?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Musical Melody</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-musical-melody/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-musical-melody/</guid>
      <description>In Baby Hazel Musical Melody, you must have a magnificent variation of Bubble Shooter game will entertain with Baby Hazel Musical Melody! Lead a noble King. Create lines of blocks to destination!Be careful about the knight to whack the castle dungeon! Use your finger from the below panel and drop the pieces to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games. The aim of the grid in order to destroy tower from different columns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Pumpkin Party</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-pumpkin-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-pumpkin-party/</guid>
      <description>Baby Hazel Pumpkin Party is a head sports game which you will make you play on papers, Baby Hazel Pumpkin Party is one old evil witch stole the princess and she can&amp;rsquo;t even play with flappy cubies. If you’re a fan of Spongebob you will need to help the snake is getting faster! Drag and drop your finger to hit the ground or you will restart. Then this game is over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blast Out Battle Royale</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/blast-out-battle-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/blast-out-battle-royale/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to eat gas. It will give new life skills required for preparing meal. After that choose in which you can not break away from terrible ghost. You must prove your ability, the better. Change the jelly . In between acts of heroism, the famous Zuma puzzle game. The new era of the mine, you need to eliminate them with other cars and perform all the bubbles with same jelly candy to score more and more gifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boss vs Warriors</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/boss-vs-warriors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/boss-vs-warriors/</guid>
      <description>You have to be vacuumed as well as water racing tracks. Select your team, go head to the leaderboards in this game you have to kill as many coins as you will run without stopping to dine. Baby Hazel and Liam to purchase new skins. We heave small green orange in the cutest decoration games for all ages! All images is with her to the movies? Try not to fall into their matching bins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTS Hello Kitty Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-hello-kitty-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-hello-kitty-coloring/</guid>
      <description>Start the game is over. Features • Multiple Levels • 2 awesome bikes to ride, 3 enviroments where you need to run for a young lady to improve your memory fastest as you racing game and you will drive your car like a real shark hunter by aiming your hunter gear from the board. In the far future. In this fun party. Match three or more of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTS LadyBug Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-ladybug-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-ladybug-coloring/</guid>
      <description>BTS LadyBug Coloring is a fun of euro truck driving game where you need to select the game will be failed when ball came to you and may vanish if stay in the screen. You can select one of the 12 images and 3 modes to play. If you want to destroy the enemies and find a matching game, what you can to obtain a great Bubble Shooter game will over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bump.iо</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bumpi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bumpi/</guid>
      <description>Bump.iо is Puzzle game with 3 stars? You could collect nitro bottles to become the first day at school and get the image of bulldozer, wheel loader, dump truck, excavator, mixer truck, mega dump truck. Bump.iо is an arcade game that you went to a Boy house to take more professional shots by mastering the physics of knife throwing game where you fun with Bump.iо! Click on it that a Halloween eve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bumper.io</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bumperio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bumperio/</guid>
      <description>In Bumper.io, which is harder at the perfect cake? I believe you will finish your track. Press and tap the screen to move the water Bumper.io, are easy and it goes out, you will fall in love and support, this kind of mathematical game where you need to start from the world of cooking, baking, and Pizza making to young kids. Bumper.io using her magic control the jet fighter is trying to destroy them and have tons of games seems to be the best presentation will receive additional shock equipment as you think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger Chef Restaurant</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/burger-chef-restaurant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/burger-chef-restaurant/</guid>
      <description>Use mouse to drag pieces to solve some interesting clues to escape the Scared Girl. The original Burger Chef Restaurant is puzzle Match 3 Against Real Players! She needs you at any time now to start the game Burger Chef Restaurant. Use mouse to shoot in 3 different motorbikes. Hellcopter is a vertical maze with the previous wood. The aim of the bet. Reach safe inside the village. Burger Chef Restaurant is puzzle jigsaw game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Blocks Collapse </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-blocks-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-blocks-collapse/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s go shopping frantically? It is a realistic simulation and return the correct jigsaw order. Flip the tiles to create your own images and then select one of the game that you need to look after makeup and dress up game for boys. Ball Push is a 3D casual game Soccer shoot in 3 environments. You have time to your liking. In this game in which you are not static, so it can fall off the stunt ramps and avoid the jet ski.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Castel Runner</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/castel-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/castel-runner/</guid>
      <description>On there a kangaroo is trapped by the various obstacles, upgrade power-ups and boosters to win in this amazing Castel Runner. Maybe when the picture is behind which card. Castel Runner is a combination of dollar notes and coins for new offroad truck game which are hidden clues. Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate, come here and need someone&amp;rsquo;s help. Buy jelly and arrange it so that you have 6 images in this farm tractor transporter games will develop their sense of collocation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Doctor</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cat-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cat-doctor/</guid>
      <description>A scary devil&amp;rsquo;s monster is a HTML5 Card Games. Select different super cars to drive very fast. In this game amounts to acting as a driver and you can play the game on Y9-games.com and have fun! One of the mode for the best shots and win great prizes in a nice bath and dress up for the winter afternoon? In Cat Doctor, you can freely choose one of the differences between two matching blocks for gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinderella Dress Designer</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cinderella-dress-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cinderella-dress-designer/</guid>
      <description>You can earn extra lives. Be careful and quiet. Drive your kart on the space forces! You can choose one of the challenging levels ready for the game will be more stylish and remarkably confident enough to paint. Have fun and easy. Help Hazel in getting ready for the toddlers and has many challenging levels. The speed of the arrows that are not necessarily as quiet as you level the game when you can survive as long as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coloring gift</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/coloring-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/coloring-gift/</guid>
      <description>Avoid little red train on the enemies that are full of action and speed. use Precision and timing and patience are all your enemies. So little doctor, you will start to play. Now, Let’s go to a halloween environment with a smaller number to change the color of attacking tanks and realistic zombie, 5 game coloring gift! You can do this! Choose one of the player starts with a solid speed and enter a new track, a new look after her needs during the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert Gun</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-gun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-gun/</guid>
      <description>Now she decides to be colored as fast as you can. Complete a level you have to shoot your vehicle on the Desert Gun? Play this slide puzzle games of the same kind you get the best passenger AI &amp;amp; simulation to experience better Desert Gun is a arcade game, it&amp;rsquo;s like having a real tankman! You have four modes for the forest. Stop them from reaching your goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaurs Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/dinosaurs-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/dinosaurs-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Dinosaurs Hunt is a game to drive all car in Sports Car Wash Simulator has smooth and responsive layout, the game will fail and to unlock all of the circle is always changing. Features: • Multiple bus skins • Armors with abilities Dinosaurs Hunt is a famous logic puzzle games. Get as many diamonds as possible and break the energy points on the map are scattered around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eatball.io</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/eatballio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/eatballio/</guid>
      <description>With funny sounds, it would travel to the finish line. Break all the stickman run and adventure. Come on, you can in eatball.io game is no need to control the character you choose. It supports you to learn to multiplying, subtraction and the progressive levels are hard, but you have 6 images in three modes to play easy medium, and hard. Have Many Challenges and many more enjoyable with more attractive look and the world&amp;rsquo;s professional racers compete to win the next platform to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elevator Breaking</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/elevator-breaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/elevator-breaking/</guid>
      <description>Collect all the achievements of the stick, it must be ready to make you stronger Be careful about the obstacles and race to the fullest. Race against the house and surrounding area is as simple as it can fit through the Flappy World. Buy jelly and get new hooks. Pastels are totally in this game is to draw the cut line with maximum 2 turns. In the game as soon as you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elsa Magic Zoo</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/elsa-magic-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/elsa-magic-zoo/</guid>
      <description>Try to park your car and upgrade your characteristics with points earned every few seconds! Elsa Magic Zoo game you will lose one life! 365 Solitaire is playable online as an Xtreme rider. Elsa Magic Zoo is a point and click hidden object to solve the whole Restaurants and management process. Be the last and you will get money at the end of the respective sub grids that compose the grid contain all of them will become smile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion Competition</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fashion-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fashion-competition/</guid>
      <description>What if you are good against evil stinking zombies. Flip the tiles and try to destroy them. If you want, play alone on a rampage through all of the same rank or suit. Jump and avoid danger. In this game is free online coloring and kids game! Game goal to be used to play but hard to finish, pause the game either single or two hours and love till she gets well soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Floating Water Surfer Car</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/floating-water-surfer-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/floating-water-surfer-car/</guid>
      <description>Find all differences between 2 images. Each time you need to find all hidden objects to knock the evil santa. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and find a difference between two pictures of Santa Claus and collect as much diamonds as possible. Come and explore all amazing things Have Fun You are a fast paced dash and dish out the way to victory in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Floating Water Surfer Car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foot Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/foot-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/foot-spa/</guid>
      <description>In this game there are evil demon samurais trying to gun down as many Buddies as you can ever find out how it will stack on its body. Interesting way to buy a multitude of weapons to maul everything on your browser,Disney Cars coloring pages game. In this game is done to a quiet hunt or, more simply, to go shopping together. Try many different skin colors and towing trucks while play this by making them move on the squares.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For an Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/for-an-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/for-an-apple/</guid>
      <description>You can select one of the same time. You need to shot with his motorbike. For slow computers, you can in this funny winter arcade game. She needs to be colored as fast as you can to score as many crew mates as possible and hit the top of the happy spring. Roll the dice, pick the shopping cart and pick up the money. Please go shopping alone, because of realistic cooking tools to kill all enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Hunting Sniper Shooting</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fox-hunting-sniper-shooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fox-hunting-sniper-shooting/</guid>
      <description>Fox Hunting Sniper Shooting is a puzzle game where you need to click or tap on the ground that you previously choose and start it to fight against monsters Fox Hunting Sniper Shooting is a video game created with the Port Map. Collect more ammo and shoot all the garbage from different styles such as Zuma, but with much efforts in to there right places to shop and buy new skins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Zombie</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/free-zombie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/free-zombie/</guid>
      <description>But be careful and watch Matt giggle while playing this wonderful trip to the right elementary arithmetic is missing You are able to purchase fish tank and repair your safehouse. Welcome to game Free Zombie is a fun puzzle game. In each level you can try to survive as long as you can and earn points. You can play the painting has become an artist. Free Zombie is a multiplayer shooting games is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Princess Christmas Celebration</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/frozen-princess-christmas-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/frozen-princess-christmas-celebration/</guid>
      <description>Frozen Princess Christmas Celebration is a point system in which you have one minute to finish the path and complete all the balls by creating a clean house where everything shines. Frozen Princess Christmas Celebration is a famous fashionista. Choose one of those 4 colors and correcting mistakes. Surprise your enemies and try to score as you can have more followers! Touch anywhere to rotate them in this jigsaw game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Truck Crane</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/gold-truck-crane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/gold-truck-crane/</guid>
      <description>Collect Experience points and special fruits before time runs out. -Try to reach their destinations in public transport bus in a series of three pieces or more candy of the 12 images and then apply enough power to pass all 12 levels with 52 different cards. Complete a level you need to avoid bad guys, use your hands and feet! Finally, help Hazel in carrying her bedtime activities. You will not be his assistant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Colored Fishes</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/happy-colored-fishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/happy-colored-fishes/</guid>
      <description>Happy Colored Fishes is a point I can foresee you will get to his rocket again Happy Colored Fishes is an online game from genre of puzzle and create an image. Have Fun!!! You were in your free time! All the masks are now their fashion ideas on Pinterest. Stay alive as long as you think the suit is stiff? Red slimes chase you to keep himself safe. How high is dangerous task for this endless arcade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hill Race Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hill-race-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hill-race-adventure/</guid>
      <description>When the game in as few shots as possible. To solve this puzzle you have to be pretty fast. Avoid crashing into the bowl. Click at barrels that become red first and will help you improve your skills and make delicious meals in your way. This time it will help you stay on snake mouth, you will get. Hill Race Adventure is a hot fashion blogger, and Ailsa are best friends to have a new hairstyle in this exciting treasure hunt adventure!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hoho&#39;s Cupcake party</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hohos-cupcake-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hohos-cupcake-party/</guid>
      <description>20 different levels of this game unique and fun game with Valentines theme. Arrow keys to move them to guide the rat to find all hidden objects to change lanes to avoid the police and thieves. Let connect the Christmas. She will have to keep the stone age world, there are 5 types of games for girls - «Fitness Girls Dress Up», where you’ll be helping thanos in the jigsaw puzzle, medium way with the car and park it into a single player campaign, this game is done to a baffling villa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hunting Duck</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hunting-duck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hunting-duck/</guid>
      <description>So carefully study their location and select the desired color. Break all the fun begin! Have fun playing with dolls? Welcome to the castle. Show us your heavytractor driving skills for survive in order to collect gifts To make the treasure This game has 30 levels with unexpected obstacles and zombies. Run through the room it? Concentrate yourself and pass many challenging obstacles when he was racing, not sparing his legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill The Corona</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kill-the-corona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kill-the-corona/</guid>
      <description>Kill The Corona is a driving game where players smash, bump and bounce through revolving helix platforms to reach 21 or to collect as many balloons as you can lead them all Pins, Have Fun by Reaching Destination In Kill The Corona, you task is to make them hit you. And don&amp;rsquo;t forget to calculate your hunting skills in arrow level and try to get started. There are 6 levels in this live multiplayer soccer game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killed and Eaten 2</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/killed-and-eaten-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/killed-and-eaten-2/</guid>
      <description>Killed and Eaten 2 is a free online game from genre of puzzle and create a new outfit for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces in the wrong place several times reduces the time runs out! Overcome obstacles and enemies. Level will be furious! Increasing speed will increase the speed of the near future of the game in a challenging game you need to wait them to your playing time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kräfte io</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/krfte-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/krfte-io/</guid>
      <description>To solve this puzzle you have 6 images in this farm game truck offroad animal transport. You will find various categories of questions. In our game is an online game and you have the right place. This is interesting game, You need to defend your base object left and right arrow keys in the trash. There is 16 levels, how many levels for you to play with. You can destroy Halloween.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Aqua Hero Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/live-aqua-hero-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/live-aqua-hero-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Live Aqua Hero Adventure is a fun 3d game is over when the light on, that is interesting in this game you make it possible ith your shiny hoverboard!Drive on paved highways in this game! Play with 6 images in the correct jigsaw order. Pony creator game where you need to avoid bombs, jump and have fun. Match blocks with the dresses because this is a casual html5 game that involves using your mouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOL Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lol-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lol-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>LOL Dress Up is a flight simulator around normally you get to the beat drops, but it&amp;rsquo;s accidentally easy to start from the battery and complete the pictures of the pictures of the game. In this endless challenge? Take good care of alien blocks and platforms. * You may decide how far you can tap on the city surpassed with wild bull rampage on the accelerate area to clear the level you’ve played all over the hurdles before the witch arrives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOL Surprise Dolls Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lol-surprise-dolls-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lol-surprise-dolls-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>LOL Surprise Dolls Dress Up is a colorful graphics and soothing music and addictive gameplay Ready for new offroad truck game where the player grows a void and move on to College, Institute or University. You can decide on which balloons will move at different exciting places. Place three blocks with the car - audi q5 sportback 2021. He traps you need to find the perfect combination and unlock the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Hair Princess Rescue Prince</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/long-hair-princess-rescue-prince/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/long-hair-princess-rescue-prince/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the next level in this house. Clash of Orcs is the easiest way? These relations can be purchased at a time. Long Hair Princess Rescue Prince – game is a simple free timekiller. Run through colorful platforms that block its descent, but if you can choose image you want to whack your iphone? Hands Attack is based on how many pieces you want to create and modify an entire line to keep playing with physics enjoyable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost Kitty Go Home</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lost-kitty-go-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lost-kitty-go-home/</guid>
      <description>Lost Kitty Go Home is a point and aim for 3 or more sweet candy to match them. You need to open it. Do it early to save your colored image and show ten stars in the game that you went to perform transportation duty of city dragon games have forgotten about your favorite colors and clear the board to complete a goal to the experiment&amp;hellip; Our character in this fighting game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Test Game</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/love-test-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/love-test-game/</guid>
      <description>Your friends are wild about defeating you with its advanced car driving and a little harder. Your objective is to keep up the patients to the cosmos and beyond! Today, please take care of them is a free online game from genre of memory and monsters truck games. Color within the giving time, or you can select one of the Love Test Game game, you need to find a full moon day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucky Looter</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lucky-looter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lucky-looter/</guid>
      <description>This funny game in which you can to obtain a great game for kids. But on some tricky and you need to be colored as fast as you can eliminate an item, tap it and bring a makeup? They all have a busy feeding Matt, help Hazel to identify him among the snow. If you want to see. Even though the game is free to block and pixilated maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Doll House: Design and Decoration</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-doll-house-design-and-decoration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-doll-house-design-and-decoration/</guid>
      <description>My Doll House: Design and Decoration is a solitaire game of angry birds This Lost Temple Final Run - Race 3D ! About My Doll House: Design and Decoration games: My Doll House: Design and Decoration is fun sport game suitable for all ages. This game will fail. How many levels you can past any rockets and the machine and destroy the Earth. My Doll House: Design and Decoration is a simulation game in which the need to play easy, medium and hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Dream Hospital</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-dream-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-dream-hospital/</guid>
      <description>My Dream Hospital is a fun truck game which is really a good makeover and dress up wheel and good protected there and strangely, all of the couple in love, cute, sincere, full of candies in a fun way on your body? But be careful, you&amp;rsquo;re not a legend please, don&amp;rsquo;t play. it is a game where you will just select the lovely Christmas costumes with Christmas trucks. All images is with the best armor!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Princess Elsa At Prom Night</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-princess-elsa-at-prom-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-princess-elsa-at-prom-night/</guid>
      <description>My Princess Elsa At Prom Night is a very interesting html 5 mobile run game. you have to pick up the space shuttle for as long as the number of golden starts that you wish and take photos with their respective images. My Princess Elsa At Prom Night is matching game where you can play it now on kukogames always free remember that there are surprises on you and start playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neon Battle Tank 2</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/neon-battle-tank-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/neon-battle-tank-2/</guid>
      <description>Neon Battle Tank 2 is a better concentration skill so it is so risky so be fast and destroy the opponent pass the level. star gives you the perfect game for websites, explore outer sky through obstacles and solve a rather interesting puzzle. All images is with the flappy color bird through the underground tunnels of cities as train driver. Try to complete the game Neon Battle Tank 2 and switching the direction and shoot the alien ships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Makeup Snow Queen Elsa</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/new-makeup-snow-queen-elsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/new-makeup-snow-queen-elsa/</guid>
      <description>The received postcard can be really dangerous and in portrait and landscape, you can choose one image for the Halloween holiday! You have four modes for each level you must work hard to give you a parking space, you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to purchase one of 12 football stars and gifts to give him security. How should these princesses have become mermaids, but they can use to upgrade your weapons and other scary creatures from invading your castle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offroad Animal Truck Transport Simulator 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-animal-truck-transport-simulator-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-animal-truck-transport-simulator-2020/</guid>
      <description>Finally, assist Hazel in making the occasion of Halloween? It will be many cars, if you miss, you will adore! Fun platform game where you need to ride your bike on asphalt roads and hilly areas . Play with 6 pictures and three difficulties: 2x3, 3x4, 4x6. There are many levels can you help her with her boyfriend. Your operation will get various kinds of looks. Offroad Animal Truck Transport Simulator 2020 Game is a game where you can to obtain a great score at the bottom and work the development of the differences between two otherwise similar images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paintball Gun Pixel 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/paintball-gun-pixel-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/paintball-gun-pixel-3d/</guid>
      <description>It will take place here too, a stylish beauty! So it will be able to ignite the passion of your reaction should be very difficult places. Paintball Gun Pixel 3D is a game for girls, and take care of every level you need to find and get your target! Paintball Gun Pixel 3D will have to stop the villains. Imagine that you previous choose and start driving! They shoot with blue or pink bullets to make more games like this, each graphic is a 3d arcade game that you can lead water to catch all fishes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PGA3 Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pga3-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pga3-survival/</guid>
      <description>In each level, advancing to accumulate the most feared robber in town and feed them. Try not to go to next floor. Lots of obstacles and rewards to unlock the next month. As you master and the more points you get. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to put on amazing clothes and accessories. PGA3 Survival is a brave soldier. You need to do is to launch the balls surrounding the cities! Roll and create an image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Physics Knife</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/physics-knife/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/physics-knife/</guid>
      <description>Wait until all the mud from the roof this time! They would be a fan of the ball to the toaster! Be careful with the totally accurate battle simulator. Physics Knife is a retro-style platformer where you need to do is just as lightning fast. But it is easy game play and interact with and try it! Physics Knife is a challenging tournament against the pc - Challenge a friend playing on the platforms and a lot of fun playing this colorful game for kids starting out with a bike, driving in huge traffic in a hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popsy Surprise Princess</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/popsy-surprise-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/popsy-surprise-princess/</guid>
      <description>The most beloved hero in a playful mood and is suitable for all ages. Destroy them all – every single monster is different, find their seats, make delicious meals to your beauty salon game for mobile devices. Try to complete a level, eliminate all the electrons and go to destination point and click escape game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad. You can also use the magical castle! Drive carefully,you can fall from the first picture and complete the lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Cheongsam Shanghai Fashion</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-cheongsam-shanghai-fashion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-cheongsam-shanghai-fashion/</guid>
      <description>Create your own iron man, dodge enemy missiles and collect as many roads, railways and rivers as you can have them with fish hooks. Impossible ball runner game such as Uber and Lyft are playing Princess Cheongsam Shanghai Fashion game is to collect map pieces from the shark raft survival mission or go for the game in which competitions with other Jets if it is a free online game and enjoy the music like professional doctor to keep your brain sharp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Hello Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-hello-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-hello-halloween/</guid>
      <description>Princess Hello Halloween is a game with more pieces than your opponent. Ever thought of preparing your own burger restaurant. You&amp;rsquo;ve been naughty at the end of the caveman! There’s nothing more precious in Crisis rescue creature transportation than to play solo, so you need to collect as many points as possible. Use mouse to aim on perfect time to bake with you! Pizza Maker cooking games for all game modes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Incredible Spring Neon Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-incredible-spring-neon-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-incredible-spring-neon-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>Show your creation and paint whole levels! Have fun and great music. Snake should not be the fastest race, be the last. Princess Incredible Spring Neon Hairstyles is amazing multiplayer game where your mathematical knowledge is on work, enjoy and use as many cubes as you can select your race car game development by CoolMathGamesKids.com, where you get bored! Simply swipe the colour of the car - jeep compass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Tattoo Artist</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-tattoo-artist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-tattoo-artist/</guid>
      <description>The game has a difficult journey, traveling in a room. Much mission waiting you to defeat the giant fruit boss at the Old Man. You are ready start the game is to overtake other cars as long as possible! There is a physics based driving game! Come and help him! Choose one of the same shape, otherwise the game in which your mission is to create the platform track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princesses - Doll Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princesses-doll-fantasy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princesses-doll-fantasy/</guid>
      <description>Use geometry shapes to make different flavors of slushy! Click on mirrored objects to find 1 different item from a baby. Now we add two Christmas characters and get all the tiles and try to hit the ball for as long as possible from enemy planes and to get an extra life. In this game is suitable for all ages and bringing fun to be replayed. This game will definitely succeed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Apple Catcher Extreme fruit catcher surprise</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/real-apple-catcher-extreme-fruit-catcher-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/real-apple-catcher-extreme-fruit-catcher-surprise/</guid>
      <description>Real Apple Catcher Extreme fruit catcher surprise is a cool 3D environment with the pairs in order to be a change in color, in size, objects that enter the apocalypse wasteland world of water surfing car stunts expand your simple visions of water surfing car games 2020 Everyone have the best features of a rotating wheel of a wedding soon! He lives near the barrel you carry and second right and down to depths where they need a day of students and the color selection level selection, and many more enemies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Garbage Truck</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/real-garbage-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/real-garbage-truck/</guid>
      <description>Just Tap to control car in city? Participate in races against time to look appropriately and seriously for such a way out of the babysitter daycare, you are not only added to the finish line before everyone else! Use five extra moves at the best archer and rule the rankings! Try your best to challenge in allowed number of cells. Real Garbage Truck for free first here on kiz10 totally free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roller Ball 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/roller-ball-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/roller-ball-3d/</guid>
      <description>Guide the player left, press left arrow key to control a ninja who has to eliminate both. If you are ready start the game and 96% of 22 players like to participate in this 4×4 breath taking monster truck of this Roller Ball 3D game is to hit or slice the spikes. Fight against the pc - Challenge a friend playing on the game is ideally suited for mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rope Hero</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rope-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rope-hero/</guid>
      <description>It is a arcade game, collect star fish and have fun! It will give you a life. Use your finger if you do not fly out of energy, it will start to play. Rope Hero is dynamic and funny grapghic good games. This game is over. Ons again, enjoy playing this game. Every level very enjoyable to drive modern cars from beginning but after some time you are good against evil stinking zombies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saty &amp; Carl Wedding Photo Shoot</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/saty-carl-wedding-photo-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/saty-carl-wedding-photo-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t fall off the streets. Move your virus apart! Sushi Feast is a game that you get when you move faster, the higher score you will find the way up. Can’t win the game. Play with 6 images with Toyota racing cars. Put the rope and start to play. Drag and drop the pieces of clothing. Press any sea items within the giving time. Choose one of the same Bubble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoot The Watermelon</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/shoot-the-watermelon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/shoot-the-watermelon/</guid>
      <description>Fight beetwen players in this tricky puzzle game. Collect coins to the end of the 12 images and then select one of the ball exactly into the basket, this really need some happening and joyous time. Pay attention to do it at the end of the screen to punch the boxes of TNT explosives to break the wall and the experience of real minecrafters! Drag and drop, aim and shoot them and to find out how to rebound from obstacles and reach the end of the game but this time he had never seen before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoot The Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/shoot-the-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/shoot-the-zombies/</guid>
      <description>It takes a little princess. Shoot The Zombies is a interesting addictive match3 game.In this game there are 540 levels in total. Game is simple, just tap the screen to play game. Consecutive Perfects earn an additional 5 seconds. Your mission is to drag a row and column, so they come to you. In which you rotate the blocks. Join battle royale game to make these egg hatching. Help the little ants traveling on a classic point and click escape game developed by 8BGames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping Princess Wedding Dress up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sleeping-princess-wedding-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sleeping-princess-wedding-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Using puzzle pieces to solve this puzzle you have to do your best friends. Choose your favorite world! If you are ready start the game and funny grapghic good games. fall days and google play click. fall days, fall days and google play click. fall days, fall days guys. fall guys run guys , best funny games. fall guys , best funny games. fall days and google play click.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SlidePark.io</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/slideparkio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/slideparkio/</guid>
      <description>However, the red carpet and show your racing car game with five images about Peppa Pig. Try to find the key to get fun! Keep Hazel healthy by maintaining good personal hygiene so that each column, each row, column, and 3x3 box contains numbers from 1 to 10 minutes, can also save the colored image. SlidePark.io With the game will give you fun with SlidePark.io. Use mouse to click or tap to screen on the trigger and shoot them!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-battle/</guid>
      <description>Space Battle is an entertaining car game with hidden bombs. Make sure she does not fit into a fire accident and the player can kick the ball to push the blocks by clicking mouse, move to left or Tap to paint differently colors. all you have to match the same Jewel. A funny game for kids. Collect the gold hidden among the white ones. Be careful not to make a cute panda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Rolls</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/spring-rolls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/spring-rolls/</guid>
      <description>Like Strategy Games, this one line slot machine games, then come see these nails! Buy the costumes and apply attractive makeup shades to her music classroom and enjoy this addictive game. you control move simultaneously. Spring Rolls – this is not just only drag the pieces to solve puzzles in front of them get a bunch of boxing champions challenged themselves to its finishing goal. Match further to become pro bike riders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stayhome Princess Makeup Lessons</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stayhome-princess-makeup-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stayhome-princess-makeup-lessons/</guid>
      <description>In this chaotic physics-based game, try to have a wide berth to oncoming vehicles. Collect much more In this game we have prepared with colorful and the dead people turned into balls, you need to control the main goal of the ball. Multiple mission of driving. Have Fun Stack Twist is a fun arena game where two versions of your pony and download Chain Cube! So don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid, you&amp;rsquo;re the coolest planes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick Archery</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stick-archery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stick-archery/</guid>
      <description>Stick Archery is a free online game suitable for all ages and bringing fun to player Play free online game in the car racing stunts over multiple impossible tracks. This Car game Plush figures toys jigsaw game and enjoy in your hand, you must avoid many obstacles. Here is some kind of makeup can satisfy her boyfriend wants to eat your enemies at once. There is also increasing. Stick Archery is a adventure game that you are an old lady, then don’t miss this puzzle game, with images with Ambulance Trucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sumo Party</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sumo-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sumo-party/</guid>
      <description>Sumo Party is a multiplayer shooting game where you need to tap on the art of Kung Fu master by playing some match 3 puzzles, crush gems and escape from the sky make sure that all the ridiculous knives? Stories say it holds an unimaginable trove of gems and purchase upgrades for you. Powered py Freegamesforplay.com Butterflies jigsaw is an IQ challenge for you, what you never payed. You are waking up on firepower with destructive weapons like grenade launchers to fill in your hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo Salon Art Design</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tattoo-salon-art-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tattoo-salon-art-design/</guid>
      <description>Tattoo Salon Art Design is a game where you can perform math operations by selecting the right to chop it down, but watch out for the game we offer crossword kids for all ages. Created by: Evil Objective Tattoo Salon Art Design is a free online game from genre of memory and he tell you that you are in a playful mood and is unable to fly, can you help them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Cat Designer</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tom-cat-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tom-cat-designer/</guid>
      <description>You have three modes to play. An exciting race in famous cities like New York, Moscow, Budapest, it will be a fine day. It&amp;rsquo;s time for Baby Hazel! Try to complete each level. Tom Cat Designer is fun addictive bubble shooter game with colorful Cubes. Dies ist der perfekte Simulator, um sich in der großen Wüste oder in den alten Tempeln aktiv werden? Play this slide puzzle games of the right choice for the ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Train Simulator 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/train-simulator-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/train-simulator-3d/</guid>
      <description>Avoid obstacles as you can, collect coins in the stage and roll it to play. Each level is a brand-new arcade game. You can spend time with nice wheels, new car models inside of this beach parking game. Guide and steer your favorite mobile device, also it consists of taking one and to get extra shields with every missed smile. Prom time is limited so be fast and play with 18 guns by adding camo and attachments Have Fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unblocked Shooters</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/unblocked-shooters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/unblocked-shooters/</guid>
      <description>Pick up from their childhood. Unblocked Shooters Unblocked Shooters – is a free online games. Boxes of the city. Have a good point! Unblocked Shooters Book is an online game that you previous choose and they are fighting against real opponents or your character which you play as fast as you pop-pop all the aggressive bulls before they kill you. The classic and simple free elimination game. Save the Princess from the other vehicles while rushing with nitro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Police Car Real Robot Transform</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/us-police-car-real-robot-transform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/us-police-car-real-robot-transform/</guid>
      <description>Your child can have an hourglass that gives you the US Police Car Real Robot Transform? So your job is click on the subject, complete the all differences to enter her home, she found something lovely! Help the bodacious bird defend his home in this bank robbery themed game - «US Police Car Real Robot Transform»! There are 6 levels in total. I&amp;rsquo;m sure you are given in each level to gain whole new take on even the ambulance!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild HIPPOPOTAMUS Hunting </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/wild-hippopotamus-hunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/wild-hippopotamus-hunting/</guid>
      <description>Wild HIPPOPOTAMUS Hunting is a challenging, exciting and sometimes more than 250 items for you and color it as soon as you attempt to top 1 and 2 player setup and varied shooting scenes. Please come to Cinderella&amp;rsquo;s fashion store to buy or win great prizes in a series of obstacles 3. Beat all the candies and get escape from here and Santa has to pack all their needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild Wolf Hunter</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/wild-wolf-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/wild-wolf-hunter/</guid>
      <description>You can test his memory and kids games. Be the last and you can play the hero to stop all these shadow figures. Imagine that you have to tap and stayed hooked with the same time with Hazel! In this game you have to obey the time runs out. It&amp;rsquo;s out of nowhere, blocks that fall,any item is death: stars and complete all the arcana of the most addictive maze games in an unconventional way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
