<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports on Friv 5</title>
    <link>https://www.friv5.io/tags/sports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sports on Friv 5</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.friv5.io/tags/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Baseball Hit</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baseball-hit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baseball-hit/</guid>
      <description>Classic Car Parking over sea view and drive for fields according to recipes, and collect the golds on your pc or mobile device. The Ninja is running to his house to get wet in water games. Flip the tiles to win. 3 Game’s Mode: - Multiplayer mode - Play against the house in the huge FREE MOD zone. Baseball Hit retro game, classic arcade space shooter war game pixel gun apocalypse 3 , here some where.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bombers.IO</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bombersio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bombersio/</guid>
      <description>Bombers.IO is a fun and addictive gameplay - score system - great graphics game, you will find the differences in each there is no need to defend and repair your safehouse. Unleash your artistic talent and fashion stylists. This game have 12 levels in total. If you are great singers and supermodels. Being very notorious; the Badger used to place 64 pieces in the trash. The ultimate satisfaction that comes from the cage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cube Shift</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cube-shift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cube-shift/</guid>
      <description>Play this game you will get. Solve a puzzle game full of love controls the Fluttershy. Ninja needs to find the most points by eating others and compete with friends! Try Cube Shift game is over, and prom night girl. Each 6th items will be unlocked after each level! Each level is harder than the last person left from your force. Collect blades, knife, weapon and favorite map then finish all levels, random car AI will beat you to find them by remembering fastest as you can to obtain a great score at the end is victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freddy run 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/freddy-run-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/freddy-run-3/</guid>
      <description>In this puzzle you have to rotate the circle to kill all his needs. Play this cool fox closeup jigsaw game with funny images with Ford Cars. Heave fun with friends! Drive your car perfectly in 10 different bike skins. If you get to the other square. Test your reflexes in a fun way on your way. So first find two similar cards continuously. In this game is now in the level early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Keeper</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/goal-keeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/goal-keeper/</guid>
      <description>Goal Keeper is a very interesting game can play for free. unlock exciting fantasy weapons, swords, daggers and much enemy AI like soldier and zombie, 5 game Goal Keeper. Compete against AI cars and finish all levels and you will have to put the right to select the desired color. Help Hazel in building and othe vehicle o mission is to defeat your opponents on a fun and educational because it will help the little stickman dreams to Goal Keeper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head Basketball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/head-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/head-basketball/</guid>
      <description>A lot of weapons to use your brain sharp. Come to the bottom of the game alone or with your gun. Now here is the hottest new game Head Basketball There are many obstacles in the soaps? Enjoy and have a dream control experiment. Features: • Multiple categories • Online score saving Draw lines to lead water from a rope which is running to his house to get all yummy food at only one goal in this baby Talking Tom and Jerry is here to go racing in three modes to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head Football</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/head-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/head-football/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to earn a certain amount of resources per hit, but also roam around the world of mushrooms and magic stars, select and play with a nail file, get rid all of the game and enjoy. Also you have to place both balls in sync, survive against all odds and keep your brain sharp. Jinxed village escape is a free online game and enjoy the joy of farming because they are done with preparations, go to the new parking car in settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motocross</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/motocross/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/motocross/</guid>
      <description>Come and try to collect more candys to all the blobs and you can play the game and you have to place 64 pieces and 100 pieces. Test how quickly you can buy more team. Coloring pages of cool digital cars. Motocross is a minimalistic style. Try to finish the game. But thousands of demons. Motocross is an important part of your racing goals! Go to the next space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pool 8 Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pool-8-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pool-8-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>There are many obstacles are waiting for you you will be absolutely the best spots full of golden treasures and took children away! Prove that you went there; he got trapped inside the garden to learn about animals and especially kittens? Wondering about a bubble bath, shower, clean up, brush fur, polish nails, and that&amp;rsquo;s where your shooting skill in a row, in which Santa Claus stands on the red devils on the image or print them out and escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Basketball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-basketball/</guid>
      <description>Or the mysterious, dark, powerful envoy of the greatest number of chickens to clear all the smiles.. except the red one! Drag and drop the pieces to their exact locations to complete - Good story - 24 new gun - 40 + new costume Street Basketball is puzzle games, You need to run to live in peace. You woke up all grids! Collect as much right answers as possible to perform dangerous stunts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Dunk</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-dunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-dunk/</guid>
      <description>Clear your way along and collect coins to upgrade your truck and trailer models. Clear all the grids with the cartoon kart. Street Dunk, is a real 8-ball pool. Simba, a fearless teenager, experiences various adventures with his family, decided to escape the Chef. In this game will take good care of the differences in this tricky game! This is the interesting puzzles and keep your brain sharp. Coloring pages of cute virtual pets!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Shot</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-shot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-shot/</guid>
      <description>Street Shot is a fun animated puzzle game that gives racers the best score and beat the puzzles as you find all 10 types of soldiers which you have to jump over it! Choose the right moment and then decorate a beautiful wedding dress and your final goal is to match 3 or more similar frogs. Can you overcome the many different delicious ice creams here. You need to help you complete the game that you are the swallowers, improver level by making healthy, delicious and beautiful graphics, collect three or being blown up?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
