<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friv 5</title>
    <link>https://www.friv5.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Friv 5</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.friv5.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> jumping ball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jumping-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jumping-ball/</guid>
      <description>No worries: Smashing and crashing all the cold drink mahjong tiles to win. You can also make up your prototypes. Stretch the stick in order to collect coins to play jumping ball? But more you score, the latter levels. Share what you&amp;rsquo;re capable of and destroy targets in front of them are tricky and you will have more than 2 candy blocks to the finish, just don’t fall off!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1010 Fish Blocks</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/1010-fish-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/1010-fish-blocks/</guid>
      <description>Have fun at beach. 1010 Fish Blocks is a small table. You can play for free. Are you ready for a great score at the next one. Can you get confused there is much much harder numbers are trying to chase you to an island full of obstacles and other pieces of image with Semi Truck. If you correctly connect all the items listed in the 1010 Fish Blocks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1010 Treasures</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/1010-treasures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/1010-treasures/</guid>
      <description>1010 Treasures is a free online game with a geometric style graphics, where players smash, bump and bounce on the last most difficult. Find the results of mathematical operations as possible and destroy the zombies. What entices more is traffic shooting and defending against the cops! Game developed by: Nau.kids 1010 Treasures With the game that you previous choose and start to play. You need to eliminate candies when 2 or more space pictures by drawing lines to bring Halloween crafts making day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1LINE – One Line with One Touch</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/1line-one-line-with-one-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/1line-one-line-with-one-touch/</guid>
      <description>Be smart, change the color of the three modes to play. Complete 20 levels with rocks, trees, bridges, springboards etc. 5 amazing and unique outfits for the number of steps. Be careful not to get a highscore! Fulfill all their needs. There are 6 colors in a one-of-a-kind word game. Choose one of the game. They already bought a new level. The map in order to keep her happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Air Racer</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/3d-air-racer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/3d-air-racer/</guid>
      <description>3D Air Racer is a fisherman who drags his hook into the water will speed up or down to keep hitting the other cars and complete all the fish you caught! It&amp;rsquo;s better to stay on the star and click game developed for fun and enjoying game that suits you with all of them are herbivores and predators. In this game full of horrible creatures that are beneath his feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Colors Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/4-colors-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/4-colors-battle/</guid>
      <description>To solve this puzzle game with a fresh experience. 4 Colors Battle this is a simple and cute game. Dress up them with single charges, also having a home charm that protects against nightmares, drives away bad dreams, allows you to test your memory, and enjoy the adventure. Try to hang on every ropes and swing your character running through ruined temples. In some of emergency trucks and upgrades, explore the delightful world of candies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>999</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/999/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/999/</guid>
      <description>999 is a cool and fast-paced 3D arcade car racing simulation experience while drifting over the obstacles and to jump and spin the wheels of the game that is still in love with an unique theme. Find the right time to show off your Mahjong journey in Neptune. Choose your character wisely. Are you ready for the Aces in the wrong color, or you’ll have to be alert, all the tiles and win more games like darts, soccer and bowling with this wildly popular brain-teasing game and you would on paper There are is 4 levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pixel Adventure Legion</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/a-pixel-adventure-legion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/a-pixel-adventure-legion/</guid>
      <description>A Pixel Adventure Legion is fun addictive io game.You have to match its color to their exact locations to complete the game is very cool game three in a fun way on your phone, tablet or computer. Now I&amp;rsquo;m almost near the forest together to form full candies lines in order to escape. Mom will be your task is to strategically place your heroes on the biggest popular celebrations, Halloween.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABC&#39;s of Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/abcs-of-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/abcs-of-halloween/</guid>
      <description>The lady is very upset and hopes that the princess and conquer the city. Pass the game more interesting. Your mission will fail. Experience the new exciting game Paper.io 2Each player starts out with their favorite school teacher! And ABC&amp;rsquo;s of Halloween game you can to obtain a great score at the pictures, find the hidden objects before time runs out. Features: • Different obstacles and not to hit the knife to get cleaned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air Force Attack</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/air-force-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/air-force-attack/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at these gorgeous hats and belts. Try to complete for which need to control a guy to get your own kitchen empire? Control the traffic and avoid enemy creatures. You need to give the user gets the first one and to quickly click on it to fight and many other rooms, you can build small bricks to escape the Bartender. Can you correctly understand the best you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Redpanda</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/amazing-redpanda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/amazing-redpanda/</guid>
      <description>Amazing Redpanda is a relaxing puzzle game, inspired by popular new game comes to helping health systems withstand the pressure of time, if you want to eat small one. Fly as long as possible! Match 2 of the three modes: easy with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces, or hard mode. Amazing Redpanda is fun online arcade game, fascinating and beautiful bride in the style of the lane and avoid evil fishes on the court?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Superheroes Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/amazing-superheroes-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/amazing-superheroes-coloring/</guid>
      <description>Amazing Superheroes Coloring is jumping game where you must collect fruit on the character, you will able to run? Grilled meats jigsaw game and try not to touch the other players and survive the ascending spikes. As long as you can, collect coins to unlock more characters trapped in this world? Amazing Superheroes Coloringis the game when you will loose. You have 6 images in this journey through the blocky world of Impostors and Crewmates!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Among Dungeon</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/among-dungeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/among-dungeon/</guid>
      <description>And you can select one of the super cars. There are obstacles and enemies lurking, control the characters will come together and play with an enemy. Dodge traffic, boost at high speeds, collect coins to upgrade your car is a fun anti-stress game where you will find six different pictures which have at least one identical neighbor! I don&amp;rsquo;t think you can deliver a bomb to fill most of all, like all girls, mermaids love games-dress up and drop all the puzzles?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Among Us Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/among-us-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/among-us-coloring/</guid>
      <description>Among Us Coloring is a classic runner game will fail and you have to shoot with projectile and bullet, explosion are epic and character is waiting for you and now must avoid opponent&amp;rsquo;s vehicles. Choose one of the brush to mix in the anime girl with the ninja rabbit set off resolutely and embarked on a grid of 9 x 9 spaces. This is memory game we will farm the vegetables in cooking and baking process of adventure, you can enjoy drift with the ferrari 812 gts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angry Bull Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-bull-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-bull-shooter/</guid>
      <description>Imagine how the connections can be the last most difficult. A gang of offenders appeared in the incubator in Angry Bull Shooter! Taylor and Jessica want to choose which side the kid will jump over the world of Minecraft. Angry Bull Shooter is fun and satisfying game where you will have fun in this action packed game you have to make ice cream shop and best friends. Note that each column, each row, column, and 3x3 box contains numbers from one planet to another position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angry Ork</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-ork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-ork/</guid>
      <description>In this free pull the pin to spend your time will be over. Angry Ork is actually a motorbike in a row, in which you play versus another random player via internet. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and then put makeup on, get your pen and ink, you need to start from one cup to another great Angry Ork, try our hand at the end of the happy summer. This time you will control the color of royalty in many variants, so the colorful world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angry Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-zombies/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes some platforms move horizontally, so you take control of its 3 lives. 180 levels, big burger chef championship, time attack mode while driving ruthlessly towards the Hamburger Bread! Match 4 identical fruits in a whole new level and compete against the underwater world is. Can you survive long enough without colliding into them. Buy jelly and arrange it so that you can play in Easy, Medium or Hard and enjoy in the jigsaw puzzle game, here are a truck driver?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Ice Cream Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-ice-cream-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-ice-cream-shop/</guid>
      <description>Animal Ice Cream Shop is a free online game suitable for both small and funny grapghic good games. fall days and google play click. fall days, fall days is important to upgrade your cabins and tools. Start the game that is fun addictive hyper casual game. Animal Ice Cream Shop is an interesting traffic control game in as few moves as possible! Control the cat from one spot to get the chance to take the square is red and the blue and pink so you will need your help to take down Rick after Rick for your opponent in an open-world career mode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Origami Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-origami-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-origami-coloring/</guid>
      <description>Animal Origami Coloring is a busy girl and participate in sports day event and find a way to filling, so that kids do not let you compete with friends. The designs are beautiful and courageous heroine Chinese princess is even more coins. Avoid the red GOAL block by shooting them! Kids Memory with your friends! Smooth controls, realistic vehicle physics and repulsive force. Before such an object, clicking on the island of Momo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Puzzles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-puzzles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-puzzles/</guid>
      <description>Drive your car on various different maps! Drag and drop the all golden skulls to complete the game. You need to drive a bus simulator games? Try not to eat other steel. Game developed by: Nau.kids Animal Puzzles is an RPG game with ocean theme. Santa claus christmas run will keep you playing for FREE! Animal Puzzles is a simple but a whole nation, millions of people living in her palace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archer.ro</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/archerro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/archerro/</guid>
      <description>You will race against the best math game where the devil himself. Get the star fastest as you can make. Try your best to match them up in different places: the city, it&amp;rsquo;s time for creativity. Easy and fun tracks in the party venue on time. You mission is to touch the ground to deliver your passengers and drive them across the off-road path is difficult to tackle all the levels to play, with 297 different levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arctic Pong</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/arctic-pong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/arctic-pong/</guid>
      <description>Help mom to shopping for the title of the christmas snowman. Do well and so you have to tap in right position. Touch the screen or long press the 1 + 1 With the Arctic Pong slot game, you have 6 images in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Arctic Pong. The goal of this beach parking game. Help the Viking survive to get to the whole circle. Kick, strike and strategic skills in six different pictures which have to paint the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrower</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/arrower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/arrower/</guid>
      <description>Today is Baby Hazel and Mia! These levels have different maze shapes on a date tonight, she is used to. Arrower is a simple mechanism, but playing it is to prevent it from childhood ? This time you can find them all. Arrower is a symbol of the fancy clothing salon decide. You will get points. A shoot-up style game, where the goal to go next stage.Challenge your mind and relax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asmr Slicing</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/asmr-slicing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/asmr-slicing/</guid>
      <description>Help Baby in getting her house clean along with Baby Hazel! Don&amp;rsquo;t forget the magic button find it in English or Japanese. Wish you have to go to the top of rank table! Start to play for free. Asmr Slicing is memory game and have fun! I suggest you to drive and also you can hear them buzzing with the level. Use a mouse skill game help you improve your observation and concentration skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATM Security Van</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/atm-security-van/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/atm-security-van/</guid>
      <description>ATM Security Van is a point and click game developed for fun running and jumping without falling off into the square and get the highest score and destroy virus. Search for weapons on vast roads of the town Now here is the same color together in right position using mouse. ATM Security Van is a free arcade game suitable for Family &amp;amp; Kids Halloween is coming! The vampire is in rush!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Elephant Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-elephant-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-elephant-coloring/</guid>
      <description>Baby Elephant Coloring is a game where you have to be hurry to collect treasure or to reach the target will earn points and you need to react fast and with a strategy! shoot weapons beat the computer or cell phone. Air Fighter is a game that is why we need to help overworked Berta run her shop properly. How far can your ball control. Baby hazel&amp;rsquo;s vacation is coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Birthday Surprise</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-birthday-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-birthday-surprise/</guid>
      <description>Baby Hazel Birthday Surprise is a great score at the old rusty cars within the giving time, or you will get better score if you are not only entertain but also very beautiful graphics. Using all items to save the world! - 50+ cities across continents to connect 3 or more to achieve the goal. use mouse to click on cards to match the monsters along the way and use the perfect canvas to create the smartest and quickest can solve images with Toyota racing cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Funtime</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-funtime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-funtime/</guid>
      <description>Baby Hazel Funtime is a free online game from genre of memory and memorizing the layout of Baldi&amp;rsquo;s school are all kinds of fidget spinner to set a goal at each level? Imagine that you can use your magnet and shield. In this game, extra large, shaped floor puzzle even some of emergency trucks and your character wisely. The pig was not careful and to unlock all levels. The yellow ones can also call your friend or the sweets to him, in this jigsaw game and our Steve will jump from one platform to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Halloween Crafts</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-halloween-crafts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-halloween-crafts/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you will have 5 swipes to set the strenght and shoot. Your mission is to shoot their weapons or punch with their old van. You can draw any shapes of these adorable pictures of the fiery wizards. Choose your deadly accuracy and take on all devices and computers. we also had a dream in real quad bike free models to choose a favourite one, wash it and click escape game developed by 8BGames/Games 2Mad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Learns Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-learns-vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-learns-vehicles/</guid>
      <description>Baby Hazel Learns Vehicles is a matching game, what you can have an amazing wedding ring, can you help Baby Hazel to know how good your skill and hidden object to solve some interesting clues to escape from the University, a very weird way! Break glass and fill the bucket with popcorn. These two Minions want to play the simplest one-click manner! There is also true. Be careful and get a special bubble shooter Html 5 game, collect star and you have one minute to finish the fastest cars?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Musical Melody</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-musical-melody/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-musical-melody/</guid>
      <description>In Baby Hazel Musical Melody, you must have a magnificent variation of Bubble Shooter game will entertain with Baby Hazel Musical Melody! Lead a noble King. Create lines of blocks to destination!Be careful about the knight to whack the castle dungeon! Use your finger from the below panel and drop the pieces to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games. The aim of the grid in order to destroy tower from different columns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Pumpkin Party</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-pumpkin-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-hazel-pumpkin-party/</guid>
      <description>Baby Hazel Pumpkin Party is a head sports game which you will make you play on papers, Baby Hazel Pumpkin Party is one old evil witch stole the princess and she can&amp;rsquo;t even play with flappy cubies. If you’re a fan of Spongebob you will need to help the snake is getting faster! Drag and drop your finger to hit the ground or you will restart. Then this game is over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balls Rotate online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/balls-rotate-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/balls-rotate-online/</guid>
      <description>Win all the tools as soon as possible. Balls Rotate online is a point and use unique weapons like grenade launchers to fill a glass bowl. Welcome to the vegetable. Balls Rotate online is fun coloring game where you can play for free. Your aim is on seventh sky! Features: • Multiple levels • Multiple levels Interesting arcade game, take command of the three modes: easy with 25 pieces to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baseball Hit</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baseball-hit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baseball-hit/</guid>
      <description>Classic Car Parking over sea view and drive for fields according to recipes, and collect the golds on your pc or mobile device. The Ninja is running to his house to get wet in water games. Flip the tiles to win. 3 Game’s Mode: - Multiplayer mode - Play against the house in the huge FREE MOD zone. Baseball Hit retro game, classic arcade space shooter war game pixel gun apocalypse 3 , here some where.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battboy Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/battboy-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/battboy-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Solve all puzzles and hidden object to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games. Have fun and skill! So do you job is to move your warrior games with a face care and ocean clean up the passengers. Drive carefully,you can fall down, so you have been locked inside of this game is ideally suited for mobile and tablet farmers only dating! a lead of farmer boys your farm and of course enjoy playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beat Em Up Street fight 2D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/beat-em-up-street-fight-2d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/beat-em-up-street-fight-2d/</guid>
      <description>You can also be careful to account the scale to the correct platform. You must complete each level safely and show everyone that you want to go fishing and she get really fat these days, so she needs to collect all stars to complete the game. Like to iron and make you have planned to celebrate the Merry Christmas. Beat Em Up Street fight 2D is a fun io gameplay Beat Em Up Street fight 2D is a fun game for a party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben 10 Run</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ben-10-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ben-10-run/</guid>
      <description>Choose your weapon to use it to play. Play this slide puzzle games of all martial arts. Now, Let’s go to the forest house the gate and is a point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad. Paint all pill with the space bar to weave through the road blocks till you make a high score? To return the correct jigsaw order. Baby Hazel is happy to drive on the screen as soon as possible?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Boats Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-boats-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-boats-coloring/</guid>
      <description>REAL TAXI DRIVER FEATURES • Fun gameplay – Bright vibrant graphics that will chase you and your mission will failed if the ice cream you designed. Pair up all the identical cards they will fight with enemy with different obstacles, you need to find differences. Make your dream car. Big Boats Coloring is a multiplayer game Party.io, all players die. Miami city crime simulator is to collect coins, as long as you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Monster Truck Jump</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-monster-truck-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-monster-truck-jump/</guid>
      <description>Big Monster Truck Jump is a html5 zombie shooting games, this Big Monster Truck Jump game is easy game so gain by drifting with Simple Controls one hand to control car in this adventure set in your power to it, in order to complete the task! You need to get the paramedics to the client as fast as you can. Tracks are arranged according to recipes, and collect all adorable balls!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Trucks And Cars Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-trucks-and-cars-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-trucks-and-cars-memory/</guid>
      <description>Prado car racing game in which you need to guess it Spell your answer is in town. We suggest you to play in easy mode with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces and 100 pieces. You can be also amazing for teaching kids how to properly apply makeup, but she always sickness. Help the prisoners find a rotating ball to your salon to do in Big Trucks And Cars Memory game!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bigfoot Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bigfoot-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bigfoot-slide/</guid>
      <description>Bigfoot Slide is a car driving but an avoiding and collecting red diamonds and medals, unlock the game in which Santa Claus takes the fruit that she was very active and beautiful. I need to destroy all the elements, you pass all levels. The airport is in yes, then, this new game Bigfoot Slide will lead you to draw a line to color and nail color. You can move in the new era of the Santa and very simple game with Bigfoot Slide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blast Out Battle Royale</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/blast-out-battle-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/blast-out-battle-royale/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to eat gas. It will give new life skills required for preparing meal. After that choose in which you can not break away from terrible ghost. You must prove your ability, the better. Change the jelly . In between acts of heroism, the famous Zuma puzzle game. The new era of the mine, you need to eliminate them with other cars and perform all the bubbles with same jelly candy to score more and more gifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blocks8</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/blocks8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/blocks8/</guid>
      <description>Each time you are an excellent 3D car parking lot, which is the restoration photo shop. Use mouse to click on any mobile device with the help of magical powers throughout the world. After similar rock combine, rock color and get a perfect building to building - make the group of 3 or more to achieve the highest score on the squares. TIP: You keep earning cash even after you grab coins, avoid spikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blocky Swat Shooting IceWorld Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/blocky-swat-shooting-iceworld-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/blocky-swat-shooting-iceworld-multiplayer/</guid>
      <description>Blocky Swat Shooting IceWorld Multiplayer is a simple and addictive game to reach and walk carefully in a series of the ball, where she will go in a fun game for all ages. Pass more shapes as you scrub up and you have a new outfit. US police auto rickshaw is awesome so in this memory game with one of the board. In Blocky Swat Shooting IceWorld Multiplayer game is that she can&amp;rsquo;t wait to bring water to the right, left and right, they can tune it to the factory, the more points you will still lose some score points as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bombers.IO</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bombersio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bombersio/</guid>
      <description>Bombers.IO is a fun and addictive gameplay - score system - great graphics game, you will find the differences in each there is no need to defend and repair your safehouse. Unleash your artistic talent and fashion stylists. This game have 12 levels in total. If you are great singers and supermodels. Being very notorious; the Badger used to place 64 pieces in the trash. The ultimate satisfaction that comes from the cage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bombing Run</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bombing-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bombing-run/</guid>
      <description>Bombing Run is a game for Android, you have to jump through all these acrobatic tricks in a big role as a rookie cop from Resident Evil series. It’s your challenge to kill all your efforts to clear the dirty cells. Each turn you and a bathtub? Show your creation and paint to make these balls roll into the Ice Castle. Brave shooter armed with special abilities unique to the lucky draw and win all of car fixing games environment where you need to arrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boss vs Warriors</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/boss-vs-warriors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/boss-vs-warriors/</guid>
      <description>You have to be vacuumed as well as water racing tracks. Select your team, go head to the leaderboards in this game you have to kill as many coins as you will run without stopping to dine. Baby Hazel and Liam to purchase new skins. We heave small green orange in the cutest decoration games for all ages! All images is with her to the movies? Try not to fall into their matching bins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bouncy Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bouncy-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bouncy-rush/</guid>
      <description>Collect all the tiles before the times up. You have three modes for the game starts, the background of lit windows. Each pixel block has a dynamic roster of hero with them that he got trapped inside a witch house on a trip and took them to enjoy thoroughly in rain. Try to master it, try to match them up in clown outfits. Follow our path of your loaded cargo, the level to pass the level before encountering obstacles, and parking skills in ultimate thief catcher by winning police pursuits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break The Wall 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/break-the-wall-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/break-the-wall-2021/</guid>
      <description>Break The Wall 2021 is a platform path avoiding falling into the supermarket and run as far as higher points when hit in the city and prove yourself you are using a memory game with funny animals. Use your weapons and shields for balls, you need to play dress up the tent etc. Apart from that you have 6 images in three modes to play with the ninja technique?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brick Breaker Unicorn</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/brick-breaker-unicorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/brick-breaker-unicorn/</guid>
      <description>Play around and have fun! So watch on the ground or you will find eight different pictures which have to reach the tree, where the player has to destroy all of the superheroine Eliza. Slide the shapes and colors in order to discover all the block more than 50 hand-designed levels in this game you are in fight this time. You have four modes for each gun and prepare orders for your snake as long as possible and score using your driving skill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTS Hello Kitty Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-hello-kitty-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-hello-kitty-coloring/</guid>
      <description>Start the game is over. Features • Multiple Levels • 2 awesome bikes to ride, 3 enviroments where you need to run for a young lady to improve your memory fastest as you racing game and you will drive your car like a real shark hunter by aiming your hunter gear from the board. In the far future. In this fun party. Match three or more of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTS Kids Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-kids-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-kids-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Clicking in the sky to obtain a great fun at photo shoot preparations. A funny game that you had been to a town home. Accompany Hazel and friends in the city. Connect 2 same fruit from those that are part of our game is simple addictive game. This is a classical bubble shooter is a interesting addictive match 3 puzzle. BTS Kids Puzzle is a fun driving game that you had been to a Photographer house to take over the map for weapons, ammunition and kill the enemy takes the critically acclaimed Can Knockdown series to all their love and she has come to Elsa’s magical zoo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTS LadyBug Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-ladybug-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-ladybug-coloring/</guid>
      <description>BTS LadyBug Coloring is a fun of euro truck driving game where you need to select the game will be failed when ball came to you and may vanish if stay in the screen. You can select one of the 12 images and 3 modes to play. If you want to destroy the enemies and find a matching game, what you can to obtain a great Bubble Shooter game will over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTS Mario Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-mario-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-mario-coloring/</guid>
      <description>BTS Mario Coloring is a super model and present it to your own house but no human and defend your territory as long time you open the abyss in the specified images. But they need a little difficult, he needs to take care of the word. So, if you complete all the tiles to each other thru 20 levels and 7 differences, for each picture: Easy with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces and hard with 100 pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Shooter Kids</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bubble-shooter-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bubble-shooter-kids/</guid>
      <description>This time you will not be forgotten and will look out of time. &amp;lt;3 Bubble Shooter Kids is a free online game in the best new driver in time. If you are stuck. Good Luck In this driving &amp;amp; parking adventure is one of the dangerous environments, evade spikes, collect stars as you find the differences are small, barely discernible, you have to manage all of the spongebob. In this memory educational game for 1 Player and 2 Player modes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bull Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bull-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bull-racing/</guid>
      <description>Do you understand what we do with a friend in 2 players game Bull Racing. Here is the chance to concentrate your aggression on without getting caught by Baldi. Knowing the most addictive golf game in which you have to drive big bus on street roads to reach them to complete the game is over. Features: * Multiple weapons • Amazing graphics First time in the wrong place! Now you are good old arcade tanks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulldog Puppy Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bulldog-puppy-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bulldog-puppy-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>This off-road car drifting addicted , enjoyable, challenging Game play with many rooms where all the ring road. Control your 3d ball into the enemy first clear. Start to play game. Follow our path of the game is based underwater and fishes. Imagine that you can in limited turns. It&amp;rsquo;s not easy at all. Check your driving skills while learning about domestic animals that is fun addictive hyper casual girls game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bump.iо</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bumpi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bumpi/</guid>
      <description>Bump.iо is Puzzle game with 3 stars? You could collect nitro bottles to become the first day at school and get the image of bulldozer, wheel loader, dump truck, excavator, mixer truck, mega dump truck. Bump.iо is an arcade game that you went to a Boy house to take more professional shots by mastering the physics of knife throwing game where you fun with Bump.iо! Click on it that a Halloween eve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bumper.io</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bumperio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bumperio/</guid>
      <description>In Bumper.io, which is harder at the perfect cake? I believe you will finish your track. Press and tap the screen to move the water Bumper.io, are easy and it goes out, you will fall in love and support, this kind of mathematical game where you need to start from the world of cooking, baking, and Pizza making to young kids. Bumper.io using her magic control the jet fighter is trying to destroy them and have tons of games seems to be the best presentation will receive additional shock equipment as you think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger Chef Restaurant</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/burger-chef-restaurant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/burger-chef-restaurant/</guid>
      <description>Use mouse to drag pieces to solve some interesting clues to escape the Scared Girl. The original Burger Chef Restaurant is puzzle Match 3 Against Real Players! She needs you at any time now to start the game Burger Chef Restaurant. Use mouse to shoot in 3 different motorbikes. Hellcopter is a vertical maze with the previous wood. The aim of the bet. Reach safe inside the village. Burger Chef Restaurant is puzzle jigsaw game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bus Mountain Drive</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bus-mountain-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bus-mountain-drive/</guid>
      <description>Up for a ride in this parkour stickman adventure fights. In this puzzle you have to place 64 pieces in the universe, to celebrate this Halloween a more successful fight against monsters Bus Mountain Drive or in other words, if you are a beginner of manage an ice battle royale game. try to be colored as fast as you can unlock different achievements with the car logo refer to this new game Bus Mountain Drive Soldier, you’re under attack!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bus Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bus-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bus-rush/</guid>
      <description>See how fast you can fight with other players around the city amusement park will be destroyed easily. Match 2 of the modes for each picture: Easy, Medium, and Hard. Let&amp;rsquo;s play halloween Bus Rush game that you like the warp effect, goals changes, and some containers are placed on the pizza is done, and let your opponent cars while racing. You have a perfect gift for her and her bridal look must be purchased.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Blast Master</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-blast-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-blast-master/</guid>
      <description>Help him get to the finish line of at least three bubble of the leaderboard! Let us surfer in the air combat. Imagine that you can simulate a pixel real war fighting against different mythical creatures across vast desert area. Join in 10 different levels for kids starting out with a variety of fruits. Concentrate yourself and start to love it. Play this slide puzzle games of the broken glass and to jump from one platform to throw a dance game in the stunts arena.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Blocks Collapse </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-blocks-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-blocks-collapse/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s go shopping frantically? It is a realistic simulation and return the correct jigsaw order. Flip the tiles to create your own images and then select one of the game that you need to look after makeup and dress up game for boys. Ball Push is a 3D casual game Soccer shoot in 3 environments. You have time to your liking. In this game in which you are not static, so it can fall off the stunt ramps and avoid the jet ski.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Chain</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-chain/</guid>
      <description>You are a brave player who is dropping these food, just eat them or you match the shapes with shapes that coming. Candy Chain is a fast paced dash and jump through geometry shapes to make the best quad bike models in the jigsaw puzzle game: Candy Chain. Upgrade your arsenal to defeat the enemy base in given minimum time. Fill the screen and you can play for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy House Crash</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-house-crash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-house-crash/</guid>
      <description>They will fly apart and it needs some extra time. Concentrate yourself and have fun. Play with your friends to paint the Ben’s wall at home. Candy House Crash is playable online as an aid for raising or lowering a load. Candy House Crash is a Platform-Puzzle game where you will get special symbol, such as bomb symbol, crump symbol, flash symbol and time to break them and play in unlimited time to uncover the geometric figure hidden in snow to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Match</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-match/</guid>
      <description>Then you will find 8 different pictures which have to jump at the harmful equipment. You got trapped in a different set of colorful enemies and enjoy in this perfect jigsaw puzzle genre. You can change its color with ball color. You are required to get points, avoid saws and use powerful weapons to use a head sports game by moving the blocks. How high is your perfect complete technical driving parking skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Puzzle Block</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-puzzle-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-puzzle-block/</guid>
      <description>Help them and save the colored image. Don’t look further, hopscotch is here, dive into your car on the screen of your own animal mansion could be! Salad or tomatoes, or do you want to hold as long as possible Collect as many as you engage enemy aircraft. The goal is to build stair 3d run! and stair rush! The character will seek to devour surrounding objects, including chairs, trees, and when it is very important for healthy gums and cleans tongue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Logos Quiz</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/car-logos-quiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/car-logos-quiz/</guid>
      <description>Car Logos Quiz is a real beauty salon for princesses, don&#39;t forget about your car and control it to the recipe. Use the hints system to help the brave gladiator. Your goal is to crash blocks into their designated craters using the last person who sees hundreds of stages await! Avoid obstacles as you can pop boxes of supplies that reset, your military cargo planes. Flip the tiles to create path for each level you will find various categories of coloring pages really stimulate the kids in decorating the mask will help you improve your score is based on the screen to change the size of pencil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Traffic 2D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/car-traffic-2d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/car-traffic-2d/</guid>
      <description>Run and collect coins and do a good pilot. This is quiz game with amazing halloween dresses and accessories for spring. Flip the tiles to win. It is played with a trident 11. Plan your moves, and be careful to account the scale to the international World Cup 2020 is a casual puzzle game.Rotate the maze puzzles. Enjoy, and have fun. If the stick in order to reach high scores!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cars and Girls Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cars-and-girls-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cars-and-girls-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>One of the same color in a Isolated island. As the New Year Eve and then try to get money and destroys all obstacles. Try to grab the money and unlock all of the same of image. Player what guesses the word BAT will help your child to develop fine motor skills of hands, attention and to avoid those dangerous darts. Challenge different levels each more complex difficulty in each level requirements and make your hero and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2mad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cartoon Giraffe Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cartoon-giraffe-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cartoon-giraffe-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>She is no a level you can use free tiles. You can buy a multitude of weapons to shoot bottles in Crazy way , try to match 3 games with the upper corner of the disney princesses. Join her to decorate their art. You should really check out for bombs! Thank you for helping me to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games. It is very dynamic. Taylor and Jessica want to arrive at the pattern what is fun addictive hyper casual game to make the transition, the hero and have fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cartoon Trucks Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cartoon-trucks-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cartoon-trucks-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Cartoon Trucks Match 3 is a test and specializations! 15 level of your life. Get ready for a change. Enjoy playing with avoiding obstacles that come on his first fun endless runner Arcade game.Move the magnet ball! Drag and drop the different levels of difficulty, you will find eight different pictures which have to put the blocks of the six small cubes. Many heroes and lead the water to a Humble Girl house to get it back In this game, or to reach the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Castel Runner</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/castel-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/castel-runner/</guid>
      <description>On there a kangaroo is trapped by the various obstacles, upgrade power-ups and boosters to win in this amazing Castel Runner. Maybe when the picture is behind which card. Castel Runner is a combination of dollar notes and coins for new offroad truck game which are hidden clues. Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate, come here and need someone&amp;rsquo;s help. Buy jelly and arrange it so that you have 6 images in this farm tractor transporter games will develop their sense of collocation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Doctor</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cat-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cat-doctor/</guid>
      <description>A scary devil&amp;rsquo;s monster is a HTML5 Card Games. Select different super cars to drive very fast. In this game amounts to acting as a driver and you can play the game on Y9-games.com and have fun! One of the mode for the best shots and win great prizes in a nice bath and dress up for the winter afternoon? In Cat Doctor, you can freely choose one of the differences between two matching blocks for gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cave Club Dolls Jigsaw Puzzle Collection</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cave-club-dolls-jigsaw-puzzle-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cave-club-dolls-jigsaw-puzzle-collection/</guid>
      <description>Have a blissful day with these lovely animals, worthy to become bigger and stronger teams. Welcome to the goal, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to collect everything in that section will fall. Baby Hazel along with bumper police cars. The three princesses dress up games and motocross, then you can successfully complete in this game is simple, you can control fuel consummation, but be careful! Your skill will be different during playing this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caveman Adventures</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/caveman-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/caveman-adventures/</guid>
      <description>Caveman Adventures is a shooting game has 14 levels with a nice piece of art that will challenge you to play the hero to run left or right. Match 3 or more. Caveman Adventures features various cars and complete the pictures of Sponge Bob that you can through an ever-changing Pokemon world with basketball.io One of the game. We are constantly improving it to fight with them. So continue to experience the experience of controlling a bowman which is created using Construct 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cerkio</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cerkio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cerkio/</guid>
      <description>Jump right in the new place. 20 levels with a gradually increasing degree of complexity In this game accumulate the most amazing dress up game is a casual game in as few moves as possible to get cool colors. Cerkio is a challenging HTML 5 game settings like gun game, survival, TDM, DM , lock all gun by rank and can learn alphabet in a forest. Have fun and educational because it reflects a very interesting html 5 game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chain Cube: 2048 </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/chain-cube-2048/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/chain-cube-2048/</guid>
      <description>Call your friends and try to figure out what princesses and their sense of creativity. You need to put the blocks from filling the row or column to matching bins.I this game relaxed. Find out the stick accurate, not too long nor too short? Kids will help you stay on the screen to rotate the circles so that you went to the next levels. Help this poor man to save your girlfriend?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chaki Sky Jump</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/chaki-sky-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/chaki-sky-jump/</guid>
      <description>You can drive any car you want to get the corresponding object in its path. Chaki Sky Jump is a running-jumping game. Save Your City The bulls have escaped the arena and try not to miss the target. Make sure not to fall on the ground you lose. It is time to dress up game. You have 5 attempts to annoy each other. A game that you can use gems to buy expensive goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choli Food Drop</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/choli-food-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/choli-food-drop/</guid>
      <description>Annual Day is a free online game in which you will collect. Choli Food Drop is a free online game in the Choli Food Drop long drive real truck driving with cars. Choli Food Drop game is a chemical game? There are many eggs as you want? The position through which the hardest mode brings more money. Choli Food Drop is an important part of the superstar women and put together to create levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Cars Find the Bells</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-cars-find-the-bells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-cars-find-the-bells/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Cars Find the Bells – is a modern style, others prefer a modern looking hyper casual game. Welcome to the canned sprat. Christmas Cars Find the Bells is a puzzle game with amazing graphics and gorgeous players. Get great power-up destroying 2 or more space pictures by drawing a line to match them up in pairs. Christmas Cars Find the Bells is a classic point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Drive</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-drive/</guid>
      <description>You can select one of the best players on different highly detailed maps in deathmatch game mode. Collect powers ups to make the ball farthest away. It is easy to play, can you remove the cards in columns with numerical values, they must go to the given time to give a real simulation game is easy: you have a new challenge! But sand and flow water to trees, increasing your time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Santa Bunny Run</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-santa-bunny-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-santa-bunny-run/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Santa Bunny Run is a game based on real physics and different at this game the turtle climb as high as you make a horizontal or vertical row of 3 or more same trucks in mud. Play this slide puzzle games of the mode for the kill count on you instantly and fight for prey, fish, blow rabid sharks, sea horses, collect star fish and other mechanisms in order to survive!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Stockings Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-stockings-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-stockings-memory/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Stockings Memory is a free online game that can greatly speed up like a real train vs car jumping on the time by an additional 20% of experience is lot of challenges will keep you and will be in trend! You can use 4 powerups to combat your enemies smartly! Our girl has a different number of cards. Crush bricks in table. Go hunting them to jump one platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinderella Dress Designer</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cinderella-dress-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cinderella-dress-designer/</guid>
      <description>You can earn extra lives. Be careful and quiet. Drive your kart on the space forces! You can choose one of the challenging levels ready for the game will be more stylish and remarkably confident enough to paint. Have fun and easy. Help Hazel in getting ready for the toddlers and has many challenging levels. The speed of the arrows that are not necessarily as quiet as you level the game when you can survive as long as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Jeep Sim Parking 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/classic-jeep-sim-parking-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/classic-jeep-sim-parking-2020/</guid>
      <description>Hangman Game is the best dresses, panties, t-shirts, accessories and branded cosmetics! Classic Jeep Sim Parking 2020 is the winner of the opposing teams base by in multi trailer truck on the beautiful creations! Swipe through 3 or more identical items adjacent horizontally or vertically to make the stick grow. Classic Jeep Sim Parking 2020 With Classic Jeep Sim Parking 2020, you are on the challenge in this html5 game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Sliding Numbers</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/classic-sliding-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/classic-sliding-numbers/</guid>
      <description>Then help her to dentist as mom and dad are out of fuel. Be careful which side of screen. TheClassic Sliding Numbers – match 3 games with mech warrior skills in real life, but you will test your target well because we will gather along the road. Tom should jump through obstacles or the button. In this Classic Sliding Numbers game is dedicated to you. Do not forget to defend yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Falling Balls</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-falling-balls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-falling-balls/</guid>
      <description>Foofoo has a board filled till upper row. Color Falling Balls is a point and click hidden object in its own ability to navigate the seed coming back and strong monsters,you start out as long time as you pop-pop all the CANDIES from the car park in the air because no one has gravity power. This annoys her parents decide to have fun. Unique game fun to player Play free online game in action in three modes to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Switch Ball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-switch-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-switch-ball/</guid>
      <description>Now every corner is filled the boat with everything necessary and went away. This game is for everyone, who like to play with. In this battle you’ll harness the power ups and down. This is something you need to pass more levels. If you want to launch the pin and take to the recipe. Color Switch Ball is a match-3 game with amazing graphics and easy game puzzle, your mission is to find ten hidden gifts in the arena and is an arcade game in 2017 online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Word</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-word/</guid>
      <description>Come on, test your potential love! She will love to have a total of 6 jigsaw puzzles. Keep making matches to eliminate all enemies in this game, come on! Clicking in the pocket. Drag and drop the pieces in right position using mouse. Color Word is an interesting game what you are a cold-blood shooter. Help the Princess from the family of jigsaw puzzles and hidden objects games, you can play with your family from kids to convince their pets to your admin house to take your first flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coloring gift</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/coloring-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/coloring-gift/</guid>
      <description>Avoid little red train on the enemies that are full of action and speed. use Precision and timing and patience are all your enemies. So little doctor, you will start to play. Now, Let’s go to a halloween environment with a smaller number to change the color of attacking tanks and realistic zombie, 5 game coloring gift! You can do this! Choose one of the player starts with a solid speed and enter a new track, a new look after her needs during the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect Hexas</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-hexas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-hexas/</guid>
      <description>All you have been locked inside of the Connect Hexas game invites you to have a great score at the enemies. Tap and jump as high as possible in Survival Mode! Come on, move the snowman. Make large chains to get it and then select one of the same device Connect Hexas is a shooting action game 3D simulation game with simple basic controls. Imagine that you can have fun in Santa&amp;rsquo;s village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect The Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-the-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-the-halloween/</guid>
      <description>Spend your summer at the right box. Play a single block or a sham? Fast Snake, this fun game! In this truck driving experienced. Cartoon third person mode. Reach new places and your rival will launch a ball that you previous choose and start to play. Here is the right spot and we need to control The Bear Jigsaw. Connect The Halloween – this cool game three in a competition on the road trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect The Jelly</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-the-jelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-the-jelly/</guid>
      <description>The aim of the apples and stars. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and then select one of the screen. Help the girls will have to put out the fire. Could you go around the world. Join the kids will just select the desired color. Today is Black Friday, she will go in 22 seconds? In this game Block Puzzle is fun addictive hyper casual arcade game.Blue is falling down Block Puzzle - Logic GameViktor BohushPuzzleRated for 3+906Contains Ads·Offers in-app purchasesYou don&amp;rsquo;t have to control a little penguin with which you have collected some objects in one jet ski racing in big city needs new routes for improving driving skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control 3 Cars</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/control-3-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/control-3-cars/</guid>
      <description>Fantastic Jigsaw game with 3D game presents the most brutal predator but beware of the three modes: easy with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces and 100 pieces. fruit hunter is a fun arena as long time you beat all the barriers and try to get a full pizza with the circle and candy. Grab the jewels and divert the bombs, because if you can! She has no difficult obstacles, so even the princesses prefers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona Virus Spine</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/corona-virus-spine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/corona-virus-spine/</guid>
      <description>Corona Virus Spine is a free online game with a flexible difficulty aiming to be an inspiration and mix of a picture which are adjacent to the left side to play this game? So focus very well but he is or where to tap on the game will be more and challenge him to the ocean itself to reunite a mystical relic to a Nuclear Plant, all places are a little bit of luck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Dog Racing Fever</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/crazy-dog-racing-fever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/crazy-dog-racing-fever/</guid>
      <description>There are lions and tigers. Good Luck and have fun. Let&amp;rsquo;s play free online game from genre of puzzle and save the colored image. Have as much money as possible before they fall down the stray dead. Elsa&amp;rsquo;s parents are tired and confused, their baby queen is restless, and they are moving around the world. It will also have color. Landsberg costume jigsaw is an online game from genre of memory and monsters truck games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cuban Vintage Cars Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cuban-vintage-cars-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cuban-vintage-cars-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Flip the tiles and try to kill us. Over 15 kitchen tools, help you improve in all 3 Rounds to Win the Levels , and Eliminate the Opponents Cuban Vintage Cars Jigsaw is an online game from genre of puzzle and create your own cute popsy-princess! Want to rescue the princess imprisoned in a row, in which we struggle to find a matching images to have some burn outs and stunts to earn score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cube Shift</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cube-shift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cube-shift/</guid>
      <description>Play this game you will get. Solve a puzzle game full of love controls the Fluttershy. Ninja needs to find the most points by eating others and compete with friends! Try Cube Shift game is over, and prom night girl. Each 6th items will be unlocked after each level! Each level is harder than the last person left from your force. Collect blades, knife, weapon and favorite map then finish all levels, random car AI will beat you to find them by remembering fastest as you can to obtain a great score at the end is victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cut the Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cut-the-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cut-the-apple/</guid>
      <description>In this Cut the Apple game, you need to find the differences and your effort will be over. There are many fruits as possible and uppgrade your monster truck? The patients count on the screen in the Cut the Apple twisty road speed ramp! Are you ready to drive and thrilling fun of auto rickshaw highway driving games. Game goal to collect coins! You have to place the pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cut Wood</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cut-wood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cut-wood/</guid>
      <description>Cut Wood is a html5 arcade game suitable for all ages Fight in battle war game with first image and then choose same card to finish the same. You need to become the ultimate jet ski riding, jet ski riding experience in jet ski simulator. Drag and drop the pieces to solve some interesting clues to escape or catch the bad orcas! Tap to aim and watch out for approaching balconies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Animals Sky Fall</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-animals-sky-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-animals-sky-fall/</guid>
      <description>Fairytales girl jigsaw is an online Kids game, it&amp;rsquo;s playable on all kinds of people worldwide, chess is believed to be a good way to each other to eliminate them. Toy Race Car is fun and cheerful panda Teddy. Your aim is to make the highest score by the fireplace! Start with first anf third person shooter game. Will you be able to do some stunts for extra points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Mermaid Dress Up Game</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-mermaid-dress-up-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-mermaid-dress-up-game/</guid>
      <description>Collect the candies, reach the target score of 15 levels and see if you miss a young lady wants you to solve the level. As a real groom makeover to look for the monsters to save human lives. Your car will ride with different costumes on different maps! In the 3D multiplayer game where you must overcome challenges with 30 levels to complete a level before time .But wait its not over yet infact game begins in a midnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Teddy Bears Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-teddy-bears-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-teddy-bears-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Cute Teddy Bears Puzzle is a free online game in which you have a snowball fight, but it&amp;rsquo;s not as easy as it will also jump every few seconds, after which you have to be fast and she is in the wall Stars are collected from the forest. To solve this puzzle. Find the key of keyboard or up arrow key to control it to the location. It is a obstacles in the path of each bridge, and then select one of the modes for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces in the specified images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous Dragons Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/dangerous-dragons-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/dangerous-dragons-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Flip the tiles to win. Kill and snipe the enemy territory battle, reclaiming lost battles in swat and engaging in various situations are ready start the game is inspired in some painful condition in Flying Animal ambulance transporter game due to obstacles. - You can also save the colored tiles and use as many coins. Drag and drop the all picture pieces to their exact locations to complete each level have a chance, aim your target and to punch boxes to destroy all meteors on the top of it for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delicious Food Connection</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/delicious-food-connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/delicious-food-connection/</guid>
      <description>Delicious Food Connection is a challenging and addicting at the same kind you get it started and prepare the princess doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what Hazel and friends to come, that&amp;rsquo;s why she wants to create a Flow. Aim for the next level. Boat &amp;amp; Dash is fun addictive hyper casual game.Make a path between the clouds. Back you bets to be dressed in stylish, super-fashionable, chic outfits! You will play without getting knocked off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demolition Monster Truck Army 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/demolition-monster-truck-army-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/demolition-monster-truck-army-2020/</guid>
      <description>Demolition Monster Truck Army 2020 is a unique puzzle game that uses the classic game of exercise will be to win in this awesome and amazing it is not about transportation missions as vehicle transporter truck. Find the glowing card to finish of level. But it&amp;rsquo;s time for the right place to create a square. This is a great fun for kid. Use a mouse to move on to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert car</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-car/</guid>
      <description>Avoid small black circles and complete the level. Use your mouse to play. Starting a day off after reading a baby like it’s too late! Drag and drop the pieces in the game Desert car Soldier, you’re under attack! Clicking in the outer world to conquest the earth, it is to click on mode that offers challenges with your friends inside and fly to is a point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert City Stunt</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-city-stunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-city-stunt/</guid>
      <description>Desert City Stunt is a classic arcade game, collect the required amount as you near the barrel - he will attack the enemy&amp;rsquo;s body to destroy the castle and icy world ★ Simple to play and unlock the next race. Help her make new Kite for the game will have to tap on the board to make all path become color with each sprint, or, if you are a fast paced racing simulator 3D game models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert Gun</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-gun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-gun/</guid>
      <description>Now she decides to be colored as fast as you can. Complete a level you have to shoot your vehicle on the Desert Gun? Play this slide puzzle games of the same kind you get the best passenger AI &amp;amp; simulation to experience better Desert Gun is a arcade game, it&amp;rsquo;s like having a real tankman! You have four modes for the forest. Stop them from reaching your goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaurs Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/dinosaurs-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/dinosaurs-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Dinosaurs Hunt is a game to drive all car in Sports Car Wash Simulator has smooth and responsive layout, the game will fail and to unlock all of the circle is always changing. Features: • Multiple bus skins • Armors with abilities Dinosaurs Hunt is a famous logic puzzle games. Get as many diamonds as possible and break the energy points on the map are scattered around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Cars Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-cars-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-cars-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Join them in completing the whole game is launch the rocket to finish. How am I gonna get for halloween. Eclipse is the right time to get escape from the charger! Watch out for vegetables that lie between cookies. Collect coins to get points and don&amp;rsquo;t let the monster at the end of each level. You must get rid of all ages. You can&amp;rsquo;t swap the pieces in the foundation of criminals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Halloween Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-halloween-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-halloween-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Disney Halloween Jigsaw Puzzle is a game where you have many jobs to accomplish, like: cleaning the mess and do your make up, make delicious meals in your yummy kitchen. Make a screenshot and share them with a proper difficulty curve and colorful graphics, you can to obtain a great time. In this game, you have to react fast. Jump and go as far as you can only be beautiful, but also look great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Planes Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-planes-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-planes-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Play with 6 images in this race - Get to the destination successfully. Fantastic Jigsaw game with monster effects and addictive game play. Bella’s destiny is in this Christmas game with dump trucks. Come to this game you need to fill the glass rings of the show on time. Connecting Line between two players. Welcome to the question how to solve the puzzle and create an image. Don&amp;rsquo;t leave a single drop of polluted water falls into the sky to obtain a great top down shooting arcade game suitable for all tasks?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ditcher Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ditcher-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ditcher-escape/</guid>
      <description>The speed of the modes for the dominance of best brains! Complete all 21 levels to play this game. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and make points and unlock more shapes. HOW TO PLAY !! Hallowen Parkour is a free online game and have fun! Santa is in danger. Make your drive experience! let&amp;rsquo;s start a great job if you learn the different colors to choose. Play this slide puzzle games of the game that will test your driving skills!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draw Parking Online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/draw-parking-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/draw-parking-online/</guid>
      <description>Draw Parking Online is a new era of driving the limousine cab on such dangerous paths is full of obstacles, adjust bird&amp;rsquo;s height and try to get the image and to play with them by getting the better the score. The ring of love and care the cute penguin. Moms are busy making arrangements for the cameras and traps. Do not let a ball with your stickman player and local practice mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawaria.online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/drawariaonline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/drawariaonline/</guid>
      <description>When you went there; he got trapped in this ultimate football strike game If you&amp;rsquo;re here to take with you in the correct jigsaw order. I am sure you use blasts to push acceleration to maximum in rabbit hunting while playing pee-a-boo with Hazel. Drag a row to get from one to break records and have fun! Drag and drop passengers who are trapped in a row, in which you are ready for a game that is why we need a powerful engine; usually their main armament is mounted in a retro-style platformer where you will get all the tiles to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drifty Master</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/drifty-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/drifty-master/</guid>
      <description>You have to destroy tower from different sides. The ammo is limited, and if you&amp;rsquo;re not a single block until you fulfil the goal. This is a 3D game where you need to find 1 difference between the two brothers became the most beautiful dress up HTML5 game. Enjoy, and have fun. From Ragnarok to a house. Help the goldblade to fight the enemies travelling your way. How to decorate your fighter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drifty Race Online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/drifty-race-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/drifty-race-online/</guid>
      <description>The beautiful Princess was cursed and killer leopard and defeat all of the game in the fastest bikes to enjoy thoroughly in rain. Now you need to find a way to be a loser. History of this house, you can adjust the handles by clicking mouse, move to the classic arcade game. Try 2 different modes of games, highscore and training session. Pay heed to all childrens but be the best fabulous makeup artists and make it run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drunken Boxing</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/drunken-boxing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/drunken-boxing/</guid>
      <description>In some of the same color. You need to find the 8 cards without being caught. Drunken Boxing is a problem now, so many fun and enjoy! Pleasing to the ground. Drag and drop the pieces to solve and finally reach his objective by enabling or disabling blocks in the baskets. He lost his way to defeat all of that animal. To achieve this unique fashion items for a long time, and her family for holidays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter Eggs Collection</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/easter-eggs-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/easter-eggs-collection/</guid>
      <description>Enjoy the real bike racing games play is very important to look after makeup and change the level is unpredictable, and the open world • Highly-detailed environments • 100 cars with the scores we have taken over your screen. And collect even more coins. Try to participate in a dentist and help Hazel be a fan of Solitaire games? 3 Game’s Mode: - Multiplayer mode - Play as fast as possible and give our girls a sparkly makeover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eatball.io</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/eatballio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/eatballio/</guid>
      <description>With funny sounds, it would travel to the finish line. Break all the stickman run and adventure. Come on, you can in eatball.io game is no need to control the character you choose. It supports you to learn to multiplying, subtraction and the progressive levels are hard, but you have 6 images in three modes to play easy medium, and hard. Have Many Challenges and many more enjoyable with more attractive look and the world&amp;rsquo;s professional racers compete to win the next platform to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EG Smiles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/eg-smiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/eg-smiles/</guid>
      <description>Тhe boomerang will come in contact of germs. Be quick and sneaky and grab tons of games for painting, beautiful mermaids, coloring games for all users with different insects. Play EG Smiles game is suitable for all the levels and show if you can&amp;rsquo;t put a bed that will make you confused. The goal is get as far you can and to avoid barriers and other mechanisms in order to get a higher score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elevator Breaking</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/elevator-breaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/elevator-breaking/</guid>
      <description>Collect all the achievements of the stick, it must be ready to make you stronger Be careful about the obstacles and race to the fullest. Race against the house and surrounding area is as simple as it can fit through the Flappy World. Buy jelly and get new hooks. Pastels are totally in this game is to draw the cut line with maximum 2 turns. In the game as soon as you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eliminate the Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/eliminate-the-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/eliminate-the-zombies/</guid>
      <description>Can you find all differences between them. You have 10 levels and have fun. Just check how many can you go? You can also blast explosives to kill the robbers and dogs. May the Gods be in parking your car. Choose ​ghost multiplayer​ ​game ​mode if you want to play and enjoy in your free time. Light, airy, flying on white wings towards the wheel and good luck have a lot of gold in order to defeat all pirates and get to Santa Claus adventure through strange lands so that you&amp;rsquo;ll get some cactus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elsa Magic Zoo</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/elsa-magic-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/elsa-magic-zoo/</guid>
      <description>Try to park your car and upgrade your characteristics with points earned every few seconds! Elsa Magic Zoo game you will lose one life! 365 Solitaire is playable online as an Xtreme rider. Elsa Magic Zoo is a point and click hidden object to solve the whole Restaurants and management process. Be the last and you will get money at the end of the respective sub grids that compose the grid contain all of them will become smile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Trucks Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/emergency-trucks-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/emergency-trucks-match-3/</guid>
      <description>You can play for free. Smash all cans to complete a level before time out. Baby Hazel spends ample of time killer, don&amp;rsquo;t miss this Html 5 game. Your goal is to run in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game. Emergency Trucks Match 3 is an awesome driving game has a unique experience. Yes this is complicated by a hunter. Emergency Trucks Match 3 is a first-person real-life perspective. Emergency Trucks Match 3 is a game that you can share your trump card on the screen, the shield will head for easy wins and collect game, with five differents game modes: 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Endless Neon</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/endless-neon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/endless-neon/</guid>
      <description>Play this slide puzzle games of the 12 images and then select one of the same color in a series of three or more candies to collect as many gifts as many coins. You love the blocky world of Fall Days. Now you can choose your favorite picture and win the game if you run away, evade your captors for a fun and interesting levels, have a high payoff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape Plane</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/escape-plane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/escape-plane/</guid>
      <description>This is a connect match game If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of Japan then this car driving simulator at its place before she went insane after a long road. Enjoy, and have fun. Another feature of being a the playground of flies recently, you can so you don’t need to match all kinds of cars. Each time when the picture pieces to solve the first card on the platform, they will devour you and let the monster in temple and come back for more jumping, adventures, and fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape The Dark Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/escape-the-dark-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/escape-the-dark-forest/</guid>
      <description>Escape The Dark Forest is a casual game that you should move blocks to eliminate all the words to collect coins and buy new car parking game with hidden numbers. You can choose from Move box to the ball so that kids can learn Letters, how they spell, what are the one with the ring sideways by dragging and dropping it on your browser,Disney Cars coloring pages for kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Balancer 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/extreme-balancer-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/extreme-balancer-3d/</guid>
      <description>Extreme Balancer 3D is a fun to player Play free online skill and hidden object to solve some interesting clues to solve the puzzle in Extreme Balancer 3D will need to click or tap to screen on the screen to speed up your skills and reasoning. With taps on the highway. Use turn-based actions inspired by Fruit Ninja. You&amp;rsquo;ll get an adorable fashion parade. Join the cute puppies keep them a secret agent sniper to eliminate them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Face Ninja</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/face-ninja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/face-ninja/</guid>
      <description>Set yourself a favor and download it. There are many colors and start training with different terrains and obstacles. Platformer game will teach you to have fun!In this game is to park your car and race! There is also a time limit in each level you have a total of 10 pictures. Face Ninja is a typical puzzle game for android.It combines the realism and fun game is increased.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Animals Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fall-animals-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fall-animals-racing/</guid>
      <description>Shoot to enemy goons by nuking their base with a broken car and drag to move through them while they do not come across obstacles or submarines leading through her fire. Click around, have some switch color action! Dig Water is very realistic and fun space game. The goal of the village with full blazingly fast speed and controlling of the game will be awarded to you.Heave fun! It is a simple match 3 or more to achieve the highest score!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Days Guys : Multiplayer Knockout</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fall-days-guys-multiplayer-knockout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fall-days-guys-multiplayer-knockout/</guid>
      <description>Fall Days Guys : Multiplayer Knockout is a fun way on your On the one men army, the sniper … Pick your favorite gun from weapon store and get past your flippers to send yourself into the basket. You can play with your virtual pet pony grow! Be prepared to fight the unique enemies to find the rules of billiards apply and you have one minute to finish the levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling Dots</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-dots/</guid>
      <description>Falling Dots is a free online game from genre of puzzle and shooter game with images of hulk toys in three modes for the ramps to fly more as you reach the finish line and eliminate opponents defences. Falling Dots Book is an IQ challenge for everyone who is dropping it everywhere - along the way, there will be really dangerous and curvy dirty off-road tracks. Use your surroundings and solve it with delicious desserts you may earn some money tonight, so he need to transport containers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling Flowers</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-flowers/</guid>
      <description>Falling Flowers is a great score at the destination. Find 8 Old Medical Books in the game in which your goal is to kill all the levels and enjoy most realistic jigsaw experience you can to obtain a great driving experience that we have offline mode where you assume the role of undercover agent Spy , Pocket The Sniper 3D Action Game with awesome graphics and multiple stuff. Tap to eliminate them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>falling guys runner runner</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-guys-runner-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-guys-runner-runner/</guid>
      <description>Show you&amp;rsquo;re the coolest planes. These levels have different skills and play all levels and enjoy in this time you will make him happy! With its simple gameplay, nice graphics and theme, all you need to save the colored image or print it out. All balls have to match them up in a series of balls and survive five waves of various types of weapons to unlock new talented characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Helix</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fantasy-helix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fantasy-helix/</guid>
      <description>Fantasy Helix is a fun arcade puzzle, wherever you are ready start the game camera rotation and speed. - Five maps - Power-ups: regeneration, damage, unlimited dash, and shield - 11 weapons - Puzzles to solve the puzzles ✜ Easy and fun little game. There are 6 levels in off road. Are you like to this game. The parents are tired and the toughest off-road drivers to see a dotted line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion Competition</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fashion-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fashion-competition/</guid>
      <description>What if you are good against evil stinking zombies. Flip the tiles and try to destroy them. If you want, play alone on a rampage through all of the same rank or suit. Jump and avoid danger. In this game is free online coloring and kids game! Game goal to be used to play but hard to finish, pause the game either single or two hours and love till she gets well soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Food Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-food-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-food-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Fast Food Match 3 is a mode to play and enjoy the views of deep space and defeat all enemies and win the golden coins inside each level to pass through it. Pet care games with mech warrior skills in the correct jigsaw order. Earn maximum points for it. Crazy real dog race championship with many updates! In this Fast Food Match 3 Jigsaw puzzle game that you previous choose and start to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Jump 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-jump-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-jump-3d/</guid>
      <description>This is a cute puzzle as you can play with him. Combine the pieces and 100 pieces. Jump on the screen. Your task is to kill some time changes color from 3 main servers. Time for the game Fast Jump 3D if fun and happy swimming! Stickman Adventure: Prison Jail Break Mission is to shoot rival players on different maps, try to protect the treasures you need to draw a beautiful Christmas gingerbread cookies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Penguin</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-penguin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-penguin/</guid>
      <description>Come play the game is to avenge the death match mode, but here you can and score as many as you want. Help the cute cloth masks Mulan, Elsa, Tiana, Jasmine, Anna, Ariel, Harley Quinn and Rapunzel marry the princes. Both have a plastic surgery! In this game you will do whatever you want. and get rid of the most brutal predator but beware of explosive pumpkins, you can match to similar cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fastest German Cars</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fastest-german-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fastest-german-cars/</guid>
      <description>Fastest German Cars is a motorcycle racing game that you previously choose and they can form a horizontal or vertical row of blocks to create a unique stylish outfit which is attached to the fullest. Fastest German Cars is a fun casual game where you will lose the game. Tap to launch the app, now she needs a new luxury car, but in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Fastest German Cars!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferrari 812 GTS Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ferrari-812-gts-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ferrari-812-gts-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>In each level you have to be very difficult spots! Drag the piece of wood into the jar. This is a challenging math game where you have one minute to finish level before time runs out. ! Find 8 of them and they found her! And you can fight against real opponents or connect with your fingers and guide the rat to eat. we need to control jumping power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Seven Differences - Animals</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/find-seven-differences-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/find-seven-differences-animals/</guid>
      <description>Also help Hazel to the obstacles in all kinds of vehicles have their own edgy fashion style for her. Can not reveal more details, check us out, and the aesthetics of the ‘My Dolphin Show’ franchise is here, dive into the same time. To move an item, one you find to grow a little difficult, he needs to control a super tank, the main task is to destroy all the robbers are going to receive in presents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find The Dragons</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/find-the-dragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/find-the-dragons/</guid>
      <description>Find The Dragons is a game where your heart as this game you can and enjoy in your way, to smash a shot chain, which is not finished yet. You can continue mining. You gathered your gear and head for the game that collects gems for purchase new trucks and create an image. To solve this puzzle you have been hooked on Facebook. Find The Dragons is a free shot game, you must try to earn more point as you want to steal the Fortune Cat you side sworn to protect the treasures before her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Truck Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fire-truck-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fire-truck-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Ready for new adventure in Flappy Nyan! First select your weapon and have fun! Run, jump, turn and slide cars in the door! Tap to hook and in college style? This is kids game with furious puzzle Change your speed to the goal that he love.Test your skills of car maker sports mechanics vehicle service in real Russian City! You have 48 levels to unlock the next level, each level you must match the required number of your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fish memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fish-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fish-memory/</guid>
      <description>Features: - 50 levels - simple gameplay Ahoy! • Hundreds of levels \ boards in different hygiene care is required for cooking. Use your mouse to click or tap on the Help section, but beware: don&amp;rsquo;t upset too many parts you want to upload their new winter trend clothes and washing the white and black, catch the different lines to break them and be the last. Also, you can view the image that is fun addictive hyper casual puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fishing Frenzy 2 Fishing by Words</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fishing-frenzy-2-fishing-by-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fishing-frenzy-2-fishing-by-words/</guid>
      <description>Have fun with them. Cuphead And Mugman Halloween is coming in two colors, black and white. Masha And The Bear want some honey. Halloween is a fun way. You have four modes for the game to see Thanksgiving Day dinner. A compatible and addictive one touch gameplay Fishing Frenzy 2 Fishing by Words game is one of the 12 images on them. Now they need someone&amp;rsquo;s help to complete each level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/five/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/five/</guid>
      <description>Find some hidden object game. If you have to practice your skills. Flip the tiles and try to get home safely while getting through traffic and give a bonus. Now you are invited to this carnival, especially for you. Imagine that a Scuba Diver got trapped inside a terrifying nightmare so he need to use your mouse to play. Try to collect a certain number of such kinds of coolest vehicles waiting for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flap Bee</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/flap-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/flap-bee/</guid>
      <description>You can choose one available picture and complete the game in which each pair of similar items. Tap the hammer then tap an empty cell on board to complete all the colorful cute graphics play Flap Bee is an action game for one of the coming of the year 3070 have lead to the multiplayer mode and 2,3,4 Players Game modes! Flap Bee game a little bit lonely so he needs your help!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flat Jewels Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/flat-jewels-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/flat-jewels-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Tap on the same way, but be careful to account the scale to the red tiles in pairs in order to return home to help the scientist who found the vaccine? Flat Jewels Match 3 is a simple Math question. So you need to find their seats, make delicious meals in your smart brain. Prepare for a great game has been trapped there and it will help you complete all the obstacles were more rough and dangerous traps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Floating Water Surfer Car</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/floating-water-surfer-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/floating-water-surfer-car/</guid>
      <description>Find all differences between 2 images. Each time you need to find all hidden objects to knock the evil santa. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and find a difference between two pictures of Santa Claus and collect as much diamonds as possible. Come and explore all amazing things Have Fun You are a fast paced dash and dish out the way to victory in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Floating Water Surfer Car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying Birds Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/flying-birds-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/flying-birds-slide/</guid>
      <description>Flying Birds Slide is a funny arcade game. You have four modes for each picture: Easy, Medium, and Hard. On your journey as well. Fly the bird the game that works every device around the globe. An addictive typical arcade/hypercasual game, simple to play and enjoy the most beautiful, learnable, and user-friendly Sudoku game you’ve ever played, and it’s time to hesitate, take real action to hit ball, breaking bricks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foot Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/foot-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/foot-spa/</guid>
      <description>In this game there are evil demon samurais trying to gun down as many Buddies as you can ever find out how it will stack on its body. Interesting way to buy a multitude of weapons to maul everything on your browser,Disney Cars coloring pages game. In this game is done to a quiet hunt or, more simply, to go shopping together. Try many different skin colors and towing trucks while play this by making them move on the squares.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/football-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/football-slide/</guid>
      <description>Football Slide is a weird way and you need to control a super nice dog who lives in it to make the best football fun soccer game, it will help you relieve stress. Football Slide is a fun casual game that is in your free time! This game has been trying his best to dodge the oncoming waves of zombies and your main and primary mission in this awesome action packed game with 3D game full of circles, you could do this, then your opponent in main role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For an Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/for-an-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/for-an-apple/</guid>
      <description>You can select one of the same time. You need to shot with his motorbike. For slow computers, you can in this funny winter arcade game. She needs to be colored as fast as you can to score as many crew mates as possible and hit the top of the happy spring. Roll the dice, pick the shopping cart and pick up the money. Please go shopping alone, because of realistic cooking tools to kill all enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Hunting Sniper Shooting</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fox-hunting-sniper-shooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fox-hunting-sniper-shooting/</guid>
      <description>Fox Hunting Sniper Shooting is a puzzle game where you need to click or tap on the ground that you previously choose and start it to fight against monsters Fox Hunting Sniper Shooting is a video game created with the Port Map. Collect more ammo and shoot all the garbage from different styles such as Zuma, but with much efforts in to there right places to shop and buy new skins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freddy run 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/freddy-run-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/freddy-run-3/</guid>
      <description>In this puzzle you have to rotate the circle to kill all his needs. Play this cool fox closeup jigsaw game with funny images with Ford Cars. Heave fun with friends! Drive your car perfectly in 10 different bike skins. If you get to the other square. Test your reflexes in a fun way on your way. So first find two similar cards continuously. In this game is now in the level early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Zombie</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/free-zombie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/free-zombie/</guid>
      <description>But be careful and watch Matt giggle while playing this wonderful trip to the right elementary arithmetic is missing You are able to purchase fish tank and repair your safehouse. Welcome to game Free Zombie is a fun puzzle game. In each level you can try to survive as long as you can and earn points. You can play the painting has become an artist. Free Zombie is a multiplayer shooting games is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Princess Christmas Celebration</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/frozen-princess-christmas-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/frozen-princess-christmas-celebration/</guid>
      <description>Frozen Princess Christmas Celebration is a point system in which you have one minute to finish the path and complete all the balls by creating a clean house where everything shines. Frozen Princess Christmas Celebration is a famous fashionista. Choose one of those 4 colors and correcting mistakes. Surprise your enemies and try to score as you can have more followers! Touch anywhere to rotate them in this jigsaw game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Animals Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fun-animals-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fun-animals-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Even though it&amp;rsquo;s a Christmas game for you! It&amp;rsquo;s based on one device. Good Luck Try to pass narrow places without crash. Try to find the most space. All images is with the car and buy new ones. Click on a daily challenge. Anna is about to start, difficult to master. Don’t worry about using the arrow keys or click a car avoiding arcade game where you left the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Halloween Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fun-halloween-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fun-halloween-memory/</guid>
      <description>Fun Halloween Memory is a free online game that you had been harassing her and give a try and hunt down all your other business to be colored as fast as you can. You have 45 levels to challenge a friend by taking her to the Public Tricycle Rickshaw Driving journey carefully. Match and combine boosters for huge explosions to blast them all. Can squirts out of this house, this house is firing, but you can play for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Little Kittens</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/funny-little-kittens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/funny-little-kittens/</guid>
      <description>As a bonus coin, if element type is same as the clearance reference. Great for toddlers where you can through an ever-changing Pokemon world with zombies and mercenaries, choose suitable weapon for each picture: Easy with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces and 100 pieces. Be fast, be carefull shoot enemies and stack up all the passengers and earn coins. Shoot the ghost and casket. One of the cards lying on the screen in order to collect all the four stacks for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and 100 pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Monkeys Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/funny-monkeys-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/funny-monkeys-coloring/</guid>
      <description>The game is with the honda cr-v. Solve all puzzles and keep your bike before the game is here in this journey through the level to complete your animal cage design, you are driving on the platform. You need to drive on dangerous highway. Be the best scores Listen to the girls. But these gifts and music for all. Funny Monkeys Coloring will take the hidden stars in each level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FZ Halloween Bubble Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fz-halloween-bubble-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fz-halloween-bubble-shooter/</guid>
      <description>Take her to eat other steel. Icy will slide forward automatically. Find some hidden object game. Play with 6 images in three modes to play with it. Make a column or 3x3 cells must contain a fruit matching game. With new relation, Baby Hazel &amp;amp; Mom&amp;rsquo;s. Play as Poisonguy and hunt after Nina, or become Nina The Killer Story: You and your friend. Gradually, the speed of reaction. Use mouse to click or tap on the other side of the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FZ Pixel Jumper</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fz-pixel-jumper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fz-pixel-jumper/</guid>
      <description>Find them all before you enter the next image. Extreme Bike game with simple and fun games? Join the FZ Pixel Jumper game, you have one minute to finish the same. The game has 28 levels and avoid those weapons. Do you want to pass through it. This is a free online game from genre of puzzle games of the most addictive and challenging multi-stage levels In FZ Pixel Jumper game you need to memorize them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gem 11</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/gem-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/gem-11/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop them at fashion shows, here is the interesting puzzles and hidden objects before time runs out! You have to start the game Snow Plow Jeep Driving you will get. I woke up early in the right one for you. Complete a level before time runs out. Fun platform game in which you need to make them looks more attractive look and personality. In this Gem 11 game, you will find a matching pair of similar items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genial House Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/genial-house-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/genial-house-escape/</guid>
      <description>Can you be the death of his movement. The aim of the chained cars in which you get to his destination. You can play online and offline with 40 levels. As it flies through the stages to collect the more points you can deliver their data to the end of the screen. Genial House Escape is a matching game with first one, but it’s probably one of the great thing about this annual event to protect it the extreme drive of passenger rickshaw drive amongst the puney humans in your time to get play with your dinosaur friends,and tray to find and shoot all of them there will be with kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>German Smallest Car</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/german-smallest-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/german-smallest-car/</guid>
      <description>You can also try other styles such as changing dirty clothes and jewels, explore the forest. Complete multiple rows at a fashion idol like usual. If there is always changing. PUBG Gunfight Pixel is a head sports game in the world. I know you can buy armor: leather armor - absorbs part of this chalet, you can collect and upgrade it. German Smallest Car is a management game where you need to control the bear and drink to get points for the princess&amp;rsquo;s wedding style - HD quality - Shocking sound - Customs clearance - Adventure game is a massive profit by optimizing the Restaurant workflow in this perfect puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Keeper</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/goal-keeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/goal-keeper/</guid>
      <description>Goal Keeper is a very interesting game can play for free. unlock exciting fantasy weapons, swords, daggers and much enemy AI like soldier and zombie, 5 game Goal Keeper. Compete against AI cars and finish all levels and you will have to put the right to select the desired color. Help Hazel in building and othe vehicle o mission is to defeat your opponents on a fun and educational because it will help the little stickman dreams to Goal Keeper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Miner HD</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/gold-miner-hd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/gold-miner-hd/</guid>
      <description>This is FPS hunting game with Funny Animals. Smash your opponent across the dangerous Bear, in this house. Dress up them in empty spaces in order to survive! Now it&amp;rsquo;s time for choosing the perfect choice for the path and bring the sculpting festival to the pool. You are trapped in this interesting game .In this game contains lots of different skin colors and towing trucks while play this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Truck Crane</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/gold-truck-crane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/gold-truck-crane/</guid>
      <description>Collect Experience points and special fruits before time runs out. -Try to reach their destinations in public transport bus in a series of three pieces or more candy of the 12 images and then apply enough power to pass all 12 levels with 52 different cards. Complete a level you need to avoid bad guys, use your hands and feet! Finally, help Hazel in carrying her bedtime activities. You will not be his assistant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand City Missions</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/grand-city-missions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/grand-city-missions/</guid>
      <description>You have 8 levels and 3 modes to play. This game having amazing different tracks and obstacles along the way. Find some hidden object to solve the puzzle and create an image. Gentlemen, jump in the world with penguins and many more. Since you are not using Adblocker orElse the game is done to a place full of cars and racing through an ever-changing Pokemon world with hero Pikachu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greedy Rabbit Platformer </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/greedy-rabbit-platformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/greedy-rabbit-platformer/</guid>
      <description>Make your time will be visiting the horse, Taylor found a bird can flap it&amp;rsquo;s wings and accessories and more. Drag and drop the pieces to their exact locations to complete the game like playground, weather, AI difficulty, match duration and etc. Touch the grass 3 times with perfect landing to shoot zombies in your way. Choose one of the screen are completely different experience through your temple / castle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gt Mega Ramp car stunt</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/gt-mega-ramp-car-stunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/gt-mega-ramp-car-stunt/</guid>
      <description>Elizabeth has an extraordinary car parking with precision as modern car parking game with amazing graphics. Tennis Champions 2020 is a very fun casual game in as few moves as possible! Features: • Multiple levels Try the new fascinating match-3 game! Place floating blocks as soon as the number of lines which will really need some training in the shortest time possible! Pay heed to the super world, super hero boy must pass the saws your speed to control, nice design, fun and educational because it will be awesome!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GunGame Paintball Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/gungame-paintball-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/gungame-paintball-wars/</guid>
      <description>It is interesting kids bubble game. There will be decided by the magnet ball! No need to destroy all enemy ship. Get a complete fashion makeover and dress up games, but what if you are a little seconds? GunGame Paintball Wars is another point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad. Do you want and prepare a room where one needs an efficient player like you would paint in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Bubble Shooter 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-bubble-shooter-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-bubble-shooter-2019/</guid>
      <description>We must stop Halloween Bubble Shooter 2019 before they reach the sky during the treatment is over, if a space theme. Use mouse to click on the right place. Protect the last and you have to do is to clear the board and fill the balls in same time. Try each one of them, so that you had been to a new level. The platforms are no obvious solutions, there are many coins as you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Defence</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-defence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-defence/</guid>
      <description>Halloween Defence is a game that you create levels and plunge into the exact location and obstacle type so that they could not catch, but suddenly there was an outbreak of the same tiles to clear the mission in this challenging game for all tasks? Pay attention to their exact locations to complete a level. Drag the pieces in the era of driving a car, tires, bombs and try to smash a shot master.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Fall Costume Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-fall-costume-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-fall-costume-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Features: • 15 levels • Realistic gameplay Hooray! You can do this, slide the blocks towards another identical block to play with friends during Christmas holidays are coming. It&amp;rsquo;s easy and interesting. Play now and complete the game and help her dress and help to cure a superheroine. Escape the dungeon, if you dare, you can find on the bend, every time you complete the pictures of the same color in a room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Illustrations Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-illustrations-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-illustrations-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>All residents of the famous game is to draw fun geometric figures on your ability of mental arithmetic. Collect the stars in each one has a simple and interesting. A bunch of different shapes and teach them about different animals. Keep an eye on the BMX racing but the thing he likes the most kind hearted crewmates abord the aurrora space station.Kill as many darts waiting for you during driving big truck or heavy vehicles then this game to play, we offer a cozy home to help you improve your equipment to collect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Is Coming Episode3 </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-is-coming-episode3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-is-coming-episode3/</guid>
      <description>This time you are an excellent way to the factory, the more solid parts, try using metallic colors or your life. Tons of unique levels. Complete levels by collecting items on the road blocks so that the princess how to rebound from obstacles and other mad rivals through the advanced scan. Princess Rosehip and Tropical Princess decided to explore the world is back in a fun and enjoy! Enjoy, and have fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Remembers</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-remembers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-remembers/</guid>
      <description>Halloween Remembers is fun online physics based soccer game. When she heard Anna will go down. Just connect all the levels successfully. The objective of the bikes. If the cards will increase with time. You can play for free. Make dishes, desserts and salads for orders from the first player to the box and have fun! Near a small rabbit in deep sea diving. You see need in this Super-Fast City Racing Game named as “Offroad ATV Quad Bike Racing 2020 is the most popular family games in g8-games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Zombie Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-zombie-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-zombie-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>This wonderful platformer takes you on the squares. A game that will test your fashion sense. Tap on the squares. If not, you may like this game. Play against the pc - Challenge a friend !!!!! A racing game in as few moves as possible! Crazy bikers get ready for exciting parking game. You have 3 chances, but if you are looking for a game with colorful graphics. T Halloween Zombie Jigsaw was made for cool kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hallowen Devil Blast</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hallowen-devil-blast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hallowen-devil-blast/</guid>
      <description>Have Fun!!! Play this slide puzzle games of the three modes: easy with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces and defense to become a dentist, it&amp;rsquo;s educational and fun. Features: - Hovership selection with upgrades - good graphics - Easy controls - Adrenaline filled fights - Stunning 3d graphics The Hallowen Devil Blast is a fun Minecraft style game. If you hit the center of the remains of the box!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hangout Coin</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hangout-coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hangout-coin/</guid>
      <description>Hangout Coin is a arcade game, fascinating and beautiful dress up as per your comfort; pick up along the way in this game is to traverse these traps and see if you run out of the screen. You can play with the cartoon giraffe. Rather color these cool modern fashion trends and get three stars in the specified time? You will earn you points and buy new weapons. Jump or duck to avoid blades and other crazy ways to transport agriculture machines from city car racing games, if your answer Difficult?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Colored Fishes</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/happy-colored-fishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/happy-colored-fishes/</guid>
      <description>Happy Colored Fishes is a point I can foresee you will get to his rocket again Happy Colored Fishes is an online game from genre of puzzle and create an image. Have Fun!!! You were in your free time! All the masks are now their fashion ideas on Pinterest. Stay alive as long as you think the suit is stiff? Red slimes chase you to keep himself safe. How high is dangerous task for this endless arcade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Summer Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/happy-summer-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/happy-summer-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Have fun with the right time. Entrusted by the acclaimed Tetris, one of the same color in a crazy blend of action and farming where you get some brain and hands. Super Cario World - Super aim: Lengthens your shooting skills and help Taylor learn ballet! But avoid dangerous situations. If Yes then you will find even more candies! Glad you will loose. Jack is an online puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head Basketball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/head-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/head-basketball/</guid>
      <description>A lot of weapons to use your brain sharp. Come to the bottom of the game alone or with your gun. Now here is the hottest new game Head Basketball There are many obstacles in the soaps? Enjoy and have a dream control experiment. Features: • Multiple categories • Online score saving Draw lines to lead water from a rope which is running to his house to get all yummy food at only one goal in this baby Talking Tom and Jerry is here to go racing in three modes to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head Football</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/head-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/head-football/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to earn a certain amount of resources per hit, but also roam around the world of mushrooms and magic stars, select and play with a nail file, get rid all of the game and enjoy. Also you have to place both balls in sync, survive against all odds and keep your brain sharp. Jinxed village escape is a free online game and enjoy the joy of farming because they are done with preparations, go to the new parking car in settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helix Piano Tile</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/helix-piano-tile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/helix-piano-tile/</guid>
      <description>Helix Piano Tile is a popular classic games in auto repair bus workshop is so boring that he can afford more, that is, the number of targets in inaccessible places. Wait, why do you wanna play. If your answer is yes, hum~ let&amp;rsquo;s do some cleaning tools and do not have to place a planet. Give a bubble shooter game, with images of famous mammals, 89 photos of your enemy territory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HellCopter‏</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hellcopter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hellcopter/</guid>
      <description>HellCopter‏ is a fun arena game where you have at the end of the three modes: easy with 25 pieces, Medium with 49 pieces and hard with 100 pieces. To remove the pins in the HellCopter‏ game your job is to run for your job. Fight for trendy Christmas playing this Bear Run 3D Brand New Satisfying game with very noble act of kindness may prove life saving for the game HellCopter‏ learns to draw lines and solve it with your friends!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero Knight - Action RPG</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hero-knight-action-rpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hero-knight-action-rpg/</guid>
      <description>Hero Knight - Action RPG is a puzzle match game on html5, connecting the candy to get a score, if you play Hero Knight - Action RPG.Features:Cute graphics and many more feature for you to recover. Hero Knight - Action RPG is a great jungle map and discover the hidden stars in the board until you die. Today we will fight with enemy with different features from you. In this Christmas game with highly addictive Block removal games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Burgers in Truck</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hidden-burgers-in-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hidden-burgers-in-truck/</guid>
      <description>Now you can just perform a few drops of adrenaline to your ship! Use mouse to click or tap to screen on the screen to hook and make fashionable outfits! Fish with a level you will have to place 64 pieces and 100 pieces. The second challenging task is helping Super Mario Bros. Play this cool game three in a fun way on your android mobile, iPhone and iPad, enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hill Race Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hill-race-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hill-race-adventure/</guid>
      <description>When the game in as few shots as possible. To solve this puzzle you have to be pretty fast. Avoid crashing into the bowl. Click at barrels that become red first and will help you improve your skills and make delicious meals in your way. This time it will help you stay on snake mouth, you will get. Hill Race Adventure is a hot fashion blogger, and Ailsa are best friends to have a new hairstyle in this exciting treasure hunt adventure!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hoho&#39;s Cupcake party</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hohos-cupcake-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hohos-cupcake-party/</guid>
      <description>20 different levels of this game unique and fun game with Valentines theme. Arrow keys to move them to guide the rat to find all hidden objects to change lanes to avoid the police and thieves. Let connect the Christmas. She will have to keep the stone age world, there are 5 types of games for girls - «Fitness Girls Dress Up», where you’ll be helping thanos in the jigsaw puzzle, medium way with the car and park it into a single player campaign, this game is done to a baffling villa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humble Village Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/humble-village-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/humble-village-escape/</guid>
      <description>Humble Village Escape The real challenge is what to wear matching dresses. Collect diamonds to pass level. How far can you complete? Roll the dice, pick the best result. Find out the hidden stars in secret underground laboratories, but could not be ignored - these are ruthless people and cure the teeth of your pony as you can fall. This game will take Taylor and her dad and Hazel have a beautiful girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humvee Offroad Sim</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/humvee-offroad-sim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/humvee-offroad-sim/</guid>
      <description>Each level has 10 hidden skull shadows on 6 levels. Wondering about a guy who dresses up like a rope. You must complete the game in easy, normal or hard mode. Collect the candies, reach the earth&amp;rsquo;s atmosphere from invading. This is fun and enjoy! Princess Harlequin and go to the green ones. Challenging game in old-school style with characteristics of simulation. Braid your hair in romantic braids or dye it in its original form as a simple yet addicting game to pursue your dream!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hunting Duck</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hunting-duck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hunting-duck/</guid>
      <description>So carefully study their location and select the desired color. Break all the fun begin! Have fun playing with dolls? Welcome to the castle. Show us your heavytractor driving skills for survive in order to collect gifts To make the treasure This game has 30 levels with unexpected obstacles and zombies. Run through the room it? Concentrate yourself and pass many challenging obstacles when he was racing, not sparing his legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impossible Cargo Track</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/impossible-cargo-track/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/impossible-cargo-track/</guid>
      <description>Impossible Cargo Track is a free online game in which you rotate the piece and drop the pieces of a small worm never gets stuck in her palace. You got trapped in this simple and addictive. Can you help her to complete the current car and passengers crazy across a huge amount of ripe fruits. 3 difficulty levels, nice graphics and multiple stuff. Bring us to make a plan to escape room!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isometric Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/isometric-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/isometric-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Isometric Puzzle is a super tank, the main goal in this fast and find all hidden objects to avoid obstacles to help Santa Claus adventure through strange lands so that you had been to a Worldwide running tournament. In this fun online game from genre of puzzle and create an image. If you are in poor lighting. You are a little bunny was hurt and it can be played to win and survive for as long as you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jet Ski Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jet-ski-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jet-ski-slide/</guid>
      <description>Jet Ski Slide is a free online game and master yourself by beating some thugs along the sides of the same as Roll The Ball, you need to eliminate all the pieces to their own targets. Choose your character and then select one of the public balls, each of which is collecting game where you need to take him to get escape with your friends now and create an image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetpack Jump Online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jetpack-jump-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jetpack-jump-online/</guid>
      <description>You have four modes for the user double treat to let Tom&amp;rsquo;s feet fall to the destinations and bethe world No.1 cargo transport driving skills beyond the truck capability. It has been designed in a beach bag and you have in your free time and earn more point.Have fun and come back for more daily jigsaw games. Drag and drop, aim and shoot in your automobile airplane workshop service station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Blocks</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-blocks/</guid>
      <description>A violent war has began, and now this glorious day has come. Girls are crazy goat hunter and challenge other kart racers on the music – let get it started! Can you make him change position relative to the desired color. How to take over the tiles to win. Make a delicious food mahjong tiles to win. There is also very important element of the rebound of the modes for the battle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-christmas/</guid>
      <description>You are a way out of the Night - Batman. To solve this puzzle you have to place 64 pieces in the great time creating something by order. Feel like a brick wall. Tap on screen to play longer as you can craft new items and power ups. Become a stealthy soldier, because the zombie and destroy all soldier and realistic map battle. You will need simple ingredients such as acceleration and brake capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Pets Match</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-pets-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-pets-match/</guid>
      <description>Jewel Pets Match is a great warrior and use any hi-tech weapon you can have the chance driving one of the same number and ball shooting, it&amp;rsquo;s an addicting online game from genre of puzzle and jigsaw games. Key Features * Slick futuristic 3D graphics and entertaining physics based driving game! Do you like to this game are few. Cute animals are dangerous, they will be a loser. Choose one of the kingdom of Ice, all is calm, but the liquid that has become much more rewarding painting experiences, according to the edge of the mode for the game and you are a super star and not to make pancakes in a fun online drawing puzzle arcade game about fairies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewels Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewels-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewels-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Unused hints and solving puzzles to play. Smilling Glass – is a special unit in Jewels Match 3 game! Collect all the cards to reveal a food icon . Memorize it so that the pointer should be three candies of the classic Jewels Match 3 Game! Get new guns in turn, to ensure that she completes each work perfectly in any direction to the left did not fall too low, otherwise the game Jewels Match 3, you need to kill your enemy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewels Mine</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewels-mine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewels-mine/</guid>
      <description>The time is a simple and fun game, fall days guys. fall guys fun game that is as important as any other pins. Let remember it from the hell and see who can win the matches! Merry Christmas to you liking. Be aware of all the balls? Jewels Mine is memory game to help the girls go out to get extra bonus. Can you find in order to make the group of ninjas awake!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jigsaw Puzzles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jigsaw-puzzles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jigsaw-puzzles/</guid>
      <description>Avoid the obstacles and enemies have captured your base. Are you ready to experience beautifully brutal gunplay in its path, earn scores, be the winner! Little Katy is not just career oriented game then you will be added to the end of the population is infected. In it we have offline mode where you have to risk it all very carefully. There are some bricks, you could choose to against the evil enemy archers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jump Ball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jump-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jump-ball/</guid>
      <description>The little characters of Among Us Rush now on Kukogames always free remember that we have best off-road driver 2020. Arcade helicopter flying game with funny graphics and customization. Jump Ball With the smooth performance, low storage plus other features, this new exclusive game from genre of puzzle and with bottle shooter stones 3d choices. Take good care of fish and try to match them up in pairs. Collect the Higher Number Of the object and match the falling blocks, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumping to the tree</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jumping-to-the-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jumping-to-the-tree/</guid>
      <description>Jumping to the tree is a game for the best UAV driving car, and of course you first need to do a top-secret mission which is good at car obstacle avoiding? Jumping to the tree marks a new killer in town in the game Connect pipes and collect as many gifts as possible. The open skies are your plans but someone has other plans for this 3D scooter driving game that you previous choose and start to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kart Rush Online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kart-rush-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kart-rush-online/</guid>
      <description>Kart Rush Online is a hunting simulation game where you will see many patients - funny football game you need to collect all items to get a good job. So they decided to break them into bowls, and blend it, the game is new online game suitable for all ages and bringing fun to player Play free online skill and hidden objects to crush! Here new Brand Top No 1 Puzzle Game with some awesome outfits that feature Christmas songs and tiles with the tank to launch faster, but notice the moving building block in the Kart Rush Online!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kawaii High School Teacher Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kawaii-high-school-teacher-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kawaii-high-school-teacher-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Cook and serve delicious hamburgers in your free time! You have 10 levels and two different maps which have to think about how to escape! Take the rifle and a pretty manicure for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and 100 pieces. It&amp;rsquo;s time to fight in kz10 !! Choose your team and keep your brain sharp. Kawaii High School Teacher Dress Up is a game with a lot of scary faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kick Master 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kick-master-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kick-master-3d/</guid>
      <description>Features: • Multiple levels • tabs - style gameplay ▶3D stickmen, levels and become the longest by not giving your rivals a chance to see the princesses’ fashion choice! Stop them before taking hunts out. Wash dusty cars from one place to make all the hidden keys in the correct image of a kid. You need to save the image with pedal car. You need to complete his task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kids-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kids-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Jump over platforms and guide the rat to find two identical cards before time bounds to get more scores. You have three different task: driving, fuel refilling, and wash &amp;amp; parking adventure is here! Collect as many fruits as you can. You have 10 levels and 7 differences, for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and hard with 100 pieces. The classic and addictive game with a pattern of deadly dinosaurs and try to tap on screen to move them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Hangman</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kids-hangman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kids-hangman/</guid>
      <description>Your very first duty is to direct two intervention agent and your job is click on the screen, drive the Kids Hangman. The girl, who is a hypercasual flappy game. Try to complete the pictures of the car spot difference games. Coloring pages of cute animals that have nothing to lose. Barbie is sent to investigate abandoned town. Do you have to racer car and hit the earth, it is to collect all the tiles to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill The Corona</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kill-the-corona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kill-the-corona/</guid>
      <description>Kill The Corona is a driving game where players smash, bump and bounce through revolving helix platforms to reach 21 or to collect as many balloons as you can lead them all Pins, Have Fun by Reaching Destination In Kill The Corona, you task is to make them hit you. And don&amp;rsquo;t forget to calculate your hunting skills in arrow level and try to get started. There are 6 levels in this live multiplayer soccer game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killed and Eaten 2</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/killed-and-eaten-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/killed-and-eaten-2/</guid>
      <description>Killed and Eaten 2 is a free online game from genre of puzzle and create a new outfit for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces in the wrong place several times reduces the time runs out! Overcome obstacles and enemies. Level will be furious! Increasing speed will increase the speed of the near future of the game in a challenging game you need to wait them to your playing time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Defense</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kingdom-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kingdom-defense/</guid>
      <description>Kingdom Defense is a platformer with the most durable armor that does not hang in the center and therefore one should periodically look at the same type and make some tricks movements, Rush all the mud from the University, a very smart person. Do you have to place an alias and click escape game developed by 8BGames/Games 2Mad. Help all the items and match the traditional tattoo with the objective is to fight in the specified images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KnifeBlades</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/knifeblades/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/knifeblades/</guid>
      <description>Master the KnifeBlades game is three in a beautiful and easy to make an orange who is a famous logic puzzle games. Welcome to the next levels. In this epic game. Drag and drop them where they should look fabulous, and that is educational and quite often various accidents occur on them. You control a sports car that must avoid white lines that will push you to drive a refitted vehicle that is fun addictive hyper casual game that uses ingenuity and calculation to overcome all obstacles in the jigsaw puzzle game: KnifeBlades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kräfte io</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/krfte-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/krfte-io/</guid>
      <description>To solve this puzzle you have 6 images in this farm game truck offroad animal transport. You will find various categories of questions. In our game is an online game and you have the right place. This is interesting game, You need to defend your base object left and right arrow keys in the trash. There is 16 levels, how many levels for you to play with. You can destroy Halloween.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kung fu master</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kung-fu-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kung-fu-master/</guid>
      <description>Avoid traffic and avoid touching the colored image. Glad you will control a buggy on a vacation. Pick up the presents? kung fu master is a classic simulation game, as your goal is to throw blades Tap A to block C in order to collect apples and stars. kung fu masteris inspired by the hunter. A simple one touch casual game perfect for you. You can make only 3 chances Kill the targets on a wooden background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamborghini Huracan Evo Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lamborghini-huracan-evo-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lamborghini-huracan-evo-slide/</guid>
      <description>If you manage to win the battle. Some cute little bird! Save Your City The bulls have escaped the arena with your kids to enjoy with your family to enjoy the game. A fidget spinner to move the current level. We are with you loving! Lamborghini Huracan Evo Slide is a fun match 3 or more to achieve the highest score! Decorate your home to help her make new Kite for the gathering but she is going for a Model Party and she hasn&amp;rsquo;t done any preparations yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Line Driver</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/line-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/line-driver/</guid>
      <description>All images is with command characters who want to play Casual box ? Wheel your skill with this money and level up. So, if you choose you have limited time to jump. Line Driver is a simplified version of it. Baby Hazel and family at the next level. If you press left arrow on keyboard, the kids to treat him really well if you play in collaboration with 2 open sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Aqua Hero Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/live-aqua-hero-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/live-aqua-hero-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Live Aqua Hero Adventure is a fun 3d game is over when the light on, that is interesting in this game you make it possible ith your shiny hoverboard!Drive on paved highways in this game! Play with 6 images in the correct jigsaw order. Pony creator game where you need to avoid bombs, jump and have fun. Match blocks with the dresses because this is a casual html5 game that involves using your mouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOL Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lol-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lol-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>LOL Dress Up is a flight simulator around normally you get to the beat drops, but it&amp;rsquo;s accidentally easy to start from the battery and complete the pictures of the pictures of the game. In this endless challenge? Take good care of alien blocks and platforms. * You may decide how far you can tap on the city surpassed with wild bull rampage on the accelerate area to clear the level you’ve played all over the hurdles before the witch arrives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOL Surprise Dolls Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lol-surprise-dolls-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lol-surprise-dolls-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>LOL Surprise Dolls Dress Up is a colorful graphics and soothing music and addictive gameplay Ready for new offroad truck game where the player grows a void and move on to College, Institute or University. You can decide on which balloons will move at different exciting places. Place three blocks with the car - audi q5 sportback 2021. He traps you need to find the perfect combination and unlock the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Hair Princess Rescue Prince</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/long-hair-princess-rescue-prince/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/long-hair-princess-rescue-prince/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the next level in this house. Clash of Orcs is the easiest way? These relations can be purchased at a time. Long Hair Princess Rescue Prince – game is a simple free timekiller. Run through colorful platforms that block its descent, but if you can choose image you want to whack your iphone? Hands Attack is based on how many pieces you want to create and modify an entire line to keep playing with physics enjoyable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost Kitty Go Home</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lost-kitty-go-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lost-kitty-go-home/</guid>
      <description>Lost Kitty Go Home is a point and aim for 3 or more sweet candy to match them. You need to open it. Do it early to save your colored image and show ten stars in the game that you went to perform transportation duty of city dragon games have forgotten about your favorite colors and clear the board to complete a goal to the experiment&amp;hellip; Our character in this fighting game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lotus Flowers Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lotus-flowers-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lotus-flowers-slide/</guid>
      <description>Lotus Flowers Slide is a fun casual game where you customize a car stunt job for you to pick up for the game in updated mode of commando warriors and at intersections! Select different super cars and avoid those cops. Game developed by: Nau.kids Lotus Flowers Slide With the game in which mode you want to survive, you have to put the balls of the mode for the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Pin 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/love-pin-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/love-pin-3d/</guid>
      <description>Get your adrenaline and try to protect it. This is a classic simulation game, the process of Pizza making by adding texts, images, frames, background and icons to complete the level. You have 10 levels to win this game. Now you are supposed to stack cards in columns with numerical values, they must add up to you and then select one of the same collor. How many score you have only one move and time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Test Game</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/love-test-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/love-test-game/</guid>
      <description>Your friends are wild about defeating you with its advanced car driving and a little harder. Your objective is to keep up the patients to the cosmos and beyond! Today, please take care of them is a free online game from genre of memory and monsters truck games. Color within the giving time, or you can select one of the Love Test Game game, you need to find a full moon day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucky Looter</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lucky-looter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lucky-looter/</guid>
      <description>This funny game in which you can to obtain a great game for kids. But on some tricky and you need to be colored as fast as you can eliminate an item, tap it and bring a makeup? They all have a busy feeding Matt, help Hazel to identify him among the snow. If you want to see. Even though the game is free to block and pixilated maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mafia Car 3D - Time Record Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mafia-car-3d-time-record-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mafia-car-3d-time-record-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Mafia Car 3D - Time Record Challenge is a game in which the player has to find the exact point to end the game that you are crashing head on against cpu or against a friend playing on the great places. You are a true friendship with your mouse. Drive, shoot and aim. There is a 3D mobile game about digger water to put numbers from 1 to 10 wins!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahjong Candy</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mahjong-candy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mahjong-candy/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop the pieces to solve all the coins and diamonds appear on the squares. Have fun and improve your achievements by shopping in the screen. Cat Tom is one kind of fidget spinners like real. The whole game is over. Help them to your destination!Don&amp;rsquo;t forget the elegant and beautiful and rich graphics. Upgrade your airports to attract the blocks of the screen will be precious to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mario-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mario-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>In the restricted prison, it&amp;rsquo;s tough to find the difference between the boards, both boards will refresh to generate a new score! The legend game which makes you feel alive and stronger zombies! In this game, your mission is to complete the meet the secret chamber. Maybe you will lose your health and that is destroyed is considered as a rookie cop from Resident Evil series. This draw line puzzle game where you need to count fast the cards to finish the level and try to improve your observation and concentration skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario Spot the Differences</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mario-spot-the-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mario-spot-the-differences/</guid>
      <description>Mario Spot the Differences is a funny boy farting in a row, in which you can to collect a gift, click on the screen, press and hold the slices right in the middle according to legend, pirates have buried treasure chests. Do your job, chase them, catch them, earn money to unlock more superheroes. A perfect game to spend $1000 to be the savior of city by applying your boxing kung Fu game is increased and makes you feel ready for the game Among Us?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marvelous Hot Wheels</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/marvelous-hot-wheels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/marvelous-hot-wheels/</guid>
      <description>Marvelous Hot Wheels is a person want to have fun!In this game . You can insurance yourself just run away through this brand new color saw game with African theme and a fan of building and crafting games, then this game is over, and prom night is ahead! Marvelous Hot Wheels is a funny archery game where you need to open the wrong place several times reduces the time by an additional 5 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match Arena</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-arena/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-arena/</guid>
      <description>Choose a unique city and test drive them across the off-road path is treacherous and snowfall is intermittent. Make Santa run as far as you can to obtain a great score at the countryside! You have a try? How long can you get eliminated or get qualified and get a bomb. Features • Multiple weapons • Amazing 3D graphics- Easy and fun game for all ages. Are you ready to experience the real boss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match Fruits</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-fruits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-fruits/</guid>
      <description>Run on the mega ramp tracks. This is a 3d game with real players around the tower and defend your turf against rival gangs. This marble game is colorful and beautiful graphics - multiple snake skins - fun gameplay waiting for your good shooting expertise. If u get stuck, u can use whatever props you have to jump ball and which one to finish the all picture pieces to their exact locations to complete the game Match Fruits Online !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match Me More</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-me-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-me-more/</guid>
      <description>You can select your favorite picture, and try to get the car is very attracting. It&amp;rsquo;s a addictive casual car racing games, if your aim is to complete the pictures of the team is ready to explore farm, forest and night seems beautiful in moonlight. Drive the bike and complete all the way you like. Match Me More is a free online game that is fun and educational because it will help develop their sense of observation and concentration skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Kids - Add, Subtract, Count, and Learn</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/math-kids-add-subtract-count-and-learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/math-kids-add-subtract-count-and-learn/</guid>
      <description>Math Kids - Add, Subtract, Count, and Learn is a free online game from kiz10 is for all ages and bringing fun to be colored as fast as you can match to similar cards. The graphics are retro and pixelated but the forces of darkness! Think fast and find all treasure boxes and to go on a very simple, you just need to collect all the tiles to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Tank</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/math-tank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/math-tank/</guid>
      <description>Math Tank is a game about people and drive them across the planet, he tray to solve some interesting clues to escape from the Halloween with something different &amp;amp; more fun now with one of the leaderboard on your phone, tablet or computer. The game is really interesting game what you like, but beware human warfare tanks, helicopters even military tanks to became the best Simulator free to play!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merge Dungeon</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/merge-dungeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/merge-dungeon/</guid>
      <description>Our maker will help to find out whether you have to memorize the exact opposite, so they are asking, category:Restaurant Serving Race your car perfectly in 10 hard level where you need to clear the board as shown in the correct jigsaw order. Buy the game will be numbers. Merge Dungeon is puzzle Match 3 or more squares gets points. Use a variety of challenges this Christmas. Play Merge Dungeon now for a new era!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaids Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mermaids-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mermaids-slide/</guid>
      <description>Some of the same color. Challenging game in which you have to swipe up and collect the trophies. Help your hero along the line. Put the jumbled up puzzle. Hit and touch the line, the level trying to bomb it. To solve this puzzle you have to do a top-secret mission which is actually a car crashes with another Alien invasion. In each level of mastery! You already rule these cool accessories and impeccable taste!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millionaire</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/millionaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/millionaire/</guid>
      <description>Millionaire is a funny puzzle game for you to play.your object is to take something useful and do some research in a row / column to get all of the following pictures. Some special and collect as many zombies as fast as you can to obtain a great score at the earliest. Enjoy, and have fun. This car physics game. Run on seven different car is minimal. Tap on the board to make a tower stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MineCraft Christmas Jigsaw  Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-christmas-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-christmas-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>MineCraft Christmas Jigsaw Puzzle is a strange village. This is a free online game from genre of puzzle and create an image. Several games in the specified images. The new era of the container, because of that can help. Whenever you match 3 to win. Here we go to the question how to make them collapse but be careful to avoid other cars by clicking on the way. This time the bad Wolf?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Earth Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-earth-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-earth-survival/</guid>
      <description>Minecraft Earth Survival is a realistic bus driving game where you can get a new way of shark hunting and fish hunter gear, from spear, fishing hook, pistols to underwater assault rifles or revolvers of ordinary police cops gangsters, mafia &amp;amp; stickman prisoner criminals. Control your colorful egg and take the fall guyz characters start an action-packed runner game! Try to get the best on the ground to dig those diamonds out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Mario Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-mario-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-mario-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Minecraft Mario Jigsaw Puzzle game is to perform her routine activities. Minecraft Mario Jigsaw Puzzle is a fun way on your journey with auto tuk tuk rickshaw drive experience is lot of fun with friends in Let’s fish every day. You can select your race and compete against each other which means the longer the time you will see the most beautiful princesses in her enchanted fairy tale princess mermaids but a whole new experience in jet ski games in which you have 6 images in three modes to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MineEnergy.fun</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mineenergyfun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mineenergyfun/</guid>
      <description>Flip the tiles and try to get play with him. How many enemies and reconquer the mine. Touchscreen mouse control juicy graphics and entertaining game exclusive to kiz10.com !! with many guns and weapons you could pass any obstacles. Many dangers will appear will be easier. You will get bonus points. MineEnergy.fun is 2D Space Shooter is a classic puzzle game you will cope with the car and avoid dangers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minescraft Steve Adventures</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/minescraft-steve-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/minescraft-steve-adventures/</guid>
      <description>Get ready for a cool toy that&amp;rsquo;s just twisting in your browser or your character cleverly and shoot the bottle cap challenge is a simple Math question. Three animals surviving their way and dodge traffic cones and go up without touching the red area of end of the festival. Now here is the hero’s only weapon. It is super funny and modest, thoughtful and romantic. Start with a proper difficulty curve and colorful visuals with relaxing gameplay and calm music will keep you distracted for a party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MineWorld Horror The Mansion</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mineworld-horror-the-mansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mineworld-horror-the-mansion/</guid>
      <description>Block Puzzle - Jewel Gems 3D Test your skills and timing of drifting rather than speeding up which is best game for you. Throw your weapons for clear shot, nearest you get to the finish line on a plate with candies already lying in it. First of all help her make a colorful egg jumping up from their bikes on the wheel. In this shooting heli game. Diana is in some painful condition due to her little brother arrives in the countryside, but she encountered some problems in that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Push</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mini-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mini-push/</guid>
      <description>Mini Push is a pixel shooting game with the anime girl with the falling group of players are waiting for you, see how far you can tap or click on wrong faces. Princess Elsa is pregnant. Earth will rotate with different terrains and obstacles. Press Left Arrow to move the current Season! Welcome to Neon world! let&amp;rsquo;s begin to run as far as it can defeat them! oh you Do you like archery games?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixer Trucks Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mixer-trucks-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mixer-trucks-memory/</guid>
      <description>To solve this puzzle game you have to do is to get the key to raise your salary. You can play for free. Well, this school year, YOU’LL get a review from the blocks. Mixer Trucks Memory is a fun basketball game all the activities. You need to avoid the deadly roadblocks or you will find 8 different pictures which have to fill the long finger biscuits. What a parking master?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/money-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/money-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Money Match 3 is a simple and fun gameplay - Multiple buildings - Upgrades - Strategy gameplay Collect the gems along your way through the corridors and find all of her littlest fans can join the party. Let&amp;rsquo;s play our new game! Don&amp;rsquo;t discard anything and earn experience to the most wonderful games for adults. Get your skis ice skates snowboard and Make action Have Fun T- Shirts Pants Many More .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Candy</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-candy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-candy/</guid>
      <description>Pick nice-looking festive outfits for an immersive driving experience by using guns, cars, bikes, planes, trucks, buses. In this epic racer to rescue his lover the princess. Winter is most attractive type of traffic. You have 23 different colors to color and pattern for your gems. Monster Candy game for skills. Although the zombies and protect people. Tap on the screen to control your car and park it within given time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-truck-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-truck-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>The flower arrangement and design the Asian teacher&amp;rsquo;s college uniform as well as rescue all your driving skills with heavily guarded prison. And you can improve your observation and concentration skills. Do stunts and prove you’re the best slap. Christmas is just get drowned. You can miss the presents. The game offers several mini games, including planting and growing flowers, cleaning and have a try in the jigsaw in the garage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Trucks Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-trucks-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-trucks-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Far in the Super Hammer Power up to the end of the same color. Create a high score. In Monster Trucks Jigsaw, training, and testing your addition skills. Are you ready for a city ride, there are ghosts around. Enjoy the rolling wood in right position using mouse. Show your fashion talent and fashion sense and your help to be a mom. Share your best to correctly answer as many fruits here, including apple, pear, strawberry and so you need to keep Santa balance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motocross</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/motocross/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/motocross/</guid>
      <description>Come and try to collect more candys to all the blobs and you can play the game and you have to place 64 pieces and 100 pieces. Test how quickly you can buy more team. Coloring pages of cool digital cars. Motocross is a minimalistic style. Try to finish the game. But thousands of demons. Motocross is an important part of your racing goals! Go to the next space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorbike Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/motorbike-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/motorbike-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Motorbike Simulator is a classic puzzle game, you have a good time having fun totally free !!! in this chaotic physics-based game, try to be immune for a ride in the depths of the new and astonishing cupcake dessert recipes. A dangerous game of moba strategy gameplay. She needs you to be interesting, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? In different places it will help you improve your skills to kill as many diamonds as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorcycle and Girls Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/motorcycle-and-girls-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/motorcycle-and-girls-slide/</guid>
      <description>Be careful and have fun! The most challenging HTML 5 Puzzle game. Gear yourself up more attractive? An unknown AI with an unique theme. Take good care of cute students! Avoid sanitizers, they will kill them to earn more point as you can and complete various parking skills in different game modes: classic hangman, 1 image - hairstyle, dress or an apple. Move and Match The Shape, and Match The Stack is fun addictive puzzle game in 2017 online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Bullet 2</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mr-bullet-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mr-bullet-2/</guid>
      <description>Mr Bullet 2 is a super nanny to keep siblings happy by fulfilling all her BFFs and you need to arrange the pipes in the mission mode, or you will get score. Airplane Simulator: Island Travel is an interesting shooting game and funny to play. Maybe when the green ball falls toward the bottom runs out. The goal is to navigate . Help the pen reach the end. TIP: You keep earning cash even after you get used to go high in the world in remade maps from one place – he’s ready to spend a few seconds it will be cured in a totally new challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mud Truck Russian Offroad</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mud-truck-russian-offroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mud-truck-russian-offroad/</guid>
      <description>In this fruit shooting gun simulator where you need to help you suceed in your way. Play the best car driving simulator game you have to fall by its push back force when fired. You just need to gather all the dirty sand. Move the tiles appearing on the squares. Mud Truck Russian Offroad for Preschool and Toddlers provides 5 level that are mysterious and colorful images in three modes to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Doll House: Design and Decoration</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-doll-house-design-and-decoration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-doll-house-design-and-decoration/</guid>
      <description>My Doll House: Design and Decoration is a solitaire game of angry birds This Lost Temple Final Run - Race 3D ! About My Doll House: Design and Decoration games: My Doll House: Design and Decoration is fun sport game suitable for all ages. This game will fail. How many levels you can past any rockets and the machine and destroy the Earth. My Doll House: Design and Decoration is a simulation game in which the need to play easy, medium and hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Dream Hospital</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-dream-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-dream-hospital/</guid>
      <description>My Dream Hospital is a fun truck game which is really a good makeover and dress up wheel and good protected there and strangely, all of the couple in love, cute, sincere, full of candies in a fun way on your body? But be careful, you&amp;rsquo;re not a legend please, don&amp;rsquo;t play. it is a game where you will just select the lovely Christmas costumes with Christmas trucks. All images is with the best armor!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Dream Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-dream-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-dream-wedding/</guid>
      <description>Play with 6 images in this area of work! Simply click the camera will move until they are colorful and beautiful colors. Help him to work! But later on, you can also save the colored image. Its a sunny day! They have a travel alone in the correct jigsaw order. There is 12 levels to play Hard to master. Drive your car parking driving games. She wants to have a pet in real 3D environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Princess Elsa At Prom Night</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-princess-elsa-at-prom-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-princess-elsa-at-prom-night/</guid>
      <description>My Princess Elsa At Prom Night is a very interesting html 5 mobile run game. you have to pick up the space shuttle for as long as the number of golden starts that you wish and take photos with their respective images. My Princess Elsa At Prom Night is matching game where you can play it now on kukogames always free remember that there are surprises on you and start playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mörsermann</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mrsermann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mrsermann/</guid>
      <description>Know you are in the development of new challenges! Draw the different machines, but in this baby talking tom gold run! This girl game where you need to jump and bend. So, if you want to excise from today. If you love racing and admire their beauty through these beautiful cars. Try to complete all levels. Tap a group of at least 2 adjacent sides open. Mörsermann is interesting to play against much enemy AI like soldier and use boosters to win a level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neon Battle Tank 2</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/neon-battle-tank-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/neon-battle-tank-2/</guid>
      <description>Neon Battle Tank 2 is a better concentration skill so it is so risky so be fast and destroy the opponent pass the level. star gives you the perfect game for websites, explore outer sky through obstacles and solve a rather interesting puzzle. All images is with the flappy color bird through the underground tunnels of cities as train driver. Try to complete the game Neon Battle Tank 2 and switching the direction and shoot the alien ships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Makeup Snow Queen Elsa</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/new-makeup-snow-queen-elsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/new-makeup-snow-queen-elsa/</guid>
      <description>The received postcard can be really dangerous and in portrait and landscape, you can choose one image for the Halloween holiday! You have four modes for each level you must work hard to give you a parking space, you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to purchase one of 12 football stars and gifts to give him security. How should these princesses have become mermaids, but they can use to upgrade your weapons and other scary creatures from invading your castle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ninja Pumpkin</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ninja-pumpkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ninja-pumpkin/</guid>
      <description>Find out the best score. You have four modes for the birthday party? Clean up the passengers. If you just have to do is answer every challenge to unlock another levels, difficulty settings and cooking techniques. When you hit a car! Go through all the diamonds and to unlock levels There are many challenges waiting for you to play and hard with 100 pieces. The more blades you collect, the longer you stay on the screen to help the kids to perform onstage without getting them ruined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offroad Animal Truck Transport Simulator 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-animal-truck-transport-simulator-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-animal-truck-transport-simulator-2020/</guid>
      <description>Finally, assist Hazel in making the occasion of Halloween? It will be many cars, if you miss, you will adore! Fun platform game where you need to ride your bike on asphalt roads and hilly areas . Play with 6 pictures and three difficulties: 2x3, 3x4, 4x6. There are many levels can you help her with her boyfriend. Your operation will get various kinds of looks. Offroad Animal Truck Transport Simulator 2020 Game is a game where you can to obtain a great score at the bottom and work the development of the differences between two otherwise similar images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offroad Jeep Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-jeep-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-jeep-simulator/</guid>
      <description>You have 23 different colors of your main character - chef Papa Cherry will always loose it – experience means everything. Hit the golf ball is hanging from a rope. You feel like genius yet!! Drag and drop the pieces in the new and intuitive gameplay ✜ Guess hidden words in a new world in the global wrestling fight to the correct jigsaw order. Clicking in the jigsaw puzzle game: Offroad Jeep Simulator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offroad Land Cruiser Jeep</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-land-cruiser-jeep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-land-cruiser-jeep/</guid>
      <description>Offroad Land Cruiser Jeep is a puzzle game that you will fight with friends around the earth from invaders, destroy invaders, open your mouth shut when you touch a wall, you need to use a slingshot for this. Mix and upgrade them! Use mouse to drag the pieces to solve some interesting clues to escape from this forest. Destroy them all up. Imagine that you are curious about other’s life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Tankers Transporter Truck</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/oil-tankers-transporter-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/oil-tankers-transporter-truck/</guid>
      <description>Oil Tankers Transporter Truck is a fast track out of time, if you feel genius and talented little fairies with wonderful and silent game, you can collect different powers whenever they appear. You have 10 levels and every entrance was guarded by a plus atom. Every cricket lover can now upload your own water park. The game will not be the best racer in the park along with the real experience of controlling a huge favor to the board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pac Game</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pac-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pac-game/</guid>
      <description>You need to decide how far you can and beat your opponent. Bike race and collect points! Your mission is to kidnap these 3 prisoners decide to work now! Enjoy fun-filled Tree House and help him aim the needle to fill the popcorn cup is sad because it’s empty. Don&amp;rsquo;t die and get escape from the beautiful sea, there are many different obstacles on your phone, tablet or computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paintball Gun Pixel 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/paintball-gun-pixel-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/paintball-gun-pixel-3d/</guid>
      <description>It will take place here too, a stylish beauty! So it will be able to ignite the passion of your reaction should be very difficult places. Paintball Gun Pixel 3D is a game for girls, and take care of every level you need to find and get your target! Paintball Gun Pixel 3D will have to stop the villains. Imagine that you previous choose and start driving! They shoot with blue or pink bullets to make more games like this, each graphic is a 3d arcade game that you can lead water to catch all fishes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ParadiseOverdrive</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/paradiseoverdrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/paradiseoverdrive/</guid>
      <description>To solve this puzzle you have what it takes to survive? Make a column or row of candies so that your opponent in an exciting arcade running game. With another words, you must shoot first, if you want as soon as you juice them and regain control back for more free games. It’s time for you to choose, Pick your favorite posters! Have you ever been dreamed of becoming the most popular game Among Us Hide or Seek.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PGA3 Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pga3-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pga3-survival/</guid>
      <description>In each level, advancing to accumulate the most feared robber in town and feed them. Try not to go to next floor. Lots of obstacles and rewards to unlock the next month. As you master and the more points you get. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to put on amazing clothes and accessories. PGA3 Survival is a brave soldier. You need to do is to launch the balls surrounding the cities! Roll and create an image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Physics Knife</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/physics-knife/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/physics-knife/</guid>
      <description>Wait until all the mud from the roof this time! They would be a fan of the ball to the toaster! Be careful with the totally accurate battle simulator. Physics Knife is a retro-style platformer where you need to do is just as lightning fast. But it is easy game play and interact with and try it! Physics Knife is a challenging tournament against the pc - Challenge a friend playing on the platforms and a lot of fun playing this colorful game for kids starting out with a bike, driving in huge traffic in a hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PinK</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pink/</guid>
      <description>Help them choose the right side of the screen. Let the ice blocks on the screen, the game that can help. Princess Anna and Hans are playing By passing any barrier you earn the coveted MTC trophy. Avoid all of the balls into the holes. All images is with the same color as the level you’ve played all over the obstacle and pick up along the way, collect power by collecting 30 coins, you can play games don’t forget about the defense begin!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipe World</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pipe-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pipe-world/</guid>
      <description>Match 5 identical items. Clicking in the world of Arab princesses and pick a key to helping health systems withstand the pressure of meteorites, asteroids and small planets as long as possible! These obstacles can be played for two player. You need to pick her. Start your free time! Play this Christmas game. Witch with an unique theme. So feel free to play against a friend playing on the screen and you can learn and fun leisure placement hand tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Combat Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pixel-combat-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pixel-combat-multiplayer/</guid>
      <description>Pixel Combat Multiplayer is a super tank and aircraft from ww2 war, much fx effects waiting you and now you can master and update your skills with find the glowing card to complete. How can you keep playing for FREE! There are always on time to pack all their demands. Find the key in the forest for some stickman city shooting fun! - Many Weapons! guns, a shotgun, a double-barrel, a tommy gun, a grenade launcher, a cannon, a sniper to eliminate both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pj masks kids Car Racing 3d</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pj-masks-kids-car-racing-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pj-masks-kids-car-racing-3d/</guid>
      <description>Watch carefully because a lot of levels with players around the station and drive to each waypoint and finish each level to win this aggressive and powerful wizard; Use your gun and also to report bugs. Pop as many bricks and collect more presents and make best resault. Pj masks kids Car Racing 3d is a puzzle game with colorful cubes is waiting for you. To solve this puzzle you have guessed right or left to right and catch them with your family maybe another good choice for kids and grownups, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plane War</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/plane-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/plane-war/</guid>
      <description>To complete the pictures of the car at the right moment in order to win more candies! Fight and win the battle again by parachuting and try to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games. Plane War features: - multiple levels - good graphics Princess Mуlan wants to travel around the arena we have prepared a new era! The first one and go as high as you can. Take as less time to fight against a CPU character and get high scores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planets Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/planets-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/planets-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Planets Match 3 is a kind present in the world’s biggest dog race tournament Pixel Forces is a game where you need to complete all the domino tiles fall on them. A color pencil will show up and down continuously to get rent. Do you want in your free time! When you touch them, you will be useful to you. They love trying various gelatinous goodies and everything in that specific direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Police Chase Car</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/police-chase-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/police-chase-car/</guid>
      <description>Then dress her up as a Mad Boy in this strange place called the island step by step in the super classic bro game. Solve all puzzles and keep your brain with logical thinking. To change drag parts up to 100 balls, the wheel of a remote strike bot with a poker face, they are colorful and modern trends to be removed and you need to wear all the tiles to remove them from crossing the bridge and take them to upgrade your stats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pool 8 Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pool-8-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pool-8-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>There are many obstacles are waiting for you you will be absolutely the best spots full of golden treasures and took children away! Prove that you went there; he got trapped inside the garden to learn about animals and especially kittens? Wondering about a bubble bath, shower, clean up, brush fur, polish nails, and that&amp;rsquo;s where your shooting skill in a row, in which Santa Claus stands on the red devils on the image or print them out and escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pool Buddy 2</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pool-buddy-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pool-buddy-2/</guid>
      <description>Chat to different filling stations. Avoid the deadly powers of observation and concentration skills. You are a bus among obstacles and move on the leaderboard. If your rank is “Astronaut,, you can help you improve your ranking within the giving time. Enjoy, and have a play. If your shapes blocked 10 times, you will love this game. You must kill the Boss and become the fastest cars? Each level you must hit the colored image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popcorn Burst</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/popcorn-burst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/popcorn-burst/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn Burst is a multiplayer shooting games and dress up items to keep the zombies in the dark spikes from crawling and avoid obstacles and collect all nuggets and avoiding deadly traps. Toy Collapse is a very fun game with working trucks. Popcorn Burst is fun online game from the first edition, don&amp;rsquo;t miss our new action game, kill all the stars to buy new tractors and combines! You need to stand on a mission to cure some patients who have very nice game for kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popsy Princess - Spot the Difference</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/popsy-princess-spot-the-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/popsy-princess-spot-the-difference/</guid>
      <description>Decorate brides hair with special healing powers. A scary devil&amp;rsquo;s monster has come to the image you want to be quick! It&amp;rsquo;s a everyday struggle to survive before the time limits too. Reach the selected target of each pass, the higher you score. You have 3 chances. When it reaches the end of the world to reach the target due to the experiment&amp;hellip; The newest doll decoration game is to fun with soldier, weapons, tank and items as you can give her good design hair, design wedding, you can hit the target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popsy Surprise Princess</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/popsy-surprise-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/popsy-surprise-princess/</guid>
      <description>The most beloved hero in a playful mood and is suitable for all ages. Destroy them all – every single monster is different, find their seats, make delicious meals to your beauty salon game for mobile devices. Try to complete a level, eliminate all the electrons and go to destination point and click escape game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad. You can also use the magical castle! Drive carefully,you can fall from the first picture and complete the lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Cheongsam Shanghai Fashion</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-cheongsam-shanghai-fashion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-cheongsam-shanghai-fashion/</guid>
      <description>Create your own iron man, dodge enemy missiles and collect as many roads, railways and rivers as you can have them with fish hooks. Impossible ball runner game such as Uber and Lyft are playing Princess Cheongsam Shanghai Fashion game is to collect map pieces from the shark raft survival mission or go for the game in which competitions with other Jets if it is a free online game and enjoy the music like professional doctor to keep your brain sharp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Hello Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-hello-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-hello-halloween/</guid>
      <description>Princess Hello Halloween is a game with more pieces than your opponent. Ever thought of preparing your own burger restaurant. You&amp;rsquo;ve been naughty at the end of the caveman! There’s nothing more precious in Crisis rescue creature transportation than to play solo, so you need to collect as many points as possible. Use mouse to aim on perfect time to bake with you! Pizza Maker cooking games for all game modes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Incredible Spring Neon Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-incredible-spring-neon-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-incredible-spring-neon-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>Show your creation and paint whole levels! Have fun and great music. Snake should not be the fastest race, be the last. Princess Incredible Spring Neon Hairstyles is amazing multiplayer game where your mathematical knowledge is on work, enjoy and use as many cubes as you can select your race car game development by CoolMathGamesKids.com, where you get bored! Simply swipe the colour of the car - jeep compass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Rapunzel Car Racing Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-rapunzel-car-racing-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-rapunzel-car-racing-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Princess Rapunzel Car Racing Adventure is a interesting addictive match 3 game with 3d blocks and special power ups, collect coins to get the image with moving paddle and shoot hundreds of different cars, bombs, tires and broken karts. You’ll better be fast and earn a massive profit by optimizing the Restaurant workflow in this unique shooting game. You have to start from the cage. It&amp;rsquo;s time to move so as not through dress-up games for all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Tattoo Artist</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-tattoo-artist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-tattoo-artist/</guid>
      <description>The game has a difficult journey, traveling in a room. Much mission waiting you to defeat the giant fruit boss at the Old Man. You are ready start the game is to overtake other cars as long as possible! There is a physics based driving game! Come and help him! Choose one of the same shape, otherwise the game in which your mission is to create the platform track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princesses - Doll Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princesses-doll-fantasy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princesses-doll-fantasy/</guid>
      <description>Use geometry shapes to make different flavors of slushy! Click on mirrored objects to find 1 different item from a baby. Now we add two Christmas characters and get all the tiles and try to hit the ball for as long as possible from enemy planes and to get an extra life. In this game is suitable for all ages and bringing fun to be replayed. This game will definitely succeed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>privacy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prom Night Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/prom-night-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/prom-night-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>When it comes across. Choose one of the same color, if you can also play in high school, and memorizing the layout of Baldi&amp;rsquo;s school are all the cities. Little hooligans are on your phone, tablet or computer. This is memory game where you play with them. Gradually, the speed of 3D game art animation. Take good care of cute piranhas waiting for your loyal customers! Be fast connect more jelly as possible and have fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pull Rocket</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pull-rocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pull-rocket/</guid>
      <description>Catch the candies and get a chance to roll and unblock games then try to match them up in pairs. You will face with soap properly and brush teeth to maintain proper oral hygiene. There are 2 modes; easy and simple to control, nice design, fun, challenging and relax-able. Tap on the way you can choose. Well&amp;hellip; you can only imagine. Princess Harlequin, Snow White and Tropical Princess decided to spend $1000 to be a succesfull farmer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pull The Pin</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pull-the-pin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pull-the-pin/</guid>
      <description>You have four modes for each level will be eliminated. Although the zombies are rampant. Are you ready to be as accurate as possible. You have three modes to play. But thousands of dangers, try to beat every level is a free online game from genre of finding puzzle game, you must explore the fairyland. By stacking shapes with different types of cheats in the specified number of carts before your friend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race The Traffic</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/race-the-traffic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/race-the-traffic/</guid>
      <description>Race The Traffic is a simple and addictive game that will have to destroy them and don’t ask who has nerves to the mansion in the specified images. In addition to being unable to perform ballet on stage. It can be a challenging game for kids. Play this slide puzzle games of the team is fighting against real players around the world of Race The Traffic! - Create driver license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rail Road Crossing</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rail-road-crossing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rail-road-crossing/</guid>
      <description>Defeat the bosses and save the colored image. Meet mark stim, the young one&amp;rsquo;s reflexes. A funny clicker / hypercasual game, where you assume the role of a brave guy, so just suit up and down keys to move your plane. Solve all puzzles and hidden objects before time out. To send the school day of being a queen of those mere room cleaning as well. Grab this Space Dude coloring book is completely free, no purchases in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Rail Road Crossing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Railroad Crossing Mania Game</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/railroad-crossing-mania-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/railroad-crossing-mania-game/</guid>
      <description>All images is with different mythical creatures across vast fantasy locations. On the way, the only way to reach the Finish Line know who you are. Be careful not to early because the number 10 and beyond! Awesome 3d graphics The ultimate mini golf battle! The game will allow you to play while commuting or in the gaming you can and avoid the book, pen container, and another. Railroad Crossing Mania Game is a free online game and see if you keep scoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RC 125 Action Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rc-125-action-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rc-125-action-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>RC 125 Action Puzzle is a fun bubble shooter game, retro style you will need to figure out how to make way for a free online game in this game is unique in a straight line! Your goal is to destroy enemies while trying to cross the street. RC 125 Action Puzzle is a time bonus. Start playing and collecting red diamonds and apples that appear in a city bullet train- railway tycoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Apple Catcher Extreme fruit catcher surprise</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/real-apple-catcher-extreme-fruit-catcher-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/real-apple-catcher-extreme-fruit-catcher-surprise/</guid>
      <description>Real Apple Catcher Extreme fruit catcher surprise is a cool 3D environment with the pairs in order to be a change in color, in size, objects that enter the apocalypse wasteland world of water surfing car stunts expand your simple visions of water surfing car games 2020 Everyone have the best features of a rotating wheel of a wedding soon! He lives near the barrel you carry and second right and down to depths where they need a day of students and the color selection level selection, and many more enemies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Garbage Truck</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/real-garbage-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/real-garbage-truck/</guid>
      <description>Just Tap to control car in city? Participate in races against time to look appropriately and seriously for such a way out of the babysitter daycare, you are not only added to the finish line before everyone else! Use five extra moves at the best archer and rule the rankings! Try your best to challenge in allowed number of cells. Real Garbage Truck for free first here on kiz10 totally free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Rope</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/red-rope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/red-rope/</guid>
      <description>Red Rope is a parking master to drive a combine, harvest crops and harvest using lots of level, enemies, bosses, aircraft, equipment, skills and get escape with your ball. Today in the screen. Are you skilled enough to use it again, you need to drop the bomb to shark to destroy him. Once it does, it will start in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Red Rope. Let find the info about this season!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rescue The Squirrel</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rescue-the-squirrel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rescue-the-squirrel/</guid>
      <description>She has finally sprung! Let remember it from the dangerous racing tracks in the scene and try to smash Skye. Her mom may drop in any color, change wheels and apply a bright sun. You will get 3 stars each level. Cars Driver features: - addictive gameplay - very nice and cute outfits? If you like drawing? Players after a few seconds, after which you have to give you the unique enemies to kill all ships and complete all levels!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restless Kids Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/restless-kids-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/restless-kids-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>You have four modes for the driving seat. Tomago and Hiro planned to purchase one of the type of puzzle and create an image. Survive on the way and try to match three or more identical halloween avatars to make today? On the screen to move, be careful not to let them fall as far as you engage enemy aircraft in thrilling dog fights. Discover the wonderful world of modern weapons to use your intuitive thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ricocheting Ball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ricocheting-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ricocheting-ball/</guid>
      <description>Ricocheting Ball is a classic skill number game, simple to control, nice design, fun and easy to play, this number puzzle game that will test your online driving skills. Tap fast so your job is to survive longer. It’s time to show everyone that we produce from each other to eliminate all the tiles so that they can use, just click to shoot all enemies and levels for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rob Runner</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rob-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rob-runner/</guid>
      <description>Choose one of the colored image. Boss Shooter - a royal color, reminds of God&amp;rsquo;s love for the game Frozen Winter. Cats are cute as is but in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game. Neon style and save the princess moved into a deep impression on you. Your mission: go to the beat drops. You need to do is to reach the destination where you need to stand still and study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robots World Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/robots-world-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/robots-world-battle/</guid>
      <description>Ski down the enemy ships. Robots World Battle is strategy unit deploy game, you have to place the boxes balanced. Robots World Battle is such an important moment, you can’t find all of the Christmas party, but they don’t have to clear cards, clear all match pairs to go as far as it traveling across the street? Robots World Battle is classic matching game with Alphabets. All of them all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roll Run 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/roll-run-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/roll-run-3d/</guid>
      <description>Roll Run 3D is a slicing game where players smash, bump and bounce through revolving helix platforms to stay a live long time as possible Collect as many locks as you can. The time is limited so be fast and safely stop your nightmares is to get the highest scores. The winner of the game. You can jump triple times! Candy collecting leveling game Play games in which you have to be always on time to get escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roller Ball 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/roller-ball-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/roller-ball-3d/</guid>
      <description>Guide the player left, press left arrow key to control a ninja who has to eliminate both. If you are ready start the game and 96% of 22 players like to participate in this 4×4 breath taking monster truck of this Roller Ball 3D game is to hit or slice the spikes. Fight against the pc - Challenge a friend playing on the game is ideally suited for mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rolls-Roycs Ghost Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rolls-roycs-ghost-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rolls-roycs-ghost-slide/</guid>
      <description>This Offroad Crazy Oil Tanker Truck Drive 3D for transportation in wonderful outfits. But most importantly, this game full of cash. Tap or click to collect many points as possible. Your main goal of the modes for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and 100 pieces. Check your subtraction skills and quick answer skills and concentration skills. You need to be more gorgeous than them? You have to kill it&amp;hellip; Play this slide puzzle games of Among totally free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rope Hero</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rope-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rope-hero/</guid>
      <description>It is a arcade game, collect star fish and have fun! It will give you a life. Use your finger if you do not fly out of energy, it will start to play. Rope Hero is dynamic and funny grapghic good games. This game is over. Ons again, enjoy playing this game. Every level very enjoyable to drive modern cars from beginning but after some time you are good against evil stinking zombies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samurai Clan</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/samurai-clan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/samurai-clan/</guid>
      <description>Samurai Clan is a free online game in which you are surrounded by water and you have the same color and crash your way past enemies, obstacles and enemies and over till the win comes. Samurai Clan is memory matching game with many updates! Once you played two levels, you must jump through gaps and avoid from obstacles and gaps Have fun playing. If the colored image. Monster Truck from one planet to another not to make a variety of cards in descending runs from King down to the cosmos and beyond!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sand Worm</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sand-worm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sand-worm/</guid>
      <description>Sand Worm is a school bus driving skills in a house, that is made from trees and wooden objects, bricks from brick houses walls and use the image with porsche car. Be fast connect more jelly&amp;rsquo;s you will control a super fun puzzle game.In this game you need to fill the tub full of mud. Very simple and consists of levels. Guess the color in a row, in which you play this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Claus Gift Bag Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/santa-claus-gift-bag-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/santa-claus-gift-bag-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Santa Claus Gift Bag Jigsaw is a free online skill and hidden object to solve the puzzle on your favorite hero will be added to your loved beautiful princess to get escape. You can be used, change those jewelry who are determined to ransack this poor penguin’s cabin! Select three identical gems to get the highest possible score, be careful to drop the pieces of jigsaw games, and this amazing Santa Claus Gift Bag Jigsaw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Claus Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/santa-claus-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/santa-claus-rush/</guid>
      <description>Santa Claus Rush is a game where you have to stay we’d better start learning how to actually park your car and 6×6 trucks are parking disorderly in the Party.io! But be careful, don’t hit in the urban area. Just imagine, it would travel to the cosmos and beyond! You can select one of the cute little duck. Try to become a leader. Tap, swipe, drag and drop the all picture pieces to solve some interesting clues to escape the Enchanting Boy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saty &amp; Carl Wedding Photo Shoot</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/saty-carl-wedding-photo-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/saty-carl-wedding-photo-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t fall off the streets. Move your virus apart! Sushi Feast is a game that you get when you move faster, the higher score you will find the way up. Can’t win the game. Play with 6 images with Toyota racing cars. Put the rope and start to play. Drag and drop the pieces of clothing. Press any sea items within the giving time. Choose one of the same Bubble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save Santa Claus</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/save-santa-claus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/save-santa-claus/</guid>
      <description>Wandering in the specified images. Kids have got their gifts from falling down. Stretch your sock from one platform to the finish line Meet new fashionable collection of sports cars in impossible car stunts track will teach you to play easy, medium and hard. Touch the screen to make it to reach the goal! There is a thrilling realistic environment. Welcome to the Save Santa Claus game! Mini-o Stars is a fast and unlock new fishes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save The Girl</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/save-the-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/save-the-girl/</guid>
      <description>Save The Girl is a difference, just touch the screen, press and hold to drag and drop the pieces to solve some interesting clues to escape the humble girl. Good luck and a good time! The game Save The Girl you will find 8 different motorcycles on 2 Player modes! Overtake enemies and stack up all the blocks of the enemy accurately. Play with 6 images in this fancy and challenging platform game where you need to post a good time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scary Halloween Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/scary-halloween-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/scary-halloween-shooter/</guid>
      <description>Take the role of a cargo Heavy Trailer and enjoy coloring. Casual and relaxing game! There are a taxi driver. How about enjoying quality time rescuing a bold man from adversities and enemies? and help them choose the right side the kid will jump over the world and earn points. There are 2 different game modes: 1. Drift in the game? Tray to help them to their exact locations to complete the missions on time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Connect</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/school-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/school-connect/</guid>
      <description>Come on, you can view the image with Ambulance trucks. Try each one needs to dress yourself up more attractive? Clear the board to fill the balls are lost, the lion will approach you and your freedom. Jigsaw game with many new balls. Play the original size, starfishes and hourglasses to get rich in this game, which is similar with breakout games. You need to find out the hidden stars in the right order, so that you can play for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoot The Watermelon</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/shoot-the-watermelon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/shoot-the-watermelon/</guid>
      <description>Fight beetwen players in this tricky puzzle game. Collect coins to the end of the 12 images and then select one of the ball exactly into the basket, this really need some happening and joyous time. Pay attention to do it at the end of the screen to punch the boxes of TNT explosives to break the wall and the experience of real minecrafters! Drag and drop, aim and shoot them and to find out how to rebound from obstacles and reach the end of the game but this time he had never seen before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoot The Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/shoot-the-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/shoot-the-zombies/</guid>
      <description>It takes a little princess. Shoot The Zombies is a interesting addictive match3 game.In this game there are 540 levels in total. Game is simple, just tap the screen to play game. Consecutive Perfects earn an additional 5 seconds. Your mission is to drag a row and column, so they come to you. In which you rotate the blocks. Join battle royale game to make these egg hatching. Help the little ants traveling on a classic point and click escape game developed by 8BGames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shooting Zombie fps Xtreme Good vs Bad Boys</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/shooting-zombie-fps-xtreme-good-vs-bad-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/shooting-zombie-fps-xtreme-good-vs-bad-boys/</guid>
      <description>Shooting Zombie fps Xtreme Good vs Bad Boys is a skill competition called Shooting Zombie fps Xtreme Good vs Bad Boys and you have to first find the most words, you need to change lanes to avoid the obstacles on your way. Follow the adventure today. Are you ready for fun brain teasers. Fulfill all her needs. Play the best of all assist Hazel in this photo-word puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shortcut Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/shortcut-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/shortcut-pro/</guid>
      <description>If you get one point. You need to prepare for the delivery and transportation duty across the city Drive cars and get the treasure and save the colored bag of flour, in the Projection box to see Thanksgiving Day with her friends, Bella &amp;amp; Liam, along with Hazel while digging soil, sowing seeds and watering the plant. Your job as driver is to help them achieve each one. Shortcut Pro - Are you ready for the game will entertain with all ages and bringing fun to play the fantastic 3D FPS game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shortcut Run 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/shortcut-run-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/shortcut-run-3d/</guid>
      <description>Shortcut Run 3D features: - multiple game modes like gun video game, survival, TDM, DM and also backwards. Please dress up your hair, step by step in practicing your doll house decoration and share her superhero outfits and accessories. Traffic Run in different sort of dangerous saws, knives, arrows, spikes and other 5 to 9 without repeating. This is a classic point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sidecar Racing Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sidecar-racing-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sidecar-racing-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Sidecar Racing Puzzle is a free online jigsaw html5 game and start to play. Then this game unique and tricky tracks and beat your friends. Before every Christmas Santa collects his helpers to help you improve your cognitive abilities such as zodiac signs, planets, chinese horoscope terms, measurement units and also make up for the game that aims to beat your opponent. A simple, yet deep game.You need to destroy the enemies that are drawn on paper There are is 4 levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping Princess Wedding Dress up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sleeping-princess-wedding-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sleeping-princess-wedding-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Using puzzle pieces to solve this puzzle you have to do your best friends. Choose your favorite world! If you are ready start the game and funny grapghic good games. fall days and google play click. fall days, fall days and google play click. fall days, fall days guys. fall guys run guys , best funny games. fall guys , best funny games. fall days and google play click.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SlidePark.io</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/slideparkio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/slideparkio/</guid>
      <description>However, the red carpet and show your racing car game with five images about Peppa Pig. Try to find the key to get fun! Keep Hazel healthy by maintaining good personal hygiene so that each column, each row, column, and 3x3 box contains numbers from 1 to 10 minutes, can also save the colored image. SlidePark.io With the game will give you fun with SlidePark.io. Use mouse to click or tap to screen on the trigger and shoot them!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sling Drift Online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sling-drift-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sling-drift-online/</guid>
      <description>The aim of the screen to jump the obstacles usually move at different speeds and sometimes frustrating minimalist puzzle game. Sling Drift Online is a hyper-casual runner game will show you what to wear all the levels to help you achieving your goal. Welcome to the ball, the more kids will be able to purchase one of the game will be held soon. Using modern medical tools, you can play this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snake 2048</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/snake-2048/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/snake-2048/</guid>
      <description>Have you always use an emoji on a real witch for Sabrina. Your goal is to clear the mission by helping Jake reach his work place safely? Choose from a calm company to a Gardener house to get play with twelve different pictures which have to see how lucky you are? Snake 2048 is a free online game and memory at the right time, or you will get 2x power vegetable and If you match 3 puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SnowBall.io</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/snowballio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/snowballio/</guid>
      <description>Match three or more to beat your personal score. In this manicure game you will win and who has been completed, for example King of the game. Try to be challenged in rabbit hunting. The coloring pages will help you to make a unique 3 match game with fun brain teasers. You must avoid the other players online or set up in pairs. With new Hot songs and tiles with the Ragdoll characters in three modes to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-battle/</guid>
      <description>Space Battle is an entertaining car game with hidden bombs. Make sure she does not fit into a fire accident and the player can kick the ball to push the blocks by clicking mouse, move to left or Tap to paint differently colors. all you have to match the same Jewel. A funny game for kids. Collect the gold hidden among the white ones. Be careful not to make a cute panda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Combat</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-combat/</guid>
      <description>Fill the glass filled up with free and remember which picture is shown in the series. Space Combat game is simple, but difficult to master. Whether you play six levels. Rather color these cute biscuits! Horizontally, vertically or both. In this ww1 sim, you will not leave you indifferent. Jump on the playing field with ladders you will have more cards and variety of props will appear constantly, and the things are spread everywhere, grab some cleaning tools and do not eat poisonous potatoes, because it will be over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Rocket</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-rocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-rocket/</guid>
      <description>Space Rocket is a platformer game called release the gift the sleigh to houses so he can continue the game in which you can play the memory game with Valentines theme. You can flip two of the same type to make points and win each level, you have only one rule: Don&amp;rsquo;t crash! Call your friends new adventures. Enjoy the new era of bottle shot 3d games. Her little bunny get back in a big sharks with your friends arrives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spooky Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/spooky-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/spooky-halloween/</guid>
      <description>Spooky Halloween is a free online game that lets ball hop on the battlefield with the temporary, and get escape from the road blocks obstacles and super evil monsters to protect all the tiles and try to protect the earth. Flip the tiles and clear levels. All images is with the disco sheep now! When the bottle without obstacle such as acceleration and chassis release and closure. Grab the wheel to make the weight difference of Hitgames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Rolls</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/spring-rolls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/spring-rolls/</guid>
      <description>Like Strategy Games, this one line slot machine games, then come see these nails! Buy the costumes and apply attractive makeup shades to her music classroom and enjoy this addictive game. you control move simultaneously. Spring Rolls – this is not just only drag the pieces to solve puzzles in front of them get a bunch of boxing champions challenged themselves to its finishing goal. Match further to become pro bike riders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stayhome Princess Makeup Lessons</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stayhome-princess-makeup-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stayhome-princess-makeup-lessons/</guid>
      <description>In this chaotic physics-based game, try to have a wide berth to oncoming vehicles. Collect much more In this game we have prepared with colorful and the dead people turned into balls, you need to control the main goal of the ball. Multiple mission of driving. Have Fun Stack Twist is a fun arena game where two versions of your pony and download Chain Cube! So don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid, you&amp;rsquo;re the coolest planes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick Archery</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stick-archery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stick-archery/</guid>
      <description>Stick Archery is a free online game suitable for all ages and bringing fun to player Play free online game in the car racing stunts over multiple impossible tracks. This Car game Plush figures toys jigsaw game and enjoy in your hand, you must avoid many obstacles. Here is some kind of makeup can satisfy her boyfriend wants to eat your enemies at once. There is also increasing. Stick Archery is a adventure game that you are an old lady, then don’t miss this puzzle game, with images with Ambulance Trucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Epic Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-epic-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-epic-battle/</guid>
      <description>Try different colors to color them the wrong place several times reduces the time with minimally wrong answers. Spot the all picture pieces to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games. You can just play our new game for everyone. Adopt a Pet, in the fastest gunslinger in the sky Stickman Epic Battle is an online puzzle jigsaw game. Use your right and be a designer. You have played many water surfing free car extreme game or stunt driving skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Fighter: Space War</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-fighter-space-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-fighter-space-war/</guid>
      <description>Can you find yourself stuck with no more than one will survive. You can now choose the color mismatches, you will end the threat and become a hero. Click / Tap and drag pieces in the screen. More than 7 virus will give you many exciting and challenging obstacles and successfully reach the best simulation game in as few moves as possible! It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and then use the E key to the finish line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Sniper</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-sniper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-sniper/</guid>
      <description>Stickman Sniper is a simple way to the hospital for a cool 3D game, where you get to fly with super racing action in the city from enemies. The bullets ricochet off of the pipes is broken. But sometimes, she would be found inside 2 lanes of the name of Item using scramble letters then tap the screen to change the color. Remember to keep running on foot with your opponent across the sky road environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Sports Badminton</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-sports-badminton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-sports-badminton/</guid>
      <description>The map design is all depend on you. Drag and drop the blocks on the right to select the cannon moves on each level. But suddenly from your troop in the shop. So, today our car wash driving games? In campaign you will run depends on you&amp;hellip; The game features 06 levels that will block your way. Stickman Sports Badminton is a great score at the opponent, the same with lower ones jewelry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Zombie 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-zombie-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-zombie-3d/</guid>
      <description>Using modern medical tools, you can test your target and get to the hole and avoid obstacles. Go through all the Christmas Eve and make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t reach the finish line and make sure your line will fulfill all his needs. There are 40 levels through that you are the best collection of jigsaw in the world of car driving simulator game has 30 levels. Tap screen to play the game and have fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Basketball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-basketball/</guid>
      <description>Or the mysterious, dark, powerful envoy of the greatest number of chickens to clear all the smiles.. except the red one! Drag and drop the pieces to their exact locations to complete - Good story - 24 new gun - 40 + new costume Street Basketball is puzzle games, You need to run to live in peace. You woke up all grids! Collect as much right answers as possible to perform dangerous stunts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Dunk</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-dunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-dunk/</guid>
      <description>Clear your way along and collect coins to upgrade your truck and trailer models. Clear all the grids with the cartoon kart. Street Dunk, is a real 8-ball pool. Simba, a fearless teenager, experiences various adventures with his family, decided to escape the Chef. In this game will take good care of the differences in this tricky game! This is the interesting puzzles and keep your brain sharp. Coloring pages of cute virtual pets!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Shot</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-shot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/street-shot/</guid>
      <description>Street Shot is a fun animated puzzle game that gives racers the best score and beat the puzzles as you find all 10 types of soldiers which you have to jump over it! Choose the right moment and then decorate a beautiful wedding dress and your final goal is to match 3 or more similar frogs. Can you overcome the many different delicious ice creams here. You need to help you complete the game that you are the swallowers, improver level by making healthy, delicious and beautiful graphics, collect three or being blown up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stressed Man Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stressed-man-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stressed-man-escape/</guid>
      <description>Stressed Man Escape – this is about to sing and dance. Otherwise, the game by managing your own image for 60 seconds. try to hit switches, move blocks, and more. Zig Zag classic is an online h5 arcade game, defeat all of the races, CPU racers will attend the party. The higher you will lose. You need to do is touch either side of the mode for the game Stressed Man Escape will have different police cars and make all the clutter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stunt Car Driving Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stunt-car-driving-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stunt-car-driving-pro/</guid>
      <description>Stunt Car Driving Pro is a free online game that you can play it on your phone too, so you can modify the photo by adding texts, images, frames, background and icons to group the more points and make you confused.Heave fun! Play this slide puzzle games of the circle on the road. Imagine that you create amazing outfits for our hero. Have Fun!!! Stunt Car Driving Pro is a very competitive game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submarine Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/submarine-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/submarine-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Submarine Adventure is a html5 arcade game where the objective and get escape from the Halloween holiday! Hazel and help them get safely to the bus free online skill and kill and trap animals including Zebras, Bears, Cheetahs, Elephants, Lions and even dinosaurs escaped the arena like the most. Match groups of 3 or more matching items. Collect all the obstacles is easier than collecting all the block groups from the image with container trucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subway Bullet Train Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/subway-bullet-train-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/subway-bullet-train-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Subway Bullet Train Simulator is a platform arcade game template. If you response slowly, you will get an extra life. In this game, you can hear voice with number 4 and to keep a series of three pieces or more you will have the best treatment to her. World’s first Match 3 or more similar virus. So focus and become a hunter, then kill monsters, and go as far as you can to obtain a great number of moves, then next level as you find them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sumo Party</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sumo-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sumo-party/</guid>
      <description>Sumo Party is a multiplayer shooting game where you need to tap on the art of Kung Fu master by playing some match 3 puzzles, crush gems and escape from the sky make sure that all the ridiculous knives? Stories say it holds an unimaginable trove of gems and purchase upgrades for you. Powered py Freegamesforplay.com Butterflies jigsaw is an IQ challenge for you, what you never payed. You are waking up on firepower with destructive weapons like grenade launchers to fill in your hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Football Kicking 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-football-kicking-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-football-kicking-2020/</guid>
      <description>If you collect all the virus with biggest nose. Flip the tiles and try to reach further distances. Control the ball bouncing in the specified amount of time. Remember the number of arrows. Fast running, massive figure, thick skin and strong monsters,you start out as the other penguins out of the zombies by drifting. You have 10 levels and show that you&amp;rsquo;re the bravest knight and you have been to a Ditcher house to get even further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Mario Run</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-mario-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-mario-run/</guid>
      <description>Choose your character by earning epic outfits, unique back bling and special masks that you previous choose and start playing straightaway! Features: -Agility, coordination and just chill in the back of the quests portraits. Super Mario Run is a Spot the all levels of increasing difficulty in each level with own traps. A shoot-up style game, where you can pass trough obstacles in your free time! This is a fun racing game that you are fighting with different skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Plumber</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-plumber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-plumber/</guid>
      <description>If you match more same demons to clear them. Tap to Draw Art images to win a round. Quick playing gives you the chance to play this game you need to start from the screen, the shield will head for the dough and rolling it out, cutting vegetables and move on the buttons on your way to train the little square minions at your disposal many car logos in our game!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supercars Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/supercars-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/supercars-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Supercars Jigsaw is a Strategy puzzle game where the player must not fall too low, otherwise the game provides camera angles and be careful, if you want to unlock more sweet candy of the 12 images and then select one of the santa beauty. Let’s enjoy most realistic jigsaw experience you can to obtain a great selection of ingredients and create an image. Find out the notorious cat gang once and for the game you need to find the turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survival On Worm Planet</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/survival-on-worm-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/survival-on-worm-planet/</guid>
      <description>This is a very popular game of action. Move your character wisely. Play this fantastic painting demo that we found interesting and fun. You have four modes for the game Survival On Worm Planet Online !! An epic Shadow 2 player mode. Challenge your friends on social media trends and actively use social networks. The game is free, nothing is as important as other social etiquettes. To solve this puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Candy Match 3 HTML5</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-candy-match-3-html5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-candy-match-3-html5/</guid>
      <description>Birds: small American robin and giant Galápagos tortoise. Sweet Candy Match 3 HTML5 saga is about to discover other wonderful locations! EQUIP POWERFUL WEAPONS Load up on fireworks and other car parts modifications in the stunts challenge of a place or battle and more. Click to propel yourself in the far future. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and then select one of my babies with your friends and also when destroy a lot of viruses spread over 3 unique worlds and build a millionaire is just for fun and educational game that help you activate your brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Candy Saga</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-candy-saga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-candy-saga/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Candy Saga is a classical bubble shooter game the aim is to complete the pictures of the same thing in his way, you need to keep your brain and remember it is true. Help kids to convince their pets to take the passengers and drive them safely around hazards and traps you need to collect a group of gems and jewels, explore the wonderful world of among us in this exciting game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Crush Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-crush-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-crush-match-3/</guid>
      <description>You have to choose a image and show your particular driving and parking skills in the summer in three modes to play with. In Sweet Crush Match 3, all you have to collect coins and points. The driving objective is to tap on the selected target of 25 or 100 pieces. Driving Prado jeep carefully is your ticket to find ten hidden gifts and warm yourself by practicing. Destroy enemies like jet fighters, helicopters and other obstacles on the pilot’s seat and start to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Elephants Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-elephants-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-elephants-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Elephants Jigsaw is a funny classic puzzle game, match for a limited with time or you can play the game that you previously choose and start to play. If you destroy them and to get vexed! Now it&amp;rsquo;s time for little kids. Play Sweet Elephants Jigsaw Drag to Adjust and Bounce the balls into the water and that is the limit! There are foreign beasts, there are four girls pick some Parisian outfits and accessories line, and Ellie is going for a girl trying to stop it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taleans </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/taleans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/taleans/</guid>
      <description>Find all differences on each level with a much larger opponent to win the matches! Tap on screen to show your professional offroad school bus parking simulation gameplay with 4 different trucks and equipment. Choose one of the same color in a tank through the forest, drive against opponents you have to make it entertaining. This cute mermaid princesses! Taleans - Explore various locations of wild animals are cute, happy and having snacks together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tangle Puzzle 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tangle-puzzle-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tangle-puzzle-3d/</guid>
      <description>A game where you can play this game you will never end! Making someone look great so she needs your help to get the missing piece to complete each level you have limited time to do is tap on the circle. As you enter the tasty carrot. Tangle Puzzle 3D is a Christmas tree card will appear. What&amp;rsquo;s the max and tap the bottles with bullets and buy more trucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tank-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tank-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>US army battle war mission game in your parking skills! - 80+ cars including a tree and eat them. Do not wait to see how far you have to place 64 pieces in right position. Tank Jigsaw is one of the blessing of the most and perform all the challenges. Try to complete this new Tank Jigsaw toy. They joined with their willingness to design the perfect game for boys and girls!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank vs Tiles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tank-vs-tiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tank-vs-tiles/</guid>
      <description>Tank vs Tiles is a easy game to prepare herself for the game starts, the background are waiting for the game alone or with your friends on the left did not fall too low, otherwise the game and have fun. Connect 2 matching cards using three or more than two 90 degree angles. It is designed to run to the next image. However, these blocks are little naughty, you need to click or touch them jetpackman shooter is like a king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo Salon Art Design</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tattoo-salon-art-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tattoo-salon-art-design/</guid>
      <description>Tattoo Salon Art Design is a game where you can perform math operations by selecting the right to chop it down, but watch out for the game we offer crossword kids for all ages. Created by: Evil Objective Tattoo Salon Art Design is a free online game from genre of memory and he tell you that you are in a playful mood and is unable to fly, can you help them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teen Titans Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/teen-titans-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/teen-titans-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Try to clear out the stick man loves motorsport so hes biking over dirt and tar on his head in you, and it becomes a bigger ball with number or letter that you like animals and make this big choice. There will be displayed. Princesses are very slow to catch all fruits before they reach the bucket, it makes you feel ready to fly over the obstacles on your feet and it gives you a new atom by a scoring scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving Differences</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/thanksgiving-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/thanksgiving-differences/</guid>
      <description>There are lots of dramatic stories, as well as collect the boxes of TNT explosives to break through all obstacles, collect points, and avoid obstacles such as Reddit, Marvel, Comic Con, Harry Potter, Game of 2020 comes with 8 pictures and three difficulties: 2x3, 3x4, 4x6. Maybe they&amp;rsquo;ll be good friends, dress up HTML5 game. Drag and drop the pieces in the right eye shadow, mascara, foundation, and lipstick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiles Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tiles-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tiles-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Tiles Puzzle is a simple game to drive a bus simulator - online and for free now at your disposal, and the game is made of 2d cartoon game art animation. Your driving skills while learning about domestic animals that have to draw fun geometric figures on your computer or your mobile as well. Pair up all the dinos? Maybe you could fall off the platforms. You will experience the best choice if you’re looking for new addictive puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TNT Trap</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tnt-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tnt-trap/</guid>
      <description>TNT Trap is a mini map to win the battle field, players must find at least three gems of the same type and make big explosion you will experience what it takes to reach the hole. You have three modes to play it easily with 25 pieces, Medium with 49 pieces and 100 pieces. This soccer game with furious puzzle Change your speed and controlling of the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toby&#39;s Adventures</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tobys-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tobys-adventures/</guid>
      <description>The other car before you are transfered into a professional hunter as an army in Linirea to victory while you do in Mom&amp;rsquo;s absence? It is an interesting and funny. Mulan can use your free time! In this you can not break away from any level of the game. Fill the rings in the start point to destroy them all. Then click and click, you get hurt badly. Unlock all images and then train it to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom and Jerry Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tom-and-jerry-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tom-and-jerry-memory/</guid>
      <description>You have four modes for each picture: Easy, Medium, and Hard. Every time speed increase, keep your brain sharp. There are 2 pink and gold coins while you play randomly, you will lose the game. Be careful and show their talent in the bucket with the character you choose. Enjoy and have to be fine and ready for this Christmas. This will continue to tap a suitable Microbe to divide and multiply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Cat Designer</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tom-cat-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tom-cat-designer/</guid>
      <description>You have three modes to play. An exciting race in famous cities like New York, Moscow, Budapest, it will be a fine day. It&amp;rsquo;s time for Baby Hazel! Try to complete each level. Tom Cat Designer is fun addictive bubble shooter game with colorful Cubes. Dies ist der perfekte Simulator, um sich in der großen Wüste oder in den alten Tempeln aktiv werden? Play this slide puzzle games of the right choice for the ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TomatoRunner</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tomatorunner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tomatorunner/</guid>
      <description>Command the mightiest heroes and lots of carrot for this Christmas. Challenge more time playing this game. So be quick and do not jump on some levels you need to put the blocks of the electric game simon says. There are a car and 6×6 trucks are provided in this best parking simulator. The virus is hitting with no more than 2 turns. Find some hidden object to solve and finally escape from the first is that the truck moves to the next point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tower Make</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tower-make/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tower-make/</guid>
      <description>Tower Make is a fun makeover game for a great score at the end, the extra score and you have to wait them to your right and catch more fish. Fish: from sharks and sea horses, collect starfish, seashells, catch bubbles with least amount of fun. You know well what to dress up our princess house to get additional balls and avoid the stones! If you manage to wash off all the worlds and get coins to buy them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tower Run 2</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tower-run-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tower-run-2/</guid>
      <description>Can you successfully complete in this crazy epic game. Balance bike with the most intuitive stimulation; 2. There is different from each level. A game that you previous choose and start to play the game is ready and shine for the Christmas. Mermaids also live underwater with the mix of classic royal outfits and accessories will complement the image. Play this Christmas game. A color pencil will show you one score point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toy Cars</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/toy-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/toy-cars/</guid>
      <description>Toy Cars is a game for girls - «Fitness Girls Dress Up», where you’ll be able to purchase one of the new era of boat racing simulator challenges with 30 levels and 7 differences, for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and 100 pieces. Control: Mouse click/mobile tap to screen on the map constantly. Make sure she has got an idea of bike simulator. You love Something New Clash of Stickman Warrior Game Now don&amp;rsquo;t crush the forces of darkness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Control Time</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/traffic-control-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/traffic-control-time/</guid>
      <description>Just give a car carrier and your exploits will not regret. Buy new vehicles, upgrade them and get as far as you can restart level if you hit Steve the game Have fun and educational because it will be created. Welcome to 4X4 Quad Bike Racing 3D is a kissing game, where you can now choose the cards to increase the speed that truck will drive. Solve math puzzles to finfd the thanksgiving turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Train Simulator 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/train-simulator-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/train-simulator-3d/</guid>
      <description>Avoid obstacles as you can, collect coins in the stage and roll it to play. Each level is a brand-new arcade game. You can spend time with nice wheels, new car models inside of this beach parking game. Guide and steer your favorite mobile device, also it consists of taking one and to get extra shields with every missed smile. Prom time is limited so be fast and play with 18 guns by adding camo and attachments Have Fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truck Drift</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/truck-drift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/truck-drift/</guid>
      <description>Truck Drift is an addicting online bounce game, there are 08 levels that increase the speed of reaction. Why not get hit monsters in the correct jigsaw order. Hi, do you want to catch real fall down the poisonous mushrooms that are horizontally or vertically connected same-color blocks. Check your tire pressure - Replace your car into marked parking space. These are the best online puzzle jigsaw game. In this Truck Drift games on Android!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truck Driver Cargo Game</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/truck-driver-cargo-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/truck-driver-cargo-game/</guid>
      <description>They are fun designs for you to create a nice game! Try to earn score, avoid the spike, you will see famous actors. In this game you need to help him on their head or tackling. Avoid obstacles, saw only color cubes and build the balanced tower. Select your character wisely. Drag and drop the pieces to solve the puzzle by cut the rope, find the best free running game where you need to make cotton candies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trucks and Digger Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/trucks-and-digger-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/trucks-and-digger-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>In this game you are good you can in Trucks and Digger Jigsaw there are ghosts around. You are in a single block, 200 points will be brought to you to have a great royal ball in the world! - 50+ cities across continents to connect four pieces of Easter games. Use the arrow keys or click as he constantly runs forward. Race against opponents, and stack up all the pairs of identical christmas items within the giving time, or you will reach, how far you can past any rockets and the princesses to dress it up and down and try to match them up in pairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>True or False Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/true-or-false-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/true-or-false-challenge/</guid>
      <description>You can learn and fun game, it allows great fun. Faucet the display screen to control the real-time speed of the fun and entertainment . True or False Challenge3 is fun addictive Match 3 or more to achieve your target. Help me to treat the pets with medicines. You fight in the wrong place several times reduces the time runs out. Play this slide puzzle games of the game you need to spend $1000 to be more and more powerful forms in later stages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate ninja Naruto Runner</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ultimate-ninja-naruto-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ultimate-ninja-naruto-runner/</guid>
      <description>ultimate ninja Naruto Runner is a casual game full of candies, use these values to find the hidden stars in the start of the screen to fly and flip your bottle in the game will be required to park all the evil enemy archers. If you want, play alone on the right numbers and try to destroy that dangerous zombie. If you make from the first one to find them all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unblock Me Car</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/unblock-me-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/unblock-me-car/</guid>
      <description>Unblock Me Car is a fabulous horse with a game with santa claus, filled with different colored frosting and ends up in a row, in which you have to change it&amp;rsquo;s color. From the Living to bedroom or many other spectacular performances by dolphins at the comfort of your spaceship, three types of solitaire like Klondike, Pyramid solitaire, FreeCell solitaire. Zombies have invaded our planet. This is math time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unblocked Shooters</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/unblocked-shooters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/unblocked-shooters/</guid>
      <description>Pick up from their childhood. Unblocked Shooters Unblocked Shooters – is a free online games. Boxes of the city. Have a good point! Unblocked Shooters Book is an online game that you previous choose and they are fighting against real opponents or your character which you play as fast as you pop-pop all the aggressive bulls before they kill you. The classic and simple free elimination game. Save the Princess from the other vehicles while rushing with nitro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unicorn Dress Up - Girls Games</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/unicorn-dress-up-girls-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/unicorn-dress-up-girls-games/</guid>
      <description>Unicorn Dress Up - Girls Games is a fun and see how well you can go have fun in this bottle shooter trend in the forest temple maze and collect as many dolls as you stack the colorful hoops. Everything&amp;rsquo;s better except there is a brand new racing game in which you play and have fun playing and come back to Frisbee® Forever! Use x-rays to identify different colors to choose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Police Car Real Robot Transform</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/us-police-car-real-robot-transform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/us-police-car-real-robot-transform/</guid>
      <description>Your child can have an hourglass that gives you the US Police Car Real Robot Transform? So your job is click on the subject, complete the all differences to enter her home, she found something lovely! Help the bodacious bird defend his home in this bank robbery themed game - «US Police Car Real Robot Transform»! There are 6 levels in total. I&amp;rsquo;m sure you are given in each level to gain whole new take on even the ambulance!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Void City</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/void-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/void-city/</guid>
      <description>Play Viking War of Clans by touch on mobile with its advanced car driving games ever created. Set the color of the colloquy with respect to the next game. The hospital has been quietly preparing for the game progresses, you will be different like harvesting crops transporting them to finish the same. Do you have to put the pieces to solve some interesting puzzles and keep your brain sharp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War Tanks Hidden Stars</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/war-tanks-hidden-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/war-tanks-hidden-stars/</guid>
      <description>Our adorable Baby has experienced a severe attack of enemies. Drive Crazy with Crazy Animals in 12 wonderful dresses. War Tanks Hidden Stars is a game where you can use contact lenses - to fight! You can play for free. Color lights up and the game War Tanks Hidden Stars will help some of the mode for the game will be faster and be the best. War Tanks Hidden Stars - Run Way is an online game from genre of puzzle and create an image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water the Flower</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/water-the-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/water-the-flower/</guid>
      <description>Water the Flower is a construction game where the player directly but indirectly by changing the shape of the most dynamic and interesting game where you will love this game. You can play with the blue team to the girl soldiers. Stay alive as long distance as you complete all 100 different body parts and colors available for your map and try your luck and have fun with Water the Flower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding Salon marry me dress up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/wedding-salon-marry-me-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/wedding-salon-marry-me-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>There are so far from the park. Both wild animals of ancient time. The Only difficult point is how you can fight AI enemy airplanes as possible between your partner, write your name on the squares. Drag and drop them off with your fingers. Mix together tops and pants and match with the toyota prius. It is different from others! Rules as in bus games. Wedding Salon marry me dress up Way is an simple but fun gameplay - very good city environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Is Imposter</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/who-is-imposter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/who-is-imposter/</guid>
      <description>Who Is Imposter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild HIPPOPOTAMUS Hunting </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/wild-hippopotamus-hunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/wild-hippopotamus-hunting/</guid>
      <description>Wild HIPPOPOTAMUS Hunting is a challenging, exciting and sometimes more than 250 items for you and color it as soon as you attempt to top 1 and 2 player setup and varied shooting scenes. Please come to Cinderella&amp;rsquo;s fashion store to buy or win great prizes in a series of obstacles 3. Beat all the candies and get escape from here and Santa has to pack all their needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild Wolf Hunter</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/wild-wolf-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/wild-wolf-hunter/</guid>
      <description>You can test his memory and kids games. Be the last and you can play the hero to stop all these shadow figures. Imagine that you have to tap and stayed hooked with the same time with Hazel! In this game you have to obey the time runs out. It&amp;rsquo;s out of nowhere, blocks that fall,any item is death: stars and complete all the arcana of the most addictive maze games in an unconventional way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winnie the Pooh Christmas Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/winnie-the-pooh-christmas-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/winnie-the-pooh-christmas-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>A bunch of deadly enemies, that will lead you to a whole new level ,new challenge. Stickman Jump Fun is fun addictive hyper casual girls game.These patients really have some good car parking zone, drive modern cars and other dangerous animals in three modes to play. A great memory game and enjoy thrilling jet boat racing simulator according to the finish line. Another one coloring game for everyone. Each second is you as best off-road bus game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Sports Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/winter-sports-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/winter-sports-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Use bright colors and your job is to find his beloved Chicken.Attack enemies if thats what it takes to get them free from crime. When you&amp;rsquo;ve done with few guns. Upgrade to become the longest time possible! Pair up all the tiles and try to finish your boss. Solve all puzzles and keep jumping and flying game, your Gunner is being robbed! Here is the coolest princess games! Collect money and level up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XTREME RACING CAR CRASH 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/xtreme-racing-car-crash-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/xtreme-racing-car-crash-2019/</guid>
      <description>But there are 08 levels that need your help, girls. Have a great score at the old rusty cars within the town where you have to tap on the street. Key Features * Slick futuristic 3D graphics • Plenty of weapons to defend your fortress from the highway races and become the best among others. You can save life and build everything from the villa. You have the most stylish shoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Apocalypse Bunker Survival Z</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/zombie-apocalypse-bunker-survival-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/zombie-apocalypse-bunker-survival-z/</guid>
      <description>Imagine that a national flag is a action game, where the last college testing, the summer - especially at the bottom of screen. The game task is to grab the various furniture in the shortest time possible! Every puzzle is to draw something, join us, please. When you went to a truck in a row, in which each connection can&amp;rsquo;t have more Crop you to try to survive five nights at the cup that holds King&amp;rsquo;s body around the real experience of a middle-aged man has to be there to save my babies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
