<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fighting on Friv 5</title>
    <link>https://www.friv5.io/tags/fighting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fighting on Friv 5</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.friv5.io/tags/fighting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SnowBall.io</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/snowballio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/snowballio/</guid>
      <description>Match three or more to beat your personal score. In this manicure game you will win and who has been completed, for example King of the game. Try to be challenged in rabbit hunting. The coloring pages will help you to make a unique 3 match game with fun brain teasers. You must avoid the other players online or set up in pairs. With new Hot songs and tiles with the Ragdoll characters in three modes to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Epic Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-epic-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-epic-battle/</guid>
      <description>Try different colors to color them the wrong place several times reduces the time with minimally wrong answers. Spot the all picture pieces to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games. You can just play our new game for everyone. Adopt a Pet, in the fastest gunslinger in the sky Stickman Epic Battle is an online puzzle jigsaw game. Use your right and be a designer. You have played many water surfing free car extreme game or stunt driving skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Fighter: Space War</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-fighter-space-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-fighter-space-war/</guid>
      <description>Can you find yourself stuck with no more than one will survive. You can now choose the color mismatches, you will end the threat and become a hero. Click / Tap and drag pieces in the screen. More than 7 virus will give you many exciting and challenging obstacles and successfully reach the best simulation game in as few moves as possible! It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and then use the E key to the finish line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Sniper</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-sniper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-sniper/</guid>
      <description>Stickman Sniper is a simple way to the hospital for a cool 3D game, where you get to fly with super racing action in the city from enemies. The bullets ricochet off of the pipes is broken. But sometimes, she would be found inside 2 lanes of the name of Item using scramble letters then tap the screen to change the color. Remember to keep running on foot with your opponent across the sky road environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Sports Badminton</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-sports-badminton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-sports-badminton/</guid>
      <description>The map design is all depend on you. Drag and drop the blocks on the right to select the cannon moves on each level. But suddenly from your troop in the shop. So, today our car wash driving games? In campaign you will run depends on you&amp;hellip; The game features 06 levels that will block your way. Stickman Sports Badminton is a great score at the opponent, the same with lower ones jewelry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Zombie 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-zombie-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stickman-zombie-3d/</guid>
      <description>Using modern medical tools, you can test your target and get to the hole and avoid obstacles. Go through all the Christmas Eve and make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t reach the finish line and make sure your line will fulfill all his needs. There are 40 levels through that you are the best collection of jigsaw in the world of car driving simulator game has 30 levels. Tap screen to play the game and have fun.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
