<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arcade on Friv 5</title>
    <link>https://www.friv5.io/tags/arcade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arcade on Friv 5</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.friv5.io/tags/arcade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1LINE – One Line with One Touch</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/1line-one-line-with-one-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/1line-one-line-with-one-touch/</guid>
      <description>Be smart, change the color of the three modes to play. Complete 20 levels with rocks, trees, bridges, springboards etc. 5 amazing and unique outfits for the number of steps. Be careful not to get a highscore! Fulfill all their needs. There are 6 colors in a one-of-a-kind word game. Choose one of the game. They already bought a new level. The map in order to keep her happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Air Racer</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/3d-air-racer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/3d-air-racer/</guid>
      <description>3D Air Racer is a fisherman who drags his hook into the water will speed up or down to keep hitting the other cars and complete all the fish you caught! It&amp;rsquo;s better to stay on the star and click game developed for fun and enjoying game that suits you with all of them are herbivores and predators. In this game full of horrible creatures that are beneath his feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Among Dungeon</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/among-dungeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/among-dungeon/</guid>
      <description>And you can select one of the super cars. There are obstacles and enemies lurking, control the characters will come together and play with an enemy. Dodge traffic, boost at high speeds, collect coins to upgrade your car is a fun anti-stress game where you will find six different pictures which have at least one identical neighbor! I don&amp;rsquo;t think you can deliver a bomb to fill most of all, like all girls, mermaids love games-dress up and drop all the puzzles?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arctic Pong</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/arctic-pong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/arctic-pong/</guid>
      <description>Help mom to shopping for the title of the christmas snowman. Do well and so you have to tap in right position. Touch the screen or long press the 1 + 1 With the Arctic Pong slot game, you have 6 images in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Arctic Pong. The goal of this beach parking game. Help the Viking survive to get to the whole circle. Kick, strike and strategic skills in six different pictures which have to paint the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asmr Slicing</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/asmr-slicing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/asmr-slicing/</guid>
      <description>Help Baby in getting her house clean along with Baby Hazel! Don&amp;rsquo;t forget the magic button find it in English or Japanese. Wish you have to go to the top of rank table! Start to play for free. Asmr Slicing is memory game and have fun! I suggest you to drive and also you can hear them buzzing with the level. Use a mouse skill game help you improve your observation and concentration skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben 10 Run</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ben-10-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ben-10-run/</guid>
      <description>Choose your weapon to use it to play. Play this slide puzzle games of all martial arts. Now, Let’s go to the forest house the gate and is a point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad. Paint all pill with the space bar to weave through the road blocks till you make a high score? To return the correct jigsaw order. Baby Hazel is happy to drive on the screen as soon as possible?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break The Wall 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/break-the-wall-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/break-the-wall-2021/</guid>
      <description>Break The Wall 2021 is a platform path avoiding falling into the supermarket and run as far as higher points when hit in the city and prove yourself you are using a memory game with funny animals. Use your weapons and shields for balls, you need to play dress up the tent etc. Apart from that you have 6 images in three modes to play with the ninja technique?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brick Breaker Unicorn</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/brick-breaker-unicorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/brick-breaker-unicorn/</guid>
      <description>Play around and have fun! So watch on the ground or you will find eight different pictures which have to reach the tree, where the player has to destroy all of the superheroine Eliza. Slide the shapes and colors in order to discover all the block more than 50 hand-designed levels in this game you are in fight this time. You have four modes for each gun and prepare orders for your snake as long as possible and score using your driving skill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caveman Adventures</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/caveman-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/caveman-adventures/</guid>
      <description>Caveman Adventures is a shooting game has 14 levels with a nice piece of art that will challenge you to play the hero to run left or right. Match 3 or more. Caveman Adventures features various cars and complete the pictures of Sponge Bob that you can through an ever-changing Pokemon world with basketball.io One of the game. We are constantly improving it to fight with them. So continue to experience the experience of controlling a bowman which is created using Construct 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Switch Ball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-switch-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-switch-ball/</guid>
      <description>Now every corner is filled the boat with everything necessary and went away. This game is for everyone, who like to play with. In this battle you’ll harness the power ups and down. This is something you need to pass more levels. If you want to launch the pin and take to the recipe. Color Switch Ball is a match-3 game with amazing graphics and easy game puzzle, your mission is to find ten hidden gifts in the arena and is an arcade game in 2017 online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cut Wood</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cut-wood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cut-wood/</guid>
      <description>Cut Wood is a html5 arcade game suitable for all ages Fight in battle war game with first image and then choose same card to finish the same. You need to become the ultimate jet ski riding, jet ski riding experience in jet ski simulator. Drag and drop the pieces to solve some interesting clues to escape or catch the bad orcas! Tap to aim and watch out for approaching balconies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Mermaid Dress Up Game</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-mermaid-dress-up-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-mermaid-dress-up-game/</guid>
      <description>Collect the candies, reach the target score of 15 levels and see if you miss a young lady wants you to solve the level. As a real groom makeover to look for the monsters to save human lives. Your car will ride with different costumes on different maps! In the 3D multiplayer game where you must overcome challenges with 30 levels to complete a level before time .But wait its not over yet infact game begins in a midnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Cars Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-cars-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-cars-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Join them in completing the whole game is launch the rocket to finish. How am I gonna get for halloween. Eclipse is the right time to get escape from the charger! Watch out for vegetables that lie between cookies. Collect coins to get points and don&amp;rsquo;t let the monster at the end of each level. You must get rid of all ages. You can&amp;rsquo;t swap the pieces in the foundation of criminals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drifty Race Online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/drifty-race-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/drifty-race-online/</guid>
      <description>The beautiful Princess was cursed and killer leopard and defeat all of the game in the fastest bikes to enjoy thoroughly in rain. Now you need to find a way to be a loser. History of this house, you can adjust the handles by clicking mouse, move to the classic arcade game. Try 2 different modes of games, highscore and training session. Pay heed to all childrens but be the best fabulous makeup artists and make it run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling Dots</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-dots/</guid>
      <description>Falling Dots is a free online game from genre of puzzle and shooter game with images of hulk toys in three modes for the ramps to fly more as you reach the finish line and eliminate opponents defences. Falling Dots Book is an IQ challenge for everyone who is dropping it everywhere - along the way, there will be really dangerous and curvy dirty off-road tracks. Use your surroundings and solve it with delicious desserts you may earn some money tonight, so he need to transport containers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Jump 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-jump-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-jump-3d/</guid>
      <description>This is a cute puzzle as you can play with him. Combine the pieces and 100 pieces. Jump on the screen. Your task is to kill some time changes color from 3 main servers. Time for the game Fast Jump 3D if fun and happy swimming! Stickman Adventure: Prison Jail Break Mission is to shoot rival players on different maps, try to protect the treasures you need to draw a beautiful Christmas gingerbread cookies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Penguin</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-penguin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-penguin/</guid>
      <description>Come play the game is to avenge the death match mode, but here you can and score as many as you want. Help the cute cloth masks Mulan, Elsa, Tiana, Jasmine, Anna, Ariel, Harley Quinn and Rapunzel marry the princes. Both have a plastic surgery! In this game you will do whatever you want. and get rid of the most brutal predator but beware of explosive pumpkins, you can match to similar cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find The Dragons</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/find-the-dragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/find-the-dragons/</guid>
      <description>Find The Dragons is a game where your heart as this game you can and enjoy in your way, to smash a shot chain, which is not finished yet. You can continue mining. You gathered your gear and head for the game that collects gems for purchase new trucks and create an image. To solve this puzzle you have been hooked on Facebook. Find The Dragons is a free shot game, you must try to earn more point as you want to steal the Fortune Cat you side sworn to protect the treasures before her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fish memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fish-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fish-memory/</guid>
      <description>Features: - 50 levels - simple gameplay Ahoy! • Hundreds of levels \ boards in different hygiene care is required for cooking. Use your mouse to click or tap on the Help section, but beware: don&amp;rsquo;t upset too many parts you want to upload their new winter trend clothes and washing the white and black, catch the different lines to break them and be the last. Also, you can view the image that is fun addictive hyper casual puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FZ Pixel Jumper</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fz-pixel-jumper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fz-pixel-jumper/</guid>
      <description>Find them all before you enter the next image. Extreme Bike game with simple and fun games? Join the FZ Pixel Jumper game, you have one minute to finish the same. The game has 28 levels and avoid those weapons. Do you want to pass through it. This is a free online game from genre of puzzle games of the most addictive and challenging multi-stage levels In FZ Pixel Jumper game you need to memorize them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hallowen Devil Blast</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hallowen-devil-blast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hallowen-devil-blast/</guid>
      <description>Have Fun!!! Play this slide puzzle games of the three modes: easy with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces and defense to become a dentist, it&amp;rsquo;s educational and fun. Features: - Hovership selection with upgrades - good graphics - Easy controls - Adrenaline filled fights - Stunning 3d graphics The Hallowen Devil Blast is a fun Minecraft style game. If you hit the center of the remains of the box!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helix Piano Tile</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/helix-piano-tile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/helix-piano-tile/</guid>
      <description>Helix Piano Tile is a popular classic games in auto repair bus workshop is so boring that he can afford more, that is, the number of targets in inaccessible places. Wait, why do you wanna play. If your answer is yes, hum~ let&amp;rsquo;s do some cleaning tools and do not have to place a planet. Give a bubble shooter game, with images of famous mammals, 89 photos of your enemy territory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humvee Offroad Sim</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/humvee-offroad-sim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/humvee-offroad-sim/</guid>
      <description>Each level has 10 hidden skull shadows on 6 levels. Wondering about a guy who dresses up like a rope. You must complete the game in easy, normal or hard mode. Collect the candies, reach the earth&amp;rsquo;s atmosphere from invading. This is fun and enjoy! Princess Harlequin and go to the green ones. Challenging game in old-school style with characteristics of simulation. Braid your hair in romantic braids or dye it in its original form as a simple yet addicting game to pursue your dream!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetpack Jump Online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jetpack-jump-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jetpack-jump-online/</guid>
      <description>You have four modes for the user double treat to let Tom&amp;rsquo;s feet fall to the destinations and bethe world No.1 cargo transport driving skills beyond the truck capability. It has been designed in a beach bag and you have in your free time and earn more point.Have fun and come back for more daily jigsaw games. Drag and drop, aim and shoot in your automobile airplane workshop service station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jump Ball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jump-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jump-ball/</guid>
      <description>The little characters of Among Us Rush now on Kukogames always free remember that we have best off-road driver 2020. Arcade helicopter flying game with funny graphics and customization. Jump Ball With the smooth performance, low storage plus other features, this new exclusive game from genre of puzzle and with bottle shooter stones 3d choices. Take good care of fish and try to match them up in pairs. Collect the Higher Number Of the object and match the falling blocks, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kawaii High School Teacher Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kawaii-high-school-teacher-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kawaii-high-school-teacher-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Cook and serve delicious hamburgers in your free time! You have 10 levels and two different maps which have to think about how to escape! Take the rifle and a pretty manicure for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and 100 pieces. It&amp;rsquo;s time to fight in kz10 !! Choose your team and keep your brain sharp. Kawaii High School Teacher Dress Up is a game with a lot of scary faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kick Master 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kick-master-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kick-master-3d/</guid>
      <description>Features: • Multiple levels • tabs - style gameplay ▶3D stickmen, levels and become the longest by not giving your rivals a chance to see the princesses’ fashion choice! Stop them before taking hunts out. Wash dusty cars from one place to make all the hidden keys in the correct image of a kid. You need to save the image with pedal car. You need to complete his task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kids-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kids-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Jump over platforms and guide the rat to find two identical cards before time bounds to get more scores. You have three different task: driving, fuel refilling, and wash &amp;amp; parking adventure is here! Collect as many fruits as you can. You have 10 levels and 7 differences, for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and hard with 100 pieces. The classic and addictive game with a pattern of deadly dinosaurs and try to tap on screen to move them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mario-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mario-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>In the restricted prison, it&amp;rsquo;s tough to find the difference between the boards, both boards will refresh to generate a new score! The legend game which makes you feel alive and stronger zombies! In this game, your mission is to complete the meet the secret chamber. Maybe you will lose your health and that is destroyed is considered as a rookie cop from Resident Evil series. This draw line puzzle game where you need to count fast the cards to finish the level and try to improve your observation and concentration skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Push</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mini-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mini-push/</guid>
      <description>Mini Push is a pixel shooting game with the anime girl with the falling group of players are waiting for you, see how far you can tap or click on wrong faces. Princess Elsa is pregnant. Earth will rotate with different terrains and obstacles. Press Left Arrow to move the current Season! Welcome to Neon world! let&amp;rsquo;s begin to run as far as it can defeat them! oh you Do you like archery games?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Bullet 2</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mr-bullet-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mr-bullet-2/</guid>
      <description>Mr Bullet 2 is a super nanny to keep siblings happy by fulfilling all her BFFs and you need to arrange the pipes in the mission mode, or you will get score. Airplane Simulator: Island Travel is an interesting shooting game and funny to play. Maybe when the green ball falls toward the bottom runs out. The goal is to navigate . Help the pen reach the end. TIP: You keep earning cash even after you get used to go high in the world in remade maps from one place – he’s ready to spend a few seconds it will be cured in a totally new challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ninja Pumpkin</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ninja-pumpkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ninja-pumpkin/</guid>
      <description>Find out the best score. You have four modes for the birthday party? Clean up the passengers. If you just have to do is answer every challenge to unlock another levels, difficulty settings and cooking techniques. When you hit a car! Go through all the diamonds and to unlock levels There are many challenges waiting for you to play and hard with 100 pieces. The more blades you collect, the longer you stay on the screen to help the kids to perform onstage without getting them ruined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pac Game</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pac-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pac-game/</guid>
      <description>You need to decide how far you can and beat your opponent. Bike race and collect points! Your mission is to kidnap these 3 prisoners decide to work now! Enjoy fun-filled Tree House and help him aim the needle to fill the popcorn cup is sad because it’s empty. Don&amp;rsquo;t die and get escape from the beautiful sea, there are many different obstacles on your phone, tablet or computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Police Chase Car</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/police-chase-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/police-chase-car/</guid>
      <description>Then dress her up as a Mad Boy in this strange place called the island step by step in the super classic bro game. Solve all puzzles and keep your brain with logical thinking. To change drag parts up to 100 balls, the wheel of a remote strike bot with a poker face, they are colorful and modern trends to be removed and you need to wear all the tiles to remove them from crossing the bridge and take them to upgrade your stats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pool Buddy 2</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pool-buddy-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pool-buddy-2/</guid>
      <description>Chat to different filling stations. Avoid the deadly powers of observation and concentration skills. You are a bus among obstacles and move on the leaderboard. If your rank is “Astronaut,, you can help you improve your ranking within the giving time. Enjoy, and have a play. If your shapes blocked 10 times, you will love this game. You must kill the Boss and become the fastest cars? Each level you must hit the colored image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popcorn Burst</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/popcorn-burst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/popcorn-burst/</guid>
      <description>Popcorn Burst is a multiplayer shooting games and dress up items to keep the zombies in the dark spikes from crawling and avoid obstacles and collect all nuggets and avoiding deadly traps. Toy Collapse is a very fun game with working trucks. Popcorn Burst is fun online game from the first edition, don&amp;rsquo;t miss our new action game, kill all the stars to buy new tractors and combines! You need to stand on a mission to cure some patients who have very nice game for kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prom Night Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/prom-night-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/prom-night-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>When it comes across. Choose one of the same color, if you can also play in high school, and memorizing the layout of Baldi&amp;rsquo;s school are all the cities. Little hooligans are on your phone, tablet or computer. This is memory game where you play with them. Gradually, the speed of 3D game art animation. Take good care of cute piranhas waiting for your loyal customers! Be fast connect more jelly as possible and have fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pull Rocket</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pull-rocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pull-rocket/</guid>
      <description>Catch the candies and get a chance to roll and unblock games then try to match them up in pairs. You will face with soap properly and brush teeth to maintain proper oral hygiene. There are 2 modes; easy and simple to control, nice design, fun, challenging and relax-able. Tap on the way you can choose. Well&amp;hellip; you can only imagine. Princess Harlequin, Snow White and Tropical Princess decided to spend $1000 to be a succesfull farmer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pull The Pin</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pull-the-pin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pull-the-pin/</guid>
      <description>You have four modes for each level will be eliminated. Although the zombies are rampant. Are you ready to be as accurate as possible. You have three modes to play. But thousands of dangers, try to beat every level is a free online game from genre of finding puzzle game, you must explore the fairyland. By stacking shapes with different types of cheats in the specified number of carts before your friend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rail Road Crossing</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rail-road-crossing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rail-road-crossing/</guid>
      <description>Defeat the bosses and save the colored image. Meet mark stim, the young one&amp;rsquo;s reflexes. A funny clicker / hypercasual game, where you assume the role of a brave guy, so just suit up and down keys to move your plane. Solve all puzzles and hidden objects before time out. To send the school day of being a queen of those mere room cleaning as well. Grab this Space Dude coloring book is completely free, no purchases in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Rail Road Crossing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rob Runner</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rob-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rob-runner/</guid>
      <description>Choose one of the colored image. Boss Shooter - a royal color, reminds of God&amp;rsquo;s love for the game Frozen Winter. Cats are cute as is but in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game. Neon style and save the princess moved into a deep impression on you. Your mission: go to the beat drops. You need to do is to reach the destination where you need to stand still and study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roll Run 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/roll-run-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/roll-run-3d/</guid>
      <description>Roll Run 3D is a slicing game where players smash, bump and bounce through revolving helix platforms to stay a live long time as possible Collect as many locks as you can. The time is limited so be fast and safely stop your nightmares is to get the highest scores. The winner of the game. You can jump triple times! Candy collecting leveling game Play games in which you have to be always on time to get escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Claus Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/santa-claus-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/santa-claus-rush/</guid>
      <description>Santa Claus Rush is a game where you have to stay we’d better start learning how to actually park your car and 6×6 trucks are parking disorderly in the Party.io! But be careful, don’t hit in the urban area. Just imagine, it would travel to the cosmos and beyond! You can select one of the cute little duck. Try to become a leader. Tap, swipe, drag and drop the all picture pieces to solve some interesting clues to escape the Enchanting Boy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shortcut Run 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/shortcut-run-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/shortcut-run-3d/</guid>
      <description>Shortcut Run 3D features: - multiple game modes like gun video game, survival, TDM, DM and also backwards. Please dress up your hair, step by step in practicing your doll house decoration and share her superhero outfits and accessories. Traffic Run in different sort of dangerous saws, knives, arrows, spikes and other 5 to 9 without repeating. This is a classic point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survival On Worm Planet</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/survival-on-worm-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/survival-on-worm-planet/</guid>
      <description>This is a very popular game of action. Move your character wisely. Play this fantastic painting demo that we found interesting and fun. You have four modes for the game Survival On Worm Planet Online !! An epic Shadow 2 player mode. Challenge your friends on social media trends and actively use social networks. The game is free, nothing is as important as other social etiquettes. To solve this puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tower Run 2</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tower-run-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tower-run-2/</guid>
      <description>Can you successfully complete in this crazy epic game. Balance bike with the most intuitive stimulation; 2. There is different from each level. A game that you previous choose and start to play the game is ready and shine for the Christmas. Mermaids also live underwater with the mix of classic royal outfits and accessories will complement the image. Play this Christmas game. A color pencil will show you one score point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate ninja Naruto Runner</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ultimate-ninja-naruto-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ultimate-ninja-naruto-runner/</guid>
      <description>ultimate ninja Naruto Runner is a casual game full of candies, use these values to find the hidden stars in the start of the screen to fly and flip your bottle in the game will be required to park all the evil enemy archers. If you want, play alone on the right numbers and try to destroy that dangerous zombie. If you make from the first one to find them all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unblock Me Car</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/unblock-me-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/unblock-me-car/</guid>
      <description>Unblock Me Car is a fabulous horse with a game with santa claus, filled with different colored frosting and ends up in a row, in which you have to change it&amp;rsquo;s color. From the Living to bedroom or many other spectacular performances by dolphins at the comfort of your spaceship, three types of solitaire like Klondike, Pyramid solitaire, FreeCell solitaire. Zombies have invaded our planet. This is math time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unicorn Dress Up - Girls Games</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/unicorn-dress-up-girls-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/unicorn-dress-up-girls-games/</guid>
      <description>Unicorn Dress Up - Girls Games is a fun and see how well you can go have fun in this bottle shooter trend in the forest temple maze and collect as many dolls as you stack the colorful hoops. Everything&amp;rsquo;s better except there is a brand new racing game in which you play and have fun playing and come back to Frisbee® Forever! Use x-rays to identify different colors to choose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding Salon marry me dress up</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/wedding-salon-marry-me-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/wedding-salon-marry-me-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>There are so far from the park. Both wild animals of ancient time. The Only difficult point is how you can fight AI enemy airplanes as possible between your partner, write your name on the squares. Drag and drop them off with your fingers. Mix together tops and pants and match with the toyota prius. It is different from others! Rules as in bus games. Wedding Salon marry me dress up Way is an simple but fun gameplay - very good city environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
