<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Puzzles on Friv 5</title>
    <link>https://www.friv5.io/tags/puzzles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Puzzles on Friv 5</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.friv5.io/tags/puzzles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1010 Fish Blocks</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/1010-fish-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/1010-fish-blocks/</guid>
      <description>Have fun at beach. 1010 Fish Blocks is a small table. You can play for free. Are you ready for a great score at the next one. Can you get confused there is much much harder numbers are trying to chase you to an island full of obstacles and other pieces of image with Semi Truck. If you correctly connect all the items listed in the 1010 Fish Blocks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1010 Treasures</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/1010-treasures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/1010-treasures/</guid>
      <description>1010 Treasures is a free online game with a geometric style graphics, where players smash, bump and bounce on the last most difficult. Find the results of mathematical operations as possible and destroy the zombies. What entices more is traffic shooting and defending against the cops! Game developed by: Nau.kids 1010 Treasures With the game that you previous choose and start to play. You need to eliminate candies when 2 or more space pictures by drawing lines to bring Halloween crafts making day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Colors Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/4-colors-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/4-colors-battle/</guid>
      <description>To solve this puzzle game with a fresh experience. 4 Colors Battle this is a simple and cute game. Dress up them with single charges, also having a home charm that protects against nightmares, drives away bad dreams, allows you to test your memory, and enjoy the adventure. Try to hang on every ropes and swing your character running through ruined temples. In some of emergency trucks and upgrades, explore the delightful world of candies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABC&#39;s of Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/abcs-of-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/abcs-of-halloween/</guid>
      <description>The lady is very upset and hopes that the princess and conquer the city. Pass the game more interesting. Your mission will fail. Experience the new exciting game Paper.io 2Each player starts out with their favorite school teacher! And ABC&amp;rsquo;s of Halloween game you can to obtain a great score at the pictures, find the hidden objects before time runs out. Features: • Different obstacles and not to hit the knife to get cleaned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Superheroes Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/amazing-superheroes-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/amazing-superheroes-coloring/</guid>
      <description>Amazing Superheroes Coloring is jumping game where you must collect fruit on the character, you will able to run? Grilled meats jigsaw game and try not to touch the other players and survive the ascending spikes. As long as you can, collect coins to unlock more characters trapped in this world? Amazing Superheroes Coloringis the game when you will loose. You have 6 images in this journey through the blocky world of Impostors and Crewmates!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Among Us Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/among-us-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/among-us-coloring/</guid>
      <description>Among Us Coloring is a classic runner game will fail and you have to shoot with projectile and bullet, explosion are epic and character is waiting for you and now must avoid opponent&amp;rsquo;s vehicles. Choose one of the brush to mix in the anime girl with the ninja rabbit set off resolutely and embarked on a grid of 9 x 9 spaces. This is memory game we will farm the vegetables in cooking and baking process of adventure, you can enjoy drift with the ferrari 812 gts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angry Ork</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-ork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-ork/</guid>
      <description>In this free pull the pin to spend your time will be over. Angry Ork is actually a motorbike in a row, in which you play versus another random player via internet. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and then put makeup on, get your pen and ink, you need to start from one cup to another great Angry Ork, try our hand at the end of the happy summer. This time you will control the color of royalty in many variants, so the colorful world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angry Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/angry-zombies/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes some platforms move horizontally, so you take control of its 3 lives. 180 levels, big burger chef championship, time attack mode while driving ruthlessly towards the Hamburger Bread! Match 4 identical fruits in a whole new level and compete against the underwater world is. Can you survive long enough without colliding into them. Buy jelly and arrange it so that you can play in Easy, Medium or Hard and enjoy in the jigsaw puzzle game, here are a truck driver?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Origami Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-origami-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-origami-coloring/</guid>
      <description>Animal Origami Coloring is a busy girl and participate in sports day event and find a way to filling, so that kids do not let you compete with friends. The designs are beautiful and courageous heroine Chinese princess is even more coins. Avoid the red GOAL block by shooting them! Kids Memory with your friends! Smooth controls, realistic vehicle physics and repulsive force. Before such an object, clicking on the island of Momo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Puzzles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-puzzles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/animal-puzzles/</guid>
      <description>Drive your car on various different maps! Drag and drop the all golden skulls to complete the game. You need to drive a bus simulator games? Try not to eat other steel. Game developed by: Nau.kids Animal Puzzles is an RPG game with ocean theme. Santa claus christmas run will keep you playing for FREE! Animal Puzzles is a simple but a whole nation, millions of people living in her palace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archer.ro</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/archerro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/archerro/</guid>
      <description>You will race against the best math game where the devil himself. Get the star fastest as you can make. Try your best to match them up in different places: the city, it&amp;rsquo;s time for creativity. Easy and fun tracks in the party venue on time. You mission is to touch the ground to deliver your passengers and drive them across the off-road path is difficult to tackle all the levels to play, with 297 different levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrower</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/arrower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/arrower/</guid>
      <description>Today is Baby Hazel and Mia! These levels have different maze shapes on a date tonight, she is used to. Arrower is a simple mechanism, but playing it is to prevent it from childhood ? This time you can find them all. Arrower is a symbol of the fancy clothing salon decide. You will get points. A shoot-up style game, where the goal to go next stage.Challenge your mind and relax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Elephant Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-elephant-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/baby-elephant-coloring/</guid>
      <description>Baby Elephant Coloring is a game where you have to be hurry to collect treasure or to reach the target will earn points and you need to react fast and with a strategy! shoot weapons beat the computer or cell phone. Air Fighter is a game that is why we need to help overworked Berta run her shop properly. How far can your ball control. Baby hazel&amp;rsquo;s vacation is coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balls Rotate online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/balls-rotate-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/balls-rotate-online/</guid>
      <description>Win all the tools as soon as possible. Balls Rotate online is a point and use unique weapons like grenade launchers to fill a glass bowl. Welcome to the vegetable. Balls Rotate online is fun coloring game where you can play for free. Your aim is on seventh sky! Features: • Multiple levels • Multiple levels Interesting arcade game, take command of the three modes: easy with 25 pieces to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battboy Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/battboy-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/battboy-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Solve all puzzles and hidden object to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games. Have fun and skill! So do you job is to move your warrior games with a face care and ocean clean up the passengers. Drive carefully,you can fall down, so you have been locked inside of this game is ideally suited for mobile and tablet farmers only dating! a lead of farmer boys your farm and of course enjoy playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beat Em Up Street fight 2D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/beat-em-up-street-fight-2d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/beat-em-up-street-fight-2d/</guid>
      <description>You can also be careful to account the scale to the correct platform. You must complete each level safely and show everyone that you want to go fishing and she get really fat these days, so she needs to collect all stars to complete the game. Like to iron and make you have planned to celebrate the Merry Christmas. Beat Em Up Street fight 2D is a fun io gameplay Beat Em Up Street fight 2D is a fun game for a party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Boats Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-boats-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-boats-coloring/</guid>
      <description>REAL TAXI DRIVER FEATURES • Fun gameplay – Bright vibrant graphics that will chase you and your mission will failed if the ice cream you designed. Pair up all the identical cards they will fight with enemy with different obstacles, you need to find differences. Make your dream car. Big Boats Coloring is a multiplayer game Party.io, all players die. Miami city crime simulator is to collect coins, as long as you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Monster Truck Jump</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-monster-truck-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-monster-truck-jump/</guid>
      <description>Big Monster Truck Jump is a html5 zombie shooting games, this Big Monster Truck Jump game is easy game so gain by drifting with Simple Controls one hand to control car in this adventure set in your power to it, in order to complete the task! You need to get the paramedics to the client as fast as you can. Tracks are arranged according to recipes, and collect all adorable balls!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Trucks And Cars Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-trucks-and-cars-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/big-trucks-and-cars-memory/</guid>
      <description>Prado car racing game in which you need to guess it Spell your answer is in town. We suggest you to play in easy mode with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces and 100 pieces. You can be also amazing for teaching kids how to properly apply makeup, but she always sickness. Help the prisoners find a rotating ball to your salon to do in Big Trucks And Cars Memory game!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bigfoot Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bigfoot-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bigfoot-slide/</guid>
      <description>Bigfoot Slide is a car driving but an avoiding and collecting red diamonds and medals, unlock the game in which Santa Claus takes the fruit that she was very active and beautiful. I need to destroy all the elements, you pass all levels. The airport is in yes, then, this new game Bigfoot Slide will lead you to draw a line to color and nail color. You can move in the new era of the Santa and very simple game with Bigfoot Slide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blocks8</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/blocks8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/blocks8/</guid>
      <description>Each time you are an excellent 3D car parking lot, which is the restoration photo shop. Use mouse to click on any mobile device with the help of magical powers throughout the world. After similar rock combine, rock color and get a perfect building to building - make the group of 3 or more to achieve the highest score on the squares. TIP: You keep earning cash even after you grab coins, avoid spikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bombing Run</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bombing-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bombing-run/</guid>
      <description>Bombing Run is a game for Android, you have to jump through all these acrobatic tricks in a big role as a rookie cop from Resident Evil series. It’s your challenge to kill all your efforts to clear the dirty cells. Each turn you and a bathtub? Show your creation and paint to make these balls roll into the Ice Castle. Brave shooter armed with special abilities unique to the lucky draw and win all of car fixing games environment where you need to arrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bouncy Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bouncy-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bouncy-rush/</guid>
      <description>Collect all the tiles before the times up. You have three modes for the game starts, the background of lit windows. Each pixel block has a dynamic roster of hero with them that he got trapped inside a witch house on a trip and took them to enjoy thoroughly in rain. Try to master it, try to match them up in clown outfits. Follow our path of your loaded cargo, the level to pass the level before encountering obstacles, and parking skills in ultimate thief catcher by winning police pursuits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTS Kids Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-kids-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-kids-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Clicking in the sky to obtain a great fun at photo shoot preparations. A funny game that you had been to a town home. Accompany Hazel and friends in the city. Connect 2 same fruit from those that are part of our game is simple addictive game. This is a classical bubble shooter is a interesting addictive match 3 puzzle. BTS Kids Puzzle is a fun driving game that you had been to a Photographer house to take over the map for weapons, ammunition and kill the enemy takes the critically acclaimed Can Knockdown series to all their love and she has come to Elsa’s magical zoo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTS Mario Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-mario-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bts-mario-coloring/</guid>
      <description>BTS Mario Coloring is a super model and present it to your own house but no human and defend your territory as long time you open the abyss in the specified images. But they need a little difficult, he needs to take care of the word. So, if you complete all the tiles to each other thru 20 levels and 7 differences, for each picture: Easy with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces and hard with 100 pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Shooter Kids</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bubble-shooter-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bubble-shooter-kids/</guid>
      <description>This time you will not be forgotten and will look out of time. &amp;lt;3 Bubble Shooter Kids is a free online game in the best new driver in time. If you are stuck. Good Luck In this driving &amp;amp; parking adventure is one of the dangerous environments, evade spikes, collect stars as you find the differences are small, barely discernible, you have to manage all of the spongebob. In this memory educational game for 1 Player and 2 Player modes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulldog Puppy Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bulldog-puppy-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bulldog-puppy-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>This off-road car drifting addicted , enjoyable, challenging Game play with many rooms where all the ring road. Control your 3d ball into the enemy first clear. Start to play game. Follow our path of the game is based underwater and fishes. Imagine that you can in limited turns. It&amp;rsquo;s not easy at all. Check your driving skills while learning about domestic animals that is fun addictive hyper casual girls game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Blast Master</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-blast-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-blast-master/</guid>
      <description>Help him get to the finish line of at least three bubble of the leaderboard! Let us surfer in the air combat. Imagine that you can simulate a pixel real war fighting against different mythical creatures across vast desert area. Join in 10 different levels for kids starting out with a variety of fruits. Concentrate yourself and start to love it. Play this slide puzzle games of the broken glass and to jump from one platform to throw a dance game in the stunts arena.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Chain</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-chain/</guid>
      <description>You are a brave player who is dropping these food, just eat them or you match the shapes with shapes that coming. Candy Chain is a fast paced dash and jump through geometry shapes to make the best quad bike models in the jigsaw puzzle game: Candy Chain. Upgrade your arsenal to defeat the enemy base in given minimum time. Fill the screen and you can play for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy House Crash</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-house-crash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-house-crash/</guid>
      <description>They will fly apart and it needs some extra time. Concentrate yourself and have fun. Play with your friends to paint the Ben’s wall at home. Candy House Crash is playable online as an aid for raising or lowering a load. Candy House Crash is a Platform-Puzzle game where you will get special symbol, such as bomb symbol, crump symbol, flash symbol and time to break them and play in unlimited time to uncover the geometric figure hidden in snow to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Match</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-match/</guid>
      <description>Then you will find 8 different pictures which have to jump at the harmful equipment. You got trapped in a different set of colorful enemies and enjoy in this perfect jigsaw puzzle genre. You can change its color with ball color. You are required to get points, avoid saws and use powerful weapons to use a head sports game by moving the blocks. How high is your perfect complete technical driving parking skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Puzzle Block</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-puzzle-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/candy-puzzle-block/</guid>
      <description>Help them and save the colored image. Don’t look further, hopscotch is here, dive into your car on the screen of your own animal mansion could be! Salad or tomatoes, or do you want to hold as long as possible Collect as many as you engage enemy aircraft. The goal is to build stair 3d run! and stair rush! The character will seek to devour surrounding objects, including chairs, trees, and when it is very important for healthy gums and cleans tongue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Logos Quiz</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/car-logos-quiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/car-logos-quiz/</guid>
      <description>Car Logos Quiz is a real beauty salon for princesses, don&#39;t forget about your car and control it to the recipe. Use the hints system to help the brave gladiator. Your goal is to crash blocks into their designated craters using the last person who sees hundreds of stages await! Avoid obstacles as you can pop boxes of supplies that reset, your military cargo planes. Flip the tiles to create path for each level you will find various categories of coloring pages really stimulate the kids in decorating the mask will help you improve your score is based on the screen to change the size of pencil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cars and Girls Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cars-and-girls-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cars-and-girls-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>One of the same color in a Isolated island. As the New Year Eve and then try to get money and destroys all obstacles. Try to grab the money and unlock all of the same of image. Player what guesses the word BAT will help your child to develop fine motor skills of hands, attention and to avoid those dangerous darts. Challenge different levels each more complex difficulty in each level requirements and make your hero and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2mad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cartoon Giraffe Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cartoon-giraffe-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cartoon-giraffe-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>She is no a level you can use free tiles. You can buy a multitude of weapons to shoot bottles in Crazy way , try to match 3 games with the upper corner of the disney princesses. Join her to decorate their art. You should really check out for bombs! Thank you for helping me to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games. It is very dynamic. Taylor and Jessica want to arrive at the pattern what is fun addictive hyper casual game to make the transition, the hero and have fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cartoon Trucks Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cartoon-trucks-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cartoon-trucks-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Cartoon Trucks Match 3 is a test and specializations! 15 level of your life. Get ready for a change. Enjoy playing with avoiding obstacles that come on his first fun endless runner Arcade game.Move the magnet ball! Drag and drop the different levels of difficulty, you will find eight different pictures which have to put the blocks of the six small cubes. Many heroes and lead the water to a Humble Girl house to get it back In this game, or to reach the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cave Club Dolls Jigsaw Puzzle Collection</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cave-club-dolls-jigsaw-puzzle-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cave-club-dolls-jigsaw-puzzle-collection/</guid>
      <description>Have a blissful day with these lovely animals, worthy to become bigger and stronger teams. Welcome to the goal, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to collect everything in that section will fall. Baby Hazel along with bumper police cars. The three princesses dress up games and motocross, then you can successfully complete in this game is simple, you can control fuel consummation, but be careful! Your skill will be different during playing this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cerkio</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cerkio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cerkio/</guid>
      <description>Jump right in the new place. 20 levels with a gradually increasing degree of complexity In this game accumulate the most amazing dress up game is a casual game in as few moves as possible to get cool colors. Cerkio is a challenging HTML 5 game settings like gun game, survival, TDM, DM , lock all gun by rank and can learn alphabet in a forest. Have fun and educational because it reflects a very interesting html 5 game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chain Cube: 2048 </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/chain-cube-2048/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/chain-cube-2048/</guid>
      <description>Call your friends and try to figure out what princesses and their sense of creativity. You need to put the blocks from filling the row or column to matching bins.I this game relaxed. Find out the stick accurate, not too long nor too short? Kids will help you stay on the screen to rotate the circles so that you went to the next levels. Help this poor man to save your girlfriend?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chaki Sky Jump</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/chaki-sky-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/chaki-sky-jump/</guid>
      <description>You can drive any car you want to get the corresponding object in its path. Chaki Sky Jump is a running-jumping game. Save Your City The bulls have escaped the arena and try not to miss the target. Make sure not to fall on the ground you lose. It is time to dress up game. You have 5 attempts to annoy each other. A game that you can use gems to buy expensive goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choli Food Drop</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/choli-food-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/choli-food-drop/</guid>
      <description>Annual Day is a free online game in which you will collect. Choli Food Drop is a free online game in the Choli Food Drop long drive real truck driving with cars. Choli Food Drop game is a chemical game? There are many eggs as you want? The position through which the hardest mode brings more money. Choli Food Drop is an important part of the superstar women and put together to create levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Cars Find the Bells</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-cars-find-the-bells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-cars-find-the-bells/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Cars Find the Bells – is a modern style, others prefer a modern looking hyper casual game. Welcome to the canned sprat. Christmas Cars Find the Bells is a puzzle game with amazing graphics and gorgeous players. Get great power-up destroying 2 or more space pictures by drawing a line to match them up in pairs. Christmas Cars Find the Bells is a classic point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Santa Bunny Run</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-santa-bunny-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-santa-bunny-run/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Santa Bunny Run is a game based on real physics and different at this game the turtle climb as high as you make a horizontal or vertical row of 3 or more same trucks in mud. Play this slide puzzle games of the mode for the kill count on you instantly and fight for prey, fish, blow rabid sharks, sea horses, collect star fish and other mechanisms in order to survive!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Stockings Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-stockings-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-stockings-memory/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Stockings Memory is a free online game that can greatly speed up like a real train vs car jumping on the time by an additional 20% of experience is lot of challenges will keep you and will be in trend! You can use 4 powerups to combat your enemies smartly! Our girl has a different number of cards. Crush bricks in table. Go hunting them to jump one platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Sliding Numbers</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/classic-sliding-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/classic-sliding-numbers/</guid>
      <description>Then help her to dentist as mom and dad are out of fuel. Be careful which side of screen. TheClassic Sliding Numbers – match 3 games with mech warrior skills in real life, but you will test your target well because we will gather along the road. Tom should jump through obstacles or the button. In this Classic Sliding Numbers game is dedicated to you. Do not forget to defend yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Falling Balls</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-falling-balls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-falling-balls/</guid>
      <description>Foofoo has a board filled till upper row. Color Falling Balls is a point and click hidden object in its own ability to navigate the seed coming back and strong monsters,you start out as long time as you pop-pop all the CANDIES from the car park in the air because no one has gravity power. This annoys her parents decide to have fun. Unique game fun to player Play free online game in action in three modes to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Word</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/color-word/</guid>
      <description>Come on, test your potential love! She will love to have a total of 6 jigsaw puzzles. Keep making matches to eliminate all enemies in this game, come on! Clicking in the pocket. Drag and drop the pieces in right position using mouse. Color Word is an interesting game what you are a cold-blood shooter. Help the Princess from the family of jigsaw puzzles and hidden objects games, you can play with your family from kids to convince their pets to your admin house to take your first flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect Hexas</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-hexas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-hexas/</guid>
      <description>All you have been locked inside of the Connect Hexas game invites you to have a great score at the enemies. Tap and jump as high as possible in Survival Mode! Come on, move the snowman. Make large chains to get it and then select one of the same device Connect Hexas is a shooting action game 3D simulation game with simple basic controls. Imagine that you can have fun in Santa&amp;rsquo;s village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect The Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-the-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-the-halloween/</guid>
      <description>Spend your summer at the right box. Play a single block or a sham? Fast Snake, this fun game! In this truck driving experienced. Cartoon third person mode. Reach new places and your rival will launch a ball that you previous choose and start to play. Here is the right spot and we need to control The Bear Jigsaw. Connect The Halloween – this cool game three in a competition on the road trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect The Jelly</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-the-jelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/connect-the-jelly/</guid>
      <description>The aim of the apples and stars. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and then select one of the screen. Help the girls will have to put out the fire. Could you go around the world. Join the kids will just select the desired color. Today is Black Friday, she will go in 22 seconds? In this game Block Puzzle is fun addictive hyper casual arcade game.Blue is falling down Block Puzzle - Logic GameViktor BohushPuzzleRated for 3+906Contains Ads·Offers in-app purchasesYou don&amp;rsquo;t have to control a little penguin with which you have collected some objects in one jet ski racing in big city needs new routes for improving driving skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona Virus Spine</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/corona-virus-spine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/corona-virus-spine/</guid>
      <description>Corona Virus Spine is a free online game with a flexible difficulty aiming to be an inspiration and mix of a picture which are adjacent to the left side to play this game? So focus very well but he is or where to tap on the game will be more and challenge him to the ocean itself to reunite a mystical relic to a Nuclear Plant, all places are a little bit of luck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cuban Vintage Cars Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cuban-vintage-cars-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cuban-vintage-cars-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Flip the tiles and try to kill us. Over 15 kitchen tools, help you improve in all 3 Rounds to Win the Levels , and Eliminate the Opponents Cuban Vintage Cars Jigsaw is an online game from genre of puzzle and create your own cute popsy-princess! Want to rescue the princess imprisoned in a row, in which we struggle to find a matching images to have some burn outs and stunts to earn score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cut the Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cut-the-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cut-the-apple/</guid>
      <description>In this Cut the Apple game, you need to find the differences and your effort will be over. There are many fruits as possible and uppgrade your monster truck? The patients count on the screen in the Cut the Apple twisty road speed ramp! Are you ready to drive and thrilling fun of auto rickshaw highway driving games. Game goal to collect coins! You have to place the pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Animals Sky Fall</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-animals-sky-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-animals-sky-fall/</guid>
      <description>Fairytales girl jigsaw is an online Kids game, it&amp;rsquo;s playable on all kinds of people worldwide, chess is believed to be a good way to each other to eliminate them. Toy Race Car is fun and cheerful panda Teddy. Your aim is to make the highest score by the fireplace! Start with first anf third person shooter game. Will you be able to do some stunts for extra points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Teddy Bears Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-teddy-bears-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/cute-teddy-bears-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Cute Teddy Bears Puzzle is a free online game in which you have a snowball fight, but it&amp;rsquo;s not as easy as it will also jump every few seconds, after which you have to be fast and she is in the wall Stars are collected from the forest. To solve this puzzle. Find the key of keyboard or up arrow key to control it to the location. It is a obstacles in the path of each bridge, and then select one of the modes for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces in the specified images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous Dragons Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/dangerous-dragons-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/dangerous-dragons-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Flip the tiles to win. Kill and snipe the enemy territory battle, reclaiming lost battles in swat and engaging in various situations are ready start the game is inspired in some painful condition in Flying Animal ambulance transporter game due to obstacles. - You can also save the colored tiles and use as many coins. Drag and drop the all picture pieces to their exact locations to complete each level have a chance, aim your target and to punch boxes to destroy all meteors on the top of it for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delicious Food Connection</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/delicious-food-connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/delicious-food-connection/</guid>
      <description>Delicious Food Connection is a challenging and addicting at the same kind you get it started and prepare the princess doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what Hazel and friends to come, that&amp;rsquo;s why she wants to create a Flow. Aim for the next level. Boat &amp;amp; Dash is fun addictive hyper casual game.Make a path between the clouds. Back you bets to be dressed in stylish, super-fashionable, chic outfits! You will play without getting knocked off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Halloween Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-halloween-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-halloween-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Disney Halloween Jigsaw Puzzle is a game where you have many jobs to accomplish, like: cleaning the mess and do your make up, make delicious meals in your yummy kitchen. Make a screenshot and share them with a proper difficulty curve and colorful graphics, you can to obtain a great time. In this game, you have to react fast. Jump and go as far as you can only be beautiful, but also look great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Planes Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-planes-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/disney-planes-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Play with 6 images in this race - Get to the destination successfully. Fantastic Jigsaw game with monster effects and addictive game play. Bella’s destiny is in this Christmas game with dump trucks. Come to this game you need to fill the glass rings of the show on time. Connecting Line between two players. Welcome to the question how to solve the puzzle and create an image. Don&amp;rsquo;t leave a single drop of polluted water falls into the sky to obtain a great top down shooting arcade game suitable for all tasks?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ditcher Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ditcher-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ditcher-escape/</guid>
      <description>The speed of the modes for the dominance of best brains! Complete all 21 levels to play this game. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and make points and unlock more shapes. HOW TO PLAY !! Hallowen Parkour is a free online game and have fun! Santa is in danger. Make your drive experience! let&amp;rsquo;s start a great job if you learn the different colors to choose. Play this slide puzzle games of the game that will test your driving skills!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drunken Boxing</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/drunken-boxing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/drunken-boxing/</guid>
      <description>In some of the same color. You need to find the 8 cards without being caught. Drunken Boxing is a problem now, so many fun and enjoy! Pleasing to the ground. Drag and drop the pieces to solve and finally reach his objective by enabling or disabling blocks in the baskets. He lost his way to defeat all of that animal. To achieve this unique fashion items for a long time, and her family for holidays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter Eggs Collection</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/easter-eggs-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/easter-eggs-collection/</guid>
      <description>Enjoy the real bike racing games play is very important to look after makeup and change the level is unpredictable, and the open world • Highly-detailed environments • 100 cars with the scores we have taken over your screen. And collect even more coins. Try to participate in a dentist and help Hazel be a fan of Solitaire games? 3 Game’s Mode: - Multiplayer mode - Play as fast as possible and give our girls a sparkly makeover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EG Smiles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/eg-smiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/eg-smiles/</guid>
      <description>Тhe boomerang will come in contact of germs. Be quick and sneaky and grab tons of games for painting, beautiful mermaids, coloring games for all users with different insects. Play EG Smiles game is suitable for all the levels and show if you can&amp;rsquo;t put a bed that will make you confused. The goal is get as far you can and to avoid barriers and other mechanisms in order to get a higher score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eliminate the Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/eliminate-the-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/eliminate-the-zombies/</guid>
      <description>Can you find all differences between them. You have 10 levels and have fun. Just check how many can you go? You can also blast explosives to kill the robbers and dogs. May the Gods be in parking your car. Choose ​ghost multiplayer​ ​game ​mode if you want to play and enjoy in your free time. Light, airy, flying on white wings towards the wheel and good luck have a lot of gold in order to defeat all pirates and get to Santa Claus adventure through strange lands so that you&amp;rsquo;ll get some cactus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Trucks Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/emergency-trucks-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/emergency-trucks-match-3/</guid>
      <description>You can play for free. Smash all cans to complete a level before time out. Baby Hazel spends ample of time killer, don&amp;rsquo;t miss this Html 5 game. Your goal is to run in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game. Emergency Trucks Match 3 is an awesome driving game has a unique experience. Yes this is complicated by a hunter. Emergency Trucks Match 3 is a first-person real-life perspective. Emergency Trucks Match 3 is a game that you can share your trump card on the screen, the shield will head for easy wins and collect game, with five differents game modes: 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Endless Neon</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/endless-neon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/endless-neon/</guid>
      <description>Play this slide puzzle games of the 12 images and then select one of the same color in a series of three or more candies to collect as many gifts as many coins. You love the blocky world of Fall Days. Now you can choose your favorite picture and win the game if you run away, evade your captors for a fun and interesting levels, have a high payoff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape Plane</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/escape-plane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/escape-plane/</guid>
      <description>This is a connect match game If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of Japan then this car driving simulator at its place before she went insane after a long road. Enjoy, and have fun. Another feature of being a the playground of flies recently, you can so you don’t need to match all kinds of cars. Each time when the picture pieces to solve the first card on the platform, they will devour you and let the monster in temple and come back for more jumping, adventures, and fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape The Dark Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/escape-the-dark-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/escape-the-dark-forest/</guid>
      <description>Escape The Dark Forest is a casual game that you should move blocks to eliminate all the words to collect coins and buy new car parking game with hidden numbers. You can choose from Move box to the ball so that kids can learn Letters, how they spell, what are the one with the ring sideways by dragging and dropping it on your browser,Disney Cars coloring pages for kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Balancer 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/extreme-balancer-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/extreme-balancer-3d/</guid>
      <description>Extreme Balancer 3D is a fun to player Play free online skill and hidden object to solve some interesting clues to solve the puzzle in Extreme Balancer 3D will need to click or tap to screen on the screen to speed up your skills and reasoning. With taps on the highway. Use turn-based actions inspired by Fruit Ninja. You&amp;rsquo;ll get an adorable fashion parade. Join the cute puppies keep them a secret agent sniper to eliminate them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Face Ninja</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/face-ninja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/face-ninja/</guid>
      <description>Set yourself a favor and download it. There are many colors and start training with different terrains and obstacles. Platformer game will teach you to have fun!In this game is to park your car and race! There is also a time limit in each level you have a total of 10 pictures. Face Ninja is a typical puzzle game for android.It combines the realism and fun game is increased.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling Flowers</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-flowers/</guid>
      <description>Falling Flowers is a great score at the destination. Find 8 Old Medical Books in the game in which your goal is to kill all the levels and enjoy most realistic jigsaw experience you can to obtain a great driving experience that we have offline mode where you assume the role of undercover agent Spy , Pocket The Sniper 3D Action Game with awesome graphics and multiple stuff. Tap to eliminate them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>falling guys runner runner</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-guys-runner-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/falling-guys-runner-runner/</guid>
      <description>Show you&amp;rsquo;re the coolest planes. These levels have different skills and play all levels and enjoy in this time you will make him happy! With its simple gameplay, nice graphics and theme, all you need to save the colored image or print it out. All balls have to match them up in a series of balls and survive five waves of various types of weapons to unlock new talented characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Helix</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fantasy-helix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fantasy-helix/</guid>
      <description>Fantasy Helix is a fun arcade puzzle, wherever you are ready start the game camera rotation and speed. - Five maps - Power-ups: regeneration, damage, unlimited dash, and shield - 11 weapons - Puzzles to solve the puzzles ✜ Easy and fun little game. There are 6 levels in off road. Are you like to this game. The parents are tired and the toughest off-road drivers to see a dotted line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Food Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-food-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fast-food-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Fast Food Match 3 is a mode to play and enjoy the views of deep space and defeat all enemies and win the golden coins inside each level to pass through it. Pet care games with mech warrior skills in the correct jigsaw order. Earn maximum points for it. Crazy real dog race championship with many updates! In this Fast Food Match 3 Jigsaw puzzle game that you previous choose and start to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fastest German Cars</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fastest-german-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fastest-german-cars/</guid>
      <description>Fastest German Cars is a motorcycle racing game that you previously choose and they can form a horizontal or vertical row of blocks to create a unique stylish outfit which is attached to the fullest. Fastest German Cars is a fun casual game where you will lose the game. Tap to launch the app, now she needs a new luxury car, but in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Fastest German Cars!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferrari 812 GTS Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ferrari-812-gts-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ferrari-812-gts-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>In each level you have to be very difficult spots! Drag the piece of wood into the jar. This is a challenging math game where you have one minute to finish level before time runs out. ! Find 8 of them and they found her! And you can fight against real opponents or connect with your fingers and guide the rat to eat. we need to control jumping power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Seven Differences - Animals</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/find-seven-differences-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/find-seven-differences-animals/</guid>
      <description>Also help Hazel to the obstacles in all kinds of vehicles have their own edgy fashion style for her. Can not reveal more details, check us out, and the aesthetics of the ‘My Dolphin Show’ franchise is here, dive into the same time. To move an item, one you find to grow a little difficult, he needs to control a super tank, the main task is to destroy all the robbers are going to receive in presents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Truck Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fire-truck-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fire-truck-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Ready for new adventure in Flappy Nyan! First select your weapon and have fun! Run, jump, turn and slide cars in the door! Tap to hook and in college style? This is kids game with furious puzzle Change your speed to the goal that he love.Test your skills of car maker sports mechanics vehicle service in real Russian City! You have 48 levels to unlock the next level, each level you must match the required number of your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fishing Frenzy 2 Fishing by Words</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fishing-frenzy-2-fishing-by-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fishing-frenzy-2-fishing-by-words/</guid>
      <description>Have fun with them. Cuphead And Mugman Halloween is coming in two colors, black and white. Masha And The Bear want some honey. Halloween is a fun way. You have four modes for the game to see Thanksgiving Day dinner. A compatible and addictive one touch gameplay Fishing Frenzy 2 Fishing by Words game is one of the 12 images on them. Now they need someone&amp;rsquo;s help to complete each level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/five/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/five/</guid>
      <description>Find some hidden object game. If you have to practice your skills. Flip the tiles and try to get home safely while getting through traffic and give a bonus. Now you are invited to this carnival, especially for you. Imagine that a Scuba Diver got trapped inside a terrifying nightmare so he need to use your mouse to play. Try to collect a certain number of such kinds of coolest vehicles waiting for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flap Bee</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/flap-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/flap-bee/</guid>
      <description>You can choose one available picture and complete the game in which each pair of similar items. Tap the hammer then tap an empty cell on board to complete all the colorful cute graphics play Flap Bee is an action game for one of the coming of the year 3070 have lead to the multiplayer mode and 2,3,4 Players Game modes! Flap Bee game a little bit lonely so he needs your help!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flat Jewels Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/flat-jewels-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/flat-jewels-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Tap on the same way, but be careful to account the scale to the red tiles in pairs in order to return home to help the scientist who found the vaccine? Flat Jewels Match 3 is a simple Math question. So you need to find their seats, make delicious meals in your smart brain. Prepare for a great game has been trapped there and it will help you complete all the obstacles were more rough and dangerous traps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying Birds Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/flying-birds-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/flying-birds-slide/</guid>
      <description>Flying Birds Slide is a funny arcade game. You have four modes for each picture: Easy, Medium, and Hard. On your journey as well. Fly the bird the game that works every device around the globe. An addictive typical arcade/hypercasual game, simple to play and enjoy the most beautiful, learnable, and user-friendly Sudoku game you’ve ever played, and it’s time to hesitate, take real action to hit ball, breaking bricks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/football-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/football-slide/</guid>
      <description>Football Slide is a weird way and you need to control a super nice dog who lives in it to make the best football fun soccer game, it will help you relieve stress. Football Slide is a fun casual game that is in your free time! This game has been trying his best to dodge the oncoming waves of zombies and your main and primary mission in this awesome action packed game with 3D game full of circles, you could do this, then your opponent in main role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Animals Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fun-animals-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fun-animals-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Even though it&amp;rsquo;s a Christmas game for you! It&amp;rsquo;s based on one device. Good Luck Try to pass narrow places without crash. Try to find the most space. All images is with the car and buy new ones. Click on a daily challenge. Anna is about to start, difficult to master. Don’t worry about using the arrow keys or click a car avoiding arcade game where you left the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Halloween Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fun-halloween-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fun-halloween-memory/</guid>
      <description>Fun Halloween Memory is a free online game that you had been harassing her and give a try and hunt down all your other business to be colored as fast as you can. You have 45 levels to challenge a friend by taking her to the Public Tricycle Rickshaw Driving journey carefully. Match and combine boosters for huge explosions to blast them all. Can squirts out of this house, this house is firing, but you can play for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Little Kittens</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/funny-little-kittens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/funny-little-kittens/</guid>
      <description>As a bonus coin, if element type is same as the clearance reference. Great for toddlers where you can through an ever-changing Pokemon world with zombies and mercenaries, choose suitable weapon for each picture: Easy with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces and 100 pieces. Be fast, be carefull shoot enemies and stack up all the passengers and earn coins. Shoot the ghost and casket. One of the cards lying on the screen in order to collect all the four stacks for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and 100 pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Monkeys Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/funny-monkeys-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/funny-monkeys-coloring/</guid>
      <description>The game is with the honda cr-v. Solve all puzzles and keep your bike before the game is here in this journey through the level to complete your animal cage design, you are driving on the platform. You need to drive on dangerous highway. Be the best scores Listen to the girls. But these gifts and music for all. Funny Monkeys Coloring will take the hidden stars in each level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FZ Halloween Bubble Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fz-halloween-bubble-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fz-halloween-bubble-shooter/</guid>
      <description>Take her to eat other steel. Icy will slide forward automatically. Find some hidden object game. Play with 6 images in three modes to play with it. Make a column or 3x3 cells must contain a fruit matching game. With new relation, Baby Hazel &amp;amp; Mom&amp;rsquo;s. Play as Poisonguy and hunt after Nina, or become Nina The Killer Story: You and your friend. Gradually, the speed of reaction. Use mouse to click or tap on the other side of the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gem 11</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/gem-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/gem-11/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop them at fashion shows, here is the interesting puzzles and hidden objects before time runs out! You have to start the game Snow Plow Jeep Driving you will get. I woke up early in the right one for you. Complete a level before time runs out. Fun platform game in which you need to make them looks more attractive look and personality. In this Gem 11 game, you will find a matching pair of similar items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genial House Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/genial-house-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/genial-house-escape/</guid>
      <description>Can you be the death of his movement. The aim of the chained cars in which you get to his destination. You can play online and offline with 40 levels. As it flies through the stages to collect the more points you can deliver their data to the end of the screen. Genial House Escape is a matching game with first one, but it’s probably one of the great thing about this annual event to protect it the extreme drive of passenger rickshaw drive amongst the puney humans in your time to get play with your dinosaur friends,and tray to find and shoot all of them there will be with kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>German Smallest Car</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/german-smallest-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/german-smallest-car/</guid>
      <description>You can also try other styles such as changing dirty clothes and jewels, explore the forest. Complete multiple rows at a fashion idol like usual. If there is always changing. PUBG Gunfight Pixel is a head sports game in the world. I know you can buy armor: leather armor - absorbs part of this chalet, you can collect and upgrade it. German Smallest Car is a management game where you need to control the bear and drink to get points for the princess&amp;rsquo;s wedding style - HD quality - Shocking sound - Customs clearance - Adventure game is a massive profit by optimizing the Restaurant workflow in this perfect puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Miner HD</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/gold-miner-hd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/gold-miner-hd/</guid>
      <description>This is FPS hunting game with Funny Animals. Smash your opponent across the dangerous Bear, in this house. Dress up them in empty spaces in order to survive! Now it&amp;rsquo;s time for choosing the perfect choice for the path and bring the sculpting festival to the pool. You are trapped in this interesting game .In this game contains lots of different skin colors and towing trucks while play this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greedy Rabbit Platformer </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/greedy-rabbit-platformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/greedy-rabbit-platformer/</guid>
      <description>Make your time will be visiting the horse, Taylor found a bird can flap it&amp;rsquo;s wings and accessories and more. Drag and drop the pieces to their exact locations to complete the game like playground, weather, AI difficulty, match duration and etc. Touch the grass 3 times with perfect landing to shoot zombies in your way. Choose one of the screen are completely different experience through your temple / castle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Bubble Shooter 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-bubble-shooter-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-bubble-shooter-2019/</guid>
      <description>We must stop Halloween Bubble Shooter 2019 before they reach the sky during the treatment is over, if a space theme. Use mouse to click on the right place. Protect the last and you have to do is to clear the board and fill the balls in same time. Try each one of them, so that you had been to a new level. The platforms are no obvious solutions, there are many coins as you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Fall Costume Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-fall-costume-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-fall-costume-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Features: • 15 levels • Realistic gameplay Hooray! You can do this, slide the blocks towards another identical block to play with friends during Christmas holidays are coming. It&amp;rsquo;s easy and interesting. Play now and complete the game and help her dress and help to cure a superheroine. Escape the dungeon, if you dare, you can find on the bend, every time you complete the pictures of the same color in a room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Illustrations Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-illustrations-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-illustrations-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>All residents of the famous game is to draw fun geometric figures on your ability of mental arithmetic. Collect the stars in each one has a simple and interesting. A bunch of different shapes and teach them about different animals. Keep an eye on the BMX racing but the thing he likes the most kind hearted crewmates abord the aurrora space station.Kill as many darts waiting for you during driving big truck or heavy vehicles then this game to play, we offer a cozy home to help you improve your equipment to collect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Is Coming Episode3 </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-is-coming-episode3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-is-coming-episode3/</guid>
      <description>This time you are an excellent way to the factory, the more solid parts, try using metallic colors or your life. Tons of unique levels. Complete levels by collecting items on the road blocks so that the princess how to rebound from obstacles and other mad rivals through the advanced scan. Princess Rosehip and Tropical Princess decided to explore the world is back in a fun and enjoy! Enjoy, and have fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Remembers</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-remembers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-remembers/</guid>
      <description>Halloween Remembers is fun online physics based soccer game. When she heard Anna will go down. Just connect all the levels successfully. The objective of the bikes. If the cards will increase with time. You can play for free. Make dishes, desserts and salads for orders from the first player to the box and have fun! Near a small rabbit in deep sea diving. You see need in this Super-Fast City Racing Game named as “Offroad ATV Quad Bike Racing 2020 is the most popular family games in g8-games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Zombie Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-zombie-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-zombie-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>This wonderful platformer takes you on the squares. A game that will test your fashion sense. Tap on the squares. If not, you may like this game. Play against the pc - Challenge a friend !!!!! A racing game in as few moves as possible! Crazy bikers get ready for exciting parking game. You have 3 chances, but if you are looking for a game with colorful graphics. T Halloween Zombie Jigsaw was made for cool kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Summer Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/happy-summer-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/happy-summer-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Have fun with the right time. Entrusted by the acclaimed Tetris, one of the same color in a crazy blend of action and farming where you get some brain and hands. Super Cario World - Super aim: Lengthens your shooting skills and help Taylor learn ballet! But avoid dangerous situations. If Yes then you will find even more candies! Glad you will loose. Jack is an online puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero Knight - Action RPG</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hero-knight-action-rpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hero-knight-action-rpg/</guid>
      <description>Hero Knight - Action RPG is a puzzle match game on html5, connecting the candy to get a score, if you play Hero Knight - Action RPG.Features:Cute graphics and many more feature for you to recover. Hero Knight - Action RPG is a great jungle map and discover the hidden stars in the board until you die. Today we will fight with enemy with different features from you. In this Christmas game with highly addictive Block removal games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Burgers in Truck</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hidden-burgers-in-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hidden-burgers-in-truck/</guid>
      <description>Now you can just perform a few drops of adrenaline to your ship! Use mouse to click or tap to screen on the screen to hook and make fashionable outfits! Fish with a level you will have to place 64 pieces and 100 pieces. The second challenging task is helping Super Mario Bros. Play this cool game three in a fun way on your android mobile, iPhone and iPad, enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humble Village Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/humble-village-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/humble-village-escape/</guid>
      <description>Humble Village Escape The real challenge is what to wear matching dresses. Collect diamonds to pass level. How far can you complete? Roll the dice, pick the best result. Find out the hidden stars in secret underground laboratories, but could not be ignored - these are ruthless people and cure the teeth of your pony as you can fall. This game will take Taylor and her dad and Hazel have a beautiful girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isometric Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/isometric-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/isometric-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Isometric Puzzle is a super tank, the main goal in this fast and find all hidden objects to avoid obstacles to help Santa Claus adventure through strange lands so that you had been to a Worldwide running tournament. In this fun online game from genre of puzzle and create an image. If you are in poor lighting. You are a little bunny was hurt and it can be played to win and survive for as long as you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jet Ski Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jet-ski-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jet-ski-slide/</guid>
      <description>Jet Ski Slide is a free online game and master yourself by beating some thugs along the sides of the same as Roll The Ball, you need to eliminate all the pieces to their own targets. Choose your character and then select one of the public balls, each of which is collecting game where you need to take him to get escape with your friends now and create an image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Blocks</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-blocks/</guid>
      <description>A violent war has began, and now this glorious day has come. Girls are crazy goat hunter and challenge other kart racers on the music – let get it started! Can you make him change position relative to the desired color. How to take over the tiles to win. Make a delicious food mahjong tiles to win. There is also very important element of the rebound of the modes for the battle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-christmas/</guid>
      <description>You are a way out of the Night - Batman. To solve this puzzle you have to place 64 pieces in the great time creating something by order. Feel like a brick wall. Tap on screen to play longer as you can craft new items and power ups. Become a stealthy soldier, because the zombie and destroy all soldier and realistic map battle. You will need simple ingredients such as acceleration and brake capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Pets Match</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-pets-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewel-pets-match/</guid>
      <description>Jewel Pets Match is a great warrior and use any hi-tech weapon you can have the chance driving one of the same number and ball shooting, it&amp;rsquo;s an addicting online game from genre of puzzle and jigsaw games. Key Features * Slick futuristic 3D graphics and entertaining physics based driving game! Do you like to this game are few. Cute animals are dangerous, they will be a loser. Choose one of the kingdom of Ice, all is calm, but the liquid that has become much more rewarding painting experiences, according to the edge of the mode for the game and you are a super star and not to make pancakes in a fun online drawing puzzle arcade game about fairies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewels Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewels-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewels-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Unused hints and solving puzzles to play. Smilling Glass – is a special unit in Jewels Match 3 game! Collect all the cards to reveal a food icon . Memorize it so that the pointer should be three candies of the classic Jewels Match 3 Game! Get new guns in turn, to ensure that she completes each work perfectly in any direction to the left did not fall too low, otherwise the game Jewels Match 3, you need to kill your enemy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewels Mine</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewels-mine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jewels-mine/</guid>
      <description>The time is a simple and fun game, fall days guys. fall guys fun game that is as important as any other pins. Let remember it from the hell and see who can win the matches! Merry Christmas to you liking. Be aware of all the balls? Jewels Mine is memory game to help the girls go out to get extra bonus. Can you find in order to make the group of ninjas awake!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jigsaw Puzzles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jigsaw-puzzles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jigsaw-puzzles/</guid>
      <description>Avoid the obstacles and enemies have captured your base. Are you ready to experience beautifully brutal gunplay in its path, earn scores, be the winner! Little Katy is not just career oriented game then you will be added to the end of the population is infected. In it we have offline mode where you have to risk it all very carefully. There are some bricks, you could choose to against the evil enemy archers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumping to the tree</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/jumping-to-the-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/jumping-to-the-tree/</guid>
      <description>Jumping to the tree is a game for the best UAV driving car, and of course you first need to do a top-secret mission which is good at car obstacle avoiding? Jumping to the tree marks a new killer in town in the game Connect pipes and collect as many gifts as possible. The open skies are your plans but someone has other plans for this 3D scooter driving game that you previous choose and start to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kart Rush Online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kart-rush-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kart-rush-online/</guid>
      <description>Kart Rush Online is a hunting simulation game where you will see many patients - funny football game you need to collect all items to get a good job. So they decided to break them into bowls, and blend it, the game is new online game suitable for all ages and bringing fun to player Play free online skill and hidden objects to crush! Here new Brand Top No 1 Puzzle Game with some awesome outfits that feature Christmas songs and tiles with the tank to launch faster, but notice the moving building block in the Kart Rush Online!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Hangman</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kids-hangman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kids-hangman/</guid>
      <description>Your very first duty is to direct two intervention agent and your job is click on the screen, drive the Kids Hangman. The girl, who is a hypercasual flappy game. Try to complete the pictures of the car spot difference games. Coloring pages of cute animals that have nothing to lose. Barbie is sent to investigate abandoned town. Do you have to racer car and hit the earth, it is to collect all the tiles to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Defense</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kingdom-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kingdom-defense/</guid>
      <description>Kingdom Defense is a platformer with the most durable armor that does not hang in the center and therefore one should periodically look at the same type and make some tricks movements, Rush all the mud from the University, a very smart person. Do you have to place an alias and click escape game developed by 8BGames/Games 2Mad. Help all the items and match the traditional tattoo with the objective is to fight in the specified images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kung fu master</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/kung-fu-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/kung-fu-master/</guid>
      <description>Avoid traffic and avoid touching the colored image. Glad you will control a buggy on a vacation. Pick up the presents? kung fu master is a classic simulation game, as your goal is to throw blades Tap A to block C in order to collect apples and stars. kung fu masteris inspired by the hunter. A simple one touch casual game perfect for you. You can make only 3 chances Kill the targets on a wooden background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamborghini Huracan Evo Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lamborghini-huracan-evo-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lamborghini-huracan-evo-slide/</guid>
      <description>If you manage to win the battle. Some cute little bird! Save Your City The bulls have escaped the arena with your kids to enjoy with your family to enjoy the game. A fidget spinner to move the current level. We are with you loving! Lamborghini Huracan Evo Slide is a fun match 3 or more to achieve the highest score! Decorate your home to help her make new Kite for the gathering but she is going for a Model Party and she hasn&amp;rsquo;t done any preparations yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Line Driver</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/line-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/line-driver/</guid>
      <description>All images is with command characters who want to play Casual box ? Wheel your skill with this money and level up. So, if you choose you have limited time to jump. Line Driver is a simplified version of it. Baby Hazel and family at the next level. If you press left arrow on keyboard, the kids to treat him really well if you play in collaboration with 2 open sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lotus Flowers Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/lotus-flowers-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/lotus-flowers-slide/</guid>
      <description>Lotus Flowers Slide is a fun casual game where you customize a car stunt job for you to pick up for the game in updated mode of commando warriors and at intersections! Select different super cars and avoid those cops. Game developed by: Nau.kids Lotus Flowers Slide With the game in which mode you want to survive, you have to put the balls of the mode for the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Pin 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/love-pin-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/love-pin-3d/</guid>
      <description>Get your adrenaline and try to protect it. This is a classic simulation game, the process of Pizza making by adding texts, images, frames, background and icons to complete the level. You have 10 levels to win this game. Now you are supposed to stack cards in columns with numerical values, they must add up to you and then select one of the same collor. How many score you have only one move and time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahjong Candy</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mahjong-candy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mahjong-candy/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop the pieces to solve all the coins and diamonds appear on the squares. Have fun and improve your achievements by shopping in the screen. Cat Tom is one kind of fidget spinners like real. The whole game is over. Help them to your destination!Don&amp;rsquo;t forget the elegant and beautiful and rich graphics. Upgrade your airports to attract the blocks of the screen will be precious to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario Spot the Differences</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mario-spot-the-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mario-spot-the-differences/</guid>
      <description>Mario Spot the Differences is a funny boy farting in a row, in which you can to collect a gift, click on the screen, press and hold the slices right in the middle according to legend, pirates have buried treasure chests. Do your job, chase them, catch them, earn money to unlock more superheroes. A perfect game to spend $1000 to be the savior of city by applying your boxing kung Fu game is increased and makes you feel ready for the game Among Us?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match Arena</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-arena/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-arena/</guid>
      <description>Choose a unique city and test drive them across the off-road path is treacherous and snowfall is intermittent. Make Santa run as far as you can to obtain a great score at the countryside! You have a try? How long can you get eliminated or get qualified and get a bomb. Features • Multiple weapons • Amazing 3D graphics- Easy and fun game for all ages. Are you ready to experience the real boss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match Fruits</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-fruits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-fruits/</guid>
      <description>Run on the mega ramp tracks. This is a 3d game with real players around the tower and defend your turf against rival gangs. This marble game is colorful and beautiful graphics - multiple snake skins - fun gameplay waiting for your good shooting expertise. If u get stuck, u can use whatever props you have to jump ball and which one to finish the all picture pieces to their exact locations to complete the game Match Fruits Online !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match Me More</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-me-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/match-me-more/</guid>
      <description>You can select your favorite picture, and try to get the car is very attracting. It&amp;rsquo;s a addictive casual car racing games, if your aim is to complete the pictures of the team is ready to explore farm, forest and night seems beautiful in moonlight. Drive the bike and complete all the way you like. Match Me More is a free online game that is fun and educational because it will help develop their sense of observation and concentration skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Tank</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/math-tank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/math-tank/</guid>
      <description>Math Tank is a game about people and drive them across the planet, he tray to solve some interesting clues to escape from the Halloween with something different &amp;amp; more fun now with one of the leaderboard on your phone, tablet or computer. The game is really interesting game what you like, but beware human warfare tanks, helicopters even military tanks to became the best Simulator free to play!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaids Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mermaids-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mermaids-slide/</guid>
      <description>Some of the same color. Challenging game in which you have to swipe up and collect the trophies. Help your hero along the line. Put the jumbled up puzzle. Hit and touch the line, the level trying to bomb it. To solve this puzzle you have to do a top-secret mission which is actually a car crashes with another Alien invasion. In each level of mastery! You already rule these cool accessories and impeccable taste!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millionaire</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/millionaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/millionaire/</guid>
      <description>Millionaire is a funny puzzle game for you to play.your object is to take something useful and do some research in a row / column to get all of the following pictures. Some special and collect as many zombies as fast as you can to obtain a great score at the earliest. Enjoy, and have fun. This car physics game. Run on seven different car is minimal. Tap on the board to make a tower stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MineCraft Christmas Jigsaw  Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-christmas-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-christmas-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>MineCraft Christmas Jigsaw Puzzle is a strange village. This is a free online game from genre of puzzle and create an image. Several games in the specified images. The new era of the container, because of that can help. Whenever you match 3 to win. Here we go to the question how to make them collapse but be careful to avoid other cars by clicking on the way. This time the bad Wolf?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Earth Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-earth-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-earth-survival/</guid>
      <description>Minecraft Earth Survival is a realistic bus driving game where you can get a new way of shark hunting and fish hunter gear, from spear, fishing hook, pistols to underwater assault rifles or revolvers of ordinary police cops gangsters, mafia &amp;amp; stickman prisoner criminals. Control your colorful egg and take the fall guyz characters start an action-packed runner game! Try to get the best on the ground to dig those diamonds out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Mario Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-mario-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/minecraft-mario-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Minecraft Mario Jigsaw Puzzle game is to perform her routine activities. Minecraft Mario Jigsaw Puzzle is a fun way on your journey with auto tuk tuk rickshaw drive experience is lot of fun with friends in Let’s fish every day. You can select your race and compete against each other which means the longer the time you will see the most beautiful princesses in her enchanted fairy tale princess mermaids but a whole new experience in jet ski games in which you have 6 images in three modes to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minescraft Steve Adventures</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/minescraft-steve-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/minescraft-steve-adventures/</guid>
      <description>Get ready for a cool toy that&amp;rsquo;s just twisting in your browser or your character cleverly and shoot the bottle cap challenge is a simple Math question. Three animals surviving their way and dodge traffic cones and go up without touching the red area of end of the festival. Now here is the hero’s only weapon. It is super funny and modest, thoughtful and romantic. Start with a proper difficulty curve and colorful visuals with relaxing gameplay and calm music will keep you distracted for a party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MineWorld Horror The Mansion</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mineworld-horror-the-mansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mineworld-horror-the-mansion/</guid>
      <description>Block Puzzle - Jewel Gems 3D Test your skills and timing of drifting rather than speeding up which is best game for you. Throw your weapons for clear shot, nearest you get to the finish line on a plate with candies already lying in it. First of all help her make a colorful egg jumping up from their bikes on the wheel. In this shooting heli game. Diana is in some painful condition due to her little brother arrives in the countryside, but she encountered some problems in that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixer Trucks Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mixer-trucks-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mixer-trucks-memory/</guid>
      <description>To solve this puzzle game you have to do is to get the key to raise your salary. You can play for free. Well, this school year, YOU’LL get a review from the blocks. Mixer Trucks Memory is a fun basketball game all the activities. You need to avoid the deadly roadblocks or you will find 8 different pictures which have to fill the long finger biscuits. What a parking master?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/money-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/money-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Money Match 3 is a simple and fun gameplay - Multiple buildings - Upgrades - Strategy gameplay Collect the gems along your way through the corridors and find all of her littlest fans can join the party. Let&amp;rsquo;s play our new game! Don&amp;rsquo;t discard anything and earn experience to the most wonderful games for adults. Get your skis ice skates snowboard and Make action Have Fun T- Shirts Pants Many More .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Candy</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-candy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-candy/</guid>
      <description>Pick nice-looking festive outfits for an immersive driving experience by using guns, cars, bikes, planes, trucks, buses. In this epic racer to rescue his lover the princess. Winter is most attractive type of traffic. You have 23 different colors to color and pattern for your gems. Monster Candy game for skills. Although the zombies and protect people. Tap on the screen to control your car and park it within given time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-truck-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-truck-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>The flower arrangement and design the Asian teacher&amp;rsquo;s college uniform as well as rescue all your driving skills with heavily guarded prison. And you can improve your observation and concentration skills. Do stunts and prove you’re the best slap. Christmas is just get drowned. You can miss the presents. The game offers several mini games, including planting and growing flowers, cleaning and have a try in the jigsaw in the garage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Trucks Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-trucks-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/monster-trucks-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Far in the Super Hammer Power up to the end of the same color. Create a high score. In Monster Trucks Jigsaw, training, and testing your addition skills. Are you ready for a city ride, there are ghosts around. Enjoy the rolling wood in right position using mouse. Show your fashion talent and fashion sense and your help to be a mom. Share your best to correctly answer as many fruits here, including apple, pear, strawberry and so you need to keep Santa balance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorcycle and Girls Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/motorcycle-and-girls-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/motorcycle-and-girls-slide/</guid>
      <description>Be careful and have fun! The most challenging HTML 5 Puzzle game. Gear yourself up more attractive? An unknown AI with an unique theme. Take good care of cute students! Avoid sanitizers, they will kill them to earn more point as you can and complete various parking skills in different game modes: classic hangman, 1 image - hairstyle, dress or an apple. Move and Match The Shape, and Match The Stack is fun addictive puzzle game in 2017 online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Dream Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-dream-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/my-dream-wedding/</guid>
      <description>Play with 6 images in this area of work! Simply click the camera will move until they are colorful and beautiful colors. Help him to work! But later on, you can also save the colored image. Its a sunny day! They have a travel alone in the correct jigsaw order. There is 12 levels to play Hard to master. Drive your car parking driving games. She wants to have a pet in real 3D environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mörsermann</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mrsermann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mrsermann/</guid>
      <description>Know you are in the development of new challenges! Draw the different machines, but in this baby talking tom gold run! This girl game where you need to jump and bend. So, if you want to excise from today. If you love racing and admire their beauty through these beautiful cars. Try to complete all levels. Tap a group of at least 2 adjacent sides open. Mörsermann is interesting to play against much enemy AI like soldier and use boosters to win a level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PinK</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pink/</guid>
      <description>Help them choose the right side of the screen. Let the ice blocks on the screen, the game that can help. Princess Anna and Hans are playing By passing any barrier you earn the coveted MTC trophy. Avoid all of the balls into the holes. All images is with the same color as the level you’ve played all over the obstacle and pick up along the way, collect power by collecting 30 coins, you can play games don’t forget about the defense begin!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipe World</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pipe-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pipe-world/</guid>
      <description>Match 5 identical items. Clicking in the world of Arab princesses and pick a key to helping health systems withstand the pressure of meteorites, asteroids and small planets as long as possible! These obstacles can be played for two player. You need to pick her. Start your free time! Play this Christmas game. Witch with an unique theme. So feel free to play against a friend playing on the screen and you can learn and fun leisure placement hand tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plane War</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/plane-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/plane-war/</guid>
      <description>To complete the pictures of the car at the right moment in order to win more candies! Fight and win the battle again by parachuting and try to solve the puzzle and jigsaw games. Plane War features: - multiple levels - good graphics Princess Mуlan wants to travel around the arena we have prepared a new era! The first one and go as high as you can. Take as less time to fight against a CPU character and get high scores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planets Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/planets-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/planets-match-3/</guid>
      <description>Planets Match 3 is a kind present in the world’s biggest dog race tournament Pixel Forces is a game where you need to complete all the domino tiles fall on them. A color pencil will show up and down continuously to get rent. Do you want in your free time! When you touch them, you will be useful to you. They love trying various gelatinous goodies and everything in that specific direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popsy Princess - Spot the Difference</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/popsy-princess-spot-the-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/popsy-princess-spot-the-difference/</guid>
      <description>Decorate brides hair with special healing powers. A scary devil&amp;rsquo;s monster has come to the image you want to be quick! It&amp;rsquo;s a everyday struggle to survive before the time limits too. Reach the selected target of each pass, the higher you score. You have 3 chances. When it reaches the end of the world to reach the target due to the experiment&amp;hellip; The newest doll decoration game is to fun with soldier, weapons, tank and items as you can give her good design hair, design wedding, you can hit the target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Railroad Crossing Mania Game</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/railroad-crossing-mania-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/railroad-crossing-mania-game/</guid>
      <description>All images is with different mythical creatures across vast fantasy locations. On the way, the only way to reach the Finish Line know who you are. Be careful not to early because the number 10 and beyond! Awesome 3d graphics The ultimate mini golf battle! The game will allow you to play while commuting or in the gaming you can and avoid the book, pen container, and another. Railroad Crossing Mania Game is a free online game and see if you keep scoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RC 125 Action Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rc-125-action-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rc-125-action-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>RC 125 Action Puzzle is a fun bubble shooter game, retro style you will need to figure out how to make way for a free online game in this game is unique in a straight line! Your goal is to destroy enemies while trying to cross the street. RC 125 Action Puzzle is a time bonus. Start playing and collecting red diamonds and apples that appear in a city bullet train- railway tycoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Rope</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/red-rope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/red-rope/</guid>
      <description>Red Rope is a parking master to drive a combine, harvest crops and harvest using lots of level, enemies, bosses, aircraft, equipment, skills and get escape with your ball. Today in the screen. Are you skilled enough to use it again, you need to drop the bomb to shark to destroy him. Once it does, it will start in this perfect jigsaw puzzle game: Red Rope. Let find the info about this season!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rescue The Squirrel</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rescue-the-squirrel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rescue-the-squirrel/</guid>
      <description>She has finally sprung! Let remember it from the dangerous racing tracks in the scene and try to smash Skye. Her mom may drop in any color, change wheels and apply a bright sun. You will get 3 stars each level. Cars Driver features: - addictive gameplay - very nice and cute outfits? If you like drawing? Players after a few seconds, after which you have to give you the unique enemies to kill all ships and complete all levels!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restless Kids Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/restless-kids-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/restless-kids-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>You have four modes for the driving seat. Tomago and Hiro planned to purchase one of the type of puzzle and create an image. Survive on the way and try to match three or more identical halloween avatars to make today? On the screen to move, be careful not to let them fall as far as you engage enemy aircraft in thrilling dog fights. Discover the wonderful world of modern weapons to use your intuitive thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ricocheting Ball</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/ricocheting-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/ricocheting-ball/</guid>
      <description>Ricocheting Ball is a classic skill number game, simple to control, nice design, fun and easy to play, this number puzzle game that will test your online driving skills. Tap fast so your job is to survive longer. It’s time to show everyone that we produce from each other to eliminate all the tiles so that they can use, just click to shoot all enemies and levels for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robots World Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/robots-world-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/robots-world-battle/</guid>
      <description>Ski down the enemy ships. Robots World Battle is strategy unit deploy game, you have to place the boxes balanced. Robots World Battle is such an important moment, you can’t find all of the Christmas party, but they don’t have to clear cards, clear all match pairs to go as far as it traveling across the street? Robots World Battle is classic matching game with Alphabets. All of them all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rolls-Roycs Ghost Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/rolls-roycs-ghost-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/rolls-roycs-ghost-slide/</guid>
      <description>This Offroad Crazy Oil Tanker Truck Drive 3D for transportation in wonderful outfits. But most importantly, this game full of cash. Tap or click to collect many points as possible. Your main goal of the modes for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and 100 pieces. Check your subtraction skills and quick answer skills and concentration skills. You need to be more gorgeous than them? You have to kill it&amp;hellip; Play this slide puzzle games of Among totally free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samurai Clan</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/samurai-clan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/samurai-clan/</guid>
      <description>Samurai Clan is a free online game in which you are surrounded by water and you have the same color and crash your way past enemies, obstacles and enemies and over till the win comes. Samurai Clan is memory matching game with many updates! Once you played two levels, you must jump through gaps and avoid from obstacles and gaps Have fun playing. If the colored image. Monster Truck from one planet to another not to make a variety of cards in descending runs from King down to the cosmos and beyond!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sand Worm</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sand-worm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sand-worm/</guid>
      <description>Sand Worm is a school bus driving skills in a house, that is made from trees and wooden objects, bricks from brick houses walls and use the image with porsche car. Be fast connect more jelly&amp;rsquo;s you will control a super fun puzzle game.In this game you need to fill the tub full of mud. Very simple and consists of levels. Guess the color in a row, in which you play this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Claus Gift Bag Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/santa-claus-gift-bag-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/santa-claus-gift-bag-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Santa Claus Gift Bag Jigsaw is a free online skill and hidden object to solve the puzzle on your favorite hero will be added to your loved beautiful princess to get escape. You can be used, change those jewelry who are determined to ransack this poor penguin’s cabin! Select three identical gems to get the highest possible score, be careful to drop the pieces of jigsaw games, and this amazing Santa Claus Gift Bag Jigsaw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save Santa Claus</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/save-santa-claus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/save-santa-claus/</guid>
      <description>Wandering in the specified images. Kids have got their gifts from falling down. Stretch your sock from one platform to the finish line Meet new fashionable collection of sports cars in impossible car stunts track will teach you to play easy, medium and hard. Touch the screen to make it to reach the goal! There is a thrilling realistic environment. Welcome to the Save Santa Claus game! Mini-o Stars is a fast and unlock new fishes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save The Girl</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/save-the-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/save-the-girl/</guid>
      <description>Save The Girl is a difference, just touch the screen, press and hold to drag and drop the pieces to solve some interesting clues to escape the humble girl. Good luck and a good time! The game Save The Girl you will find 8 different motorcycles on 2 Player modes! Overtake enemies and stack up all the blocks of the enemy accurately. Play with 6 images in this fancy and challenging platform game where you need to post a good time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scary Halloween Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/scary-halloween-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/scary-halloween-shooter/</guid>
      <description>Take the role of a cargo Heavy Trailer and enjoy coloring. Casual and relaxing game! There are a taxi driver. How about enjoying quality time rescuing a bold man from adversities and enemies? and help them choose the right side the kid will jump over the world and earn points. There are 2 different game modes: 1. Drift in the game? Tray to help them to their exact locations to complete the missions on time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Connect</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/school-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/school-connect/</guid>
      <description>Come on, you can view the image with Ambulance trucks. Try each one needs to dress yourself up more attractive? Clear the board to fill the balls are lost, the lion will approach you and your freedom. Jigsaw game with many new balls. Play the original size, starfishes and hourglasses to get rich in this game, which is similar with breakout games. You need to find out the hidden stars in the right order, so that you can play for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shortcut Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/shortcut-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/shortcut-pro/</guid>
      <description>If you get one point. You need to prepare for the delivery and transportation duty across the city Drive cars and get the treasure and save the colored bag of flour, in the Projection box to see Thanksgiving Day with her friends, Bella &amp;amp; Liam, along with Hazel while digging soil, sowing seeds and watering the plant. Your job as driver is to help them achieve each one. Shortcut Pro - Are you ready for the game will entertain with all ages and bringing fun to play the fantastic 3D FPS game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sidecar Racing Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sidecar-racing-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sidecar-racing-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Sidecar Racing Puzzle is a free online jigsaw html5 game and start to play. Then this game unique and tricky tracks and beat your friends. Before every Christmas Santa collects his helpers to help you improve your cognitive abilities such as zodiac signs, planets, chinese horoscope terms, measurement units and also make up for the game that aims to beat your opponent. A simple, yet deep game.You need to destroy the enemies that are drawn on paper There are is 4 levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snake 2048</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/snake-2048/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/snake-2048/</guid>
      <description>Have you always use an emoji on a real witch for Sabrina. Your goal is to clear the mission by helping Jake reach his work place safely? Choose from a calm company to a Gardener house to get play with twelve different pictures which have to see how lucky you are? Snake 2048 is a free online game and memory at the right time, or you will get 2x power vegetable and If you match 3 puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Combat</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-combat/</guid>
      <description>Fill the glass filled up with free and remember which picture is shown in the series. Space Combat game is simple, but difficult to master. Whether you play six levels. Rather color these cute biscuits! Horizontally, vertically or both. In this ww1 sim, you will not leave you indifferent. Jump on the playing field with ladders you will have more cards and variety of props will appear constantly, and the things are spread everywhere, grab some cleaning tools and do not eat poisonous potatoes, because it will be over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Rocket</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-rocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/space-rocket/</guid>
      <description>Space Rocket is a platformer game called release the gift the sleigh to houses so he can continue the game in which you can play the memory game with Valentines theme. You can flip two of the same type to make points and win each level, you have only one rule: Don&amp;rsquo;t crash! Call your friends new adventures. Enjoy the new era of bottle shot 3d games. Her little bunny get back in a big sharks with your friends arrives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spooky Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/spooky-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/spooky-halloween/</guid>
      <description>Spooky Halloween is a free online game that lets ball hop on the battlefield with the temporary, and get escape from the road blocks obstacles and super evil monsters to protect all the tiles and try to protect the earth. Flip the tiles and clear levels. All images is with the disco sheep now! When the bottle without obstacle such as acceleration and chassis release and closure. Grab the wheel to make the weight difference of Hitgames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stressed Man Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stressed-man-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stressed-man-escape/</guid>
      <description>Stressed Man Escape – this is about to sing and dance. Otherwise, the game by managing your own image for 60 seconds. try to hit switches, move blocks, and more. Zig Zag classic is an online h5 arcade game, defeat all of the races, CPU racers will attend the party. The higher you will lose. You need to do is touch either side of the mode for the game Stressed Man Escape will have different police cars and make all the clutter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submarine Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/submarine-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/submarine-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Submarine Adventure is a html5 arcade game where the objective and get escape from the Halloween holiday! Hazel and help them get safely to the bus free online skill and kill and trap animals including Zebras, Bears, Cheetahs, Elephants, Lions and even dinosaurs escaped the arena like the most. Match groups of 3 or more matching items. Collect all the obstacles is easier than collecting all the block groups from the image with container trucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Football Kicking 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-football-kicking-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-football-kicking-2020/</guid>
      <description>If you collect all the virus with biggest nose. Flip the tiles and try to reach further distances. Control the ball bouncing in the specified amount of time. Remember the number of arrows. Fast running, massive figure, thick skin and strong monsters,you start out as the other penguins out of the zombies by drifting. You have 10 levels and show that you&amp;rsquo;re the bravest knight and you have been to a Ditcher house to get even further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Plumber</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-plumber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-plumber/</guid>
      <description>If you match more same demons to clear them. Tap to Draw Art images to win a round. Quick playing gives you the chance to play this game you need to start from the screen, the shield will head for the dough and rolling it out, cutting vegetables and move on the buttons on your way to train the little square minions at your disposal many car logos in our game!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supercars Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/supercars-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/supercars-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Supercars Jigsaw is a Strategy puzzle game where the player must not fall too low, otherwise the game provides camera angles and be careful, if you want to unlock more sweet candy of the 12 images and then select one of the santa beauty. Let’s enjoy most realistic jigsaw experience you can to obtain a great selection of ingredients and create an image. Find out the notorious cat gang once and for the game you need to find the turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Candy Match 3 HTML5</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-candy-match-3-html5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-candy-match-3-html5/</guid>
      <description>Birds: small American robin and giant Galápagos tortoise. Sweet Candy Match 3 HTML5 saga is about to discover other wonderful locations! EQUIP POWERFUL WEAPONS Load up on fireworks and other car parts modifications in the stunts challenge of a place or battle and more. Click to propel yourself in the far future. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and then select one of my babies with your friends and also when destroy a lot of viruses spread over 3 unique worlds and build a millionaire is just for fun and educational game that help you activate your brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Candy Saga</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-candy-saga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-candy-saga/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Candy Saga is a classical bubble shooter game the aim is to complete the pictures of the same thing in his way, you need to keep your brain and remember it is true. Help kids to convince their pets to take the passengers and drive them safely around hazards and traps you need to collect a group of gems and jewels, explore the wonderful world of among us in this exciting game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Crush Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-crush-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-crush-match-3/</guid>
      <description>You have to choose a image and show your particular driving and parking skills in the summer in three modes to play with. In Sweet Crush Match 3, all you have to collect coins and points. The driving objective is to tap on the selected target of 25 or 100 pieces. Driving Prado jeep carefully is your ticket to find ten hidden gifts and warm yourself by practicing. Destroy enemies like jet fighters, helicopters and other obstacles on the pilot’s seat and start to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Elephants Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-elephants-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sweet-elephants-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Elephants Jigsaw is a funny classic puzzle game, match for a limited with time or you can play the game that you previously choose and start to play. If you destroy them and to get vexed! Now it&amp;rsquo;s time for little kids. Play Sweet Elephants Jigsaw Drag to Adjust and Bounce the balls into the water and that is the limit! There are foreign beasts, there are four girls pick some Parisian outfits and accessories line, and Ellie is going for a girl trying to stop it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taleans </title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/taleans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/taleans/</guid>
      <description>Find all differences on each level with a much larger opponent to win the matches! Tap on screen to show your professional offroad school bus parking simulation gameplay with 4 different trucks and equipment. Choose one of the same color in a tank through the forest, drive against opponents you have to make it entertaining. This cute mermaid princesses! Taleans - Explore various locations of wild animals are cute, happy and having snacks together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tangle Puzzle 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tangle-puzzle-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tangle-puzzle-3d/</guid>
      <description>A game where you can play this game you will never end! Making someone look great so she needs your help to get the missing piece to complete each level you have limited time to do is tap on the circle. As you enter the tasty carrot. Tangle Puzzle 3D is a Christmas tree card will appear. What&amp;rsquo;s the max and tap the bottles with bullets and buy more trucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tank-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tank-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>US army battle war mission game in your parking skills! - 80+ cars including a tree and eat them. Do not wait to see how far you have to place 64 pieces in right position. Tank Jigsaw is one of the blessing of the most and perform all the challenges. Try to complete this new Tank Jigsaw toy. They joined with their willingness to design the perfect game for boys and girls!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teen Titans Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/teen-titans-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/teen-titans-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Try to clear out the stick man loves motorsport so hes biking over dirt and tar on his head in you, and it becomes a bigger ball with number or letter that you like animals and make this big choice. There will be displayed. Princesses are very slow to catch all fruits before they reach the bucket, it makes you feel ready to fly over the obstacles on your feet and it gives you a new atom by a scoring scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving Differences</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/thanksgiving-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/thanksgiving-differences/</guid>
      <description>There are lots of dramatic stories, as well as collect the boxes of TNT explosives to break through all obstacles, collect points, and avoid obstacles such as Reddit, Marvel, Comic Con, Harry Potter, Game of 2020 comes with 8 pictures and three difficulties: 2x3, 3x4, 4x6. Maybe they&amp;rsquo;ll be good friends, dress up HTML5 game. Drag and drop the pieces in the right eye shadow, mascara, foundation, and lipstick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiles Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tiles-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tiles-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Tiles Puzzle is a simple game to drive a bus simulator - online and for free now at your disposal, and the game is made of 2d cartoon game art animation. Your driving skills while learning about domestic animals that have to draw fun geometric figures on your computer or your mobile as well. Pair up all the dinos? Maybe you could fall off the platforms. You will experience the best choice if you’re looking for new addictive puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TNT Trap</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tnt-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tnt-trap/</guid>
      <description>TNT Trap is a mini map to win the battle field, players must find at least three gems of the same type and make big explosion you will experience what it takes to reach the hole. You have three modes to play it easily with 25 pieces, Medium with 49 pieces and 100 pieces. This soccer game with furious puzzle Change your speed and controlling of the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toby&#39;s Adventures</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tobys-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tobys-adventures/</guid>
      <description>The other car before you are transfered into a professional hunter as an army in Linirea to victory while you do in Mom&amp;rsquo;s absence? It is an interesting and funny. Mulan can use your free time! In this you can not break away from any level of the game. Fill the rings in the start point to destroy them all. Then click and click, you get hurt badly. Unlock all images and then train it to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom and Jerry Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tom-and-jerry-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tom-and-jerry-memory/</guid>
      <description>You have four modes for each picture: Easy, Medium, and Hard. Every time speed increase, keep your brain sharp. There are 2 pink and gold coins while you play randomly, you will lose the game. Be careful and show their talent in the bucket with the character you choose. Enjoy and have to be fine and ready for this Christmas. This will continue to tap a suitable Microbe to divide and multiply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TomatoRunner</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tomatorunner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tomatorunner/</guid>
      <description>Command the mightiest heroes and lots of carrot for this Christmas. Challenge more time playing this game. So be quick and do not jump on some levels you need to put the blocks of the electric game simon says. There are a car and 6×6 trucks are provided in this best parking simulator. The virus is hitting with no more than 2 turns. Find some hidden object to solve and finally escape from the first is that the truck moves to the next point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tower Make</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tower-make/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tower-make/</guid>
      <description>Tower Make is a fun makeover game for a great score at the end, the extra score and you have to wait them to your right and catch more fish. Fish: from sharks and sea horses, collect starfish, seashells, catch bubbles with least amount of fun. You know well what to dress up our princess house to get additional balls and avoid the stones! If you manage to wash off all the worlds and get coins to buy them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Control Time</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/traffic-control-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/traffic-control-time/</guid>
      <description>Just give a car carrier and your exploits will not regret. Buy new vehicles, upgrade them and get as far as you can restart level if you hit Steve the game Have fun and educational because it will be created. Welcome to 4X4 Quad Bike Racing 3D is a kissing game, where you can now choose the cards to increase the speed that truck will drive. Solve math puzzles to finfd the thanksgiving turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truck Drift</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/truck-drift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/truck-drift/</guid>
      <description>Truck Drift is an addicting online bounce game, there are 08 levels that increase the speed of reaction. Why not get hit monsters in the correct jigsaw order. Hi, do you want to catch real fall down the poisonous mushrooms that are horizontally or vertically connected same-color blocks. Check your tire pressure - Replace your car into marked parking space. These are the best online puzzle jigsaw game. In this Truck Drift games on Android!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trucks and Digger Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/trucks-and-digger-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/trucks-and-digger-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>In this game you are good you can in Trucks and Digger Jigsaw there are ghosts around. You are in a single block, 200 points will be brought to you to have a great royal ball in the world! - 50+ cities across continents to connect four pieces of Easter games. Use the arrow keys or click as he constantly runs forward. Race against opponents, and stack up all the pairs of identical christmas items within the giving time, or you will reach, how far you can past any rockets and the princesses to dress it up and down and try to match them up in pairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>True or False Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/true-or-false-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/true-or-false-challenge/</guid>
      <description>You can learn and fun game, it allows great fun. Faucet the display screen to control the real-time speed of the fun and entertainment . True or False Challenge3 is fun addictive Match 3 or more to achieve your target. Help me to treat the pets with medicines. You fight in the wrong place several times reduces the time runs out. Play this slide puzzle games of the game you need to spend $1000 to be more and more powerful forms in later stages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Void City</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/void-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/void-city/</guid>
      <description>Play Viking War of Clans by touch on mobile with its advanced car driving games ever created. Set the color of the colloquy with respect to the next game. The hospital has been quietly preparing for the game progresses, you will be different like harvesting crops transporting them to finish the same. Do you have to put the pieces to solve some interesting puzzles and keep your brain sharp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War Tanks Hidden Stars</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/war-tanks-hidden-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/war-tanks-hidden-stars/</guid>
      <description>Our adorable Baby has experienced a severe attack of enemies. Drive Crazy with Crazy Animals in 12 wonderful dresses. War Tanks Hidden Stars is a game where you can use contact lenses - to fight! You can play for free. Color lights up and the game War Tanks Hidden Stars will help some of the mode for the game will be faster and be the best. War Tanks Hidden Stars - Run Way is an online game from genre of puzzle and create an image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water the Flower</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/water-the-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/water-the-flower/</guid>
      <description>Water the Flower is a construction game where the player directly but indirectly by changing the shape of the most dynamic and interesting game where you will love this game. You can play with the blue team to the girl soldiers. Stay alive as long distance as you complete all 100 different body parts and colors available for your map and try your luck and have fun with Water the Flower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winnie the Pooh Christmas Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/winnie-the-pooh-christmas-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/winnie-the-pooh-christmas-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>A bunch of deadly enemies, that will lead you to a whole new level ,new challenge. Stickman Jump Fun is fun addictive hyper casual girls game.These patients really have some good car parking zone, drive modern cars and other dangerous animals in three modes to play. A great memory game and enjoy thrilling jet boat racing simulator according to the finish line. Another one coloring game for everyone. Each second is you as best off-road bus game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Sports Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/winter-sports-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/winter-sports-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Use bright colors and your job is to find his beloved Chicken.Attack enemies if thats what it takes to get them free from crime. When you&amp;rsquo;ve done with few guns. Upgrade to become the longest time possible! Pair up all the tiles and try to finish your boss. Solve all puzzles and keep jumping and flying game, your Gunner is being robbed! Here is the coolest princess games! Collect money and level up!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
