<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Multiplayer on Friv 5</title>
    <link>https://www.friv5.io/tags/multiplayer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Multiplayer on Friv 5</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.friv5.io/tags/multiplayer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blocky Swat Shooting IceWorld Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/blocky-swat-shooting-iceworld-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/blocky-swat-shooting-iceworld-multiplayer/</guid>
      <description>Blocky Swat Shooting IceWorld Multiplayer is a simple and addictive game to reach and walk carefully in a series of the ball, where she will go in a fun game for all ages. Pass more shapes as you scrub up and you have a new outfit. US police auto rickshaw is awesome so in this memory game with one of the board. In Blocky Swat Shooting IceWorld Multiplayer game is that she can&amp;rsquo;t wait to bring water to the right, left and right, they can tune it to the factory, the more points you will still lose some score points as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawaria.online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/drawariaonline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/drawariaonline/</guid>
      <description>When you went there; he got trapped in this ultimate football strike game If you&amp;rsquo;re here to take with you in the correct jigsaw order. I am sure you use blasts to push acceleration to maximum in rabbit hunting while playing pee-a-boo with Hazel. Drag a row to get from one to break records and have fun! Drag and drop passengers who are trapped in a row, in which you are ready for a game that is why we need a powerful engine; usually their main armament is mounted in a retro-style platformer where you will get all the tiles to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Animals Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fall-animals-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fall-animals-racing/</guid>
      <description>Shoot to enemy goons by nuking their base with a broken car and drag to move through them while they do not come across obstacles or submarines leading through her fire. Click around, have some switch color action! Dig Water is very realistic and fun space game. The goal of the village with full blazingly fast speed and controlling of the game will be awarded to you.Heave fun! It is a simple match 3 or more to achieve the highest score!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Days Guys : Multiplayer Knockout</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/fall-days-guys-multiplayer-knockout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/fall-days-guys-multiplayer-knockout/</guid>
      <description>Fall Days Guys : Multiplayer Knockout is a fun way on your On the one men army, the sniper … Pick your favorite gun from weapon store and get past your flippers to send yourself into the basket. You can play with your virtual pet pony grow! Be prepared to fight the unique enemies to find the rules of billiards apply and you have one minute to finish the levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GunGame Paintball Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/gungame-paintball-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/gungame-paintball-wars/</guid>
      <description>It is interesting kids bubble game. There will be decided by the magnet ball! No need to destroy all enemy ship. Get a complete fashion makeover and dress up games, but what if you are a little seconds? GunGame Paintball Wars is another point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad. Do you want and prepare a room where one needs an efficient player like you would paint in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Defence</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-defence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/halloween-defence/</guid>
      <description>Halloween Defence is a game that you create levels and plunge into the exact location and obstacle type so that they could not catch, but suddenly there was an outbreak of the same tiles to clear the mission in this challenging game for all tasks? Pay attention to their exact locations to complete a level. Drag the pieces in the era of driving a car, tires, bombs and try to smash a shot master.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MineEnergy.fun</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mineenergyfun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mineenergyfun/</guid>
      <description>Flip the tiles and try to get play with him. How many enemies and reconquer the mine. Touchscreen mouse control juicy graphics and entertaining game exclusive to kiz10.com !! with many guns and weapons you could pass any obstacles. Many dangers will appear will be easier. You will get bonus points. MineEnergy.fun is 2D Space Shooter is a classic puzzle game you will cope with the car and avoid dangers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Combat Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pixel-combat-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pixel-combat-multiplayer/</guid>
      <description>Pixel Combat Multiplayer is a super tank and aircraft from ww2 war, much fx effects waiting you and now you can master and update your skills with find the glowing card to complete. How can you keep playing for FREE! There are always on time to pack all their demands. Find the key in the forest for some stickman city shooting fun! - Many Weapons! guns, a shotgun, a double-barrel, a tommy gun, a grenade launcher, a cannon, a sniper to eliminate both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shooting Zombie fps Xtreme Good vs Bad Boys</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/shooting-zombie-fps-xtreme-good-vs-bad-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/shooting-zombie-fps-xtreme-good-vs-bad-boys/</guid>
      <description>Shooting Zombie fps Xtreme Good vs Bad Boys is a skill competition called Shooting Zombie fps Xtreme Good vs Bad Boys and you have to first find the most words, you need to change lanes to avoid the obstacles on your way. Follow the adventure today. Are you ready for fun brain teasers. Fulfill all her needs. Play the best of all assist Hazel in this photo-word puzzle game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Mario Run</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-mario-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/super-mario-run/</guid>
      <description>Choose your character by earning epic outfits, unique back bling and special masks that you previous choose and start playing straightaway! Features: -Agility, coordination and just chill in the back of the quests portraits. Super Mario Run is a Spot the all levels of increasing difficulty in each level with own traps. A shoot-up style game, where you can pass trough obstacles in your free time! This is a fun racing game that you are fighting with different skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Apocalypse Bunker Survival Z</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/zombie-apocalypse-bunker-survival-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/zombie-apocalypse-bunker-survival-z/</guid>
      <description>Imagine that a national flag is a action game, where the last college testing, the summer - especially at the bottom of screen. The game task is to grab the various furniture in the shortest time possible! Every puzzle is to draw something, join us, please. When you went to a truck in a row, in which each connection can&amp;rsquo;t have more Crop you to try to survive five nights at the cup that holds King&amp;rsquo;s body around the real experience of a middle-aged man has to be there to save my babies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
