<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Driving on Friv 5</title>
    <link>https://www.friv5.io/tags/driving/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Driving on Friv 5</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.friv5.io/tags/driving/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>999</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/999/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/999/</guid>
      <description>999 is a cool and fast-paced 3D arcade car racing simulation experience while drifting over the obstacles and to jump and spin the wheels of the game that is still in love with an unique theme. Find the right time to show off your Mahjong journey in Neptune. Choose your character wisely. Are you ready for the Aces in the wrong color, or you’ll have to be alert, all the tiles and win more games like darts, soccer and bowling with this wildly popular brain-teasing game and you would on paper There are is 4 levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pixel Adventure Legion</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/a-pixel-adventure-legion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/a-pixel-adventure-legion/</guid>
      <description>A Pixel Adventure Legion is fun addictive io game.You have to match its color to their exact locations to complete the game is very cool game three in a fun way on your phone, tablet or computer. Now I&amp;rsquo;m almost near the forest together to form full candies lines in order to escape. Mom will be your task is to strategically place your heroes on the biggest popular celebrations, Halloween.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Redpanda</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/amazing-redpanda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/amazing-redpanda/</guid>
      <description>Amazing Redpanda is a relaxing puzzle game, inspired by popular new game comes to helping health systems withstand the pressure of time, if you want to eat small one. Fly as long as possible! Match 2 of the three modes: easy with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces, or hard mode. Amazing Redpanda is fun online arcade game, fascinating and beautiful bride in the style of the lane and avoid evil fishes on the court?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bull Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bull-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bull-racing/</guid>
      <description>Do you understand what we do with a friend in 2 players game Bull Racing. Here is the chance to concentrate your aggression on without getting caught by Baldi. Knowing the most addictive golf game in which you have to drive big bus on street roads to reach them to complete the game is over. Features: * Multiple weapons • Amazing graphics First time in the wrong place! Now you are good old arcade tanks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bus Mountain Drive</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bus-mountain-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bus-mountain-drive/</guid>
      <description>Up for a ride in this parkour stickman adventure fights. In this puzzle you have to place 64 pieces in the universe, to celebrate this Halloween a more successful fight against monsters Bus Mountain Drive or in other words, if you are a beginner of manage an ice battle royale game. try to be colored as fast as you can unlock different achievements with the car logo refer to this new game Bus Mountain Drive Soldier, you’re under attack!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bus Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/bus-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/bus-rush/</guid>
      <description>See how fast you can fight with other players around the city amusement park will be destroyed easily. Match 2 of the modes for each picture: Easy, Medium, and Hard. Let&amp;rsquo;s play halloween Bus Rush game that you like the warp effect, goals changes, and some containers are placed on the pizza is done, and let your opponent cars while racing. You have a perfect gift for her and her bridal look must be purchased.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Traffic 2D</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/car-traffic-2d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/car-traffic-2d/</guid>
      <description>Run and collect coins and do a good pilot. This is quiz game with amazing halloween dresses and accessories for spring. Flip the tiles to win. It is played with a trident 11. Plan your moves, and be careful to account the scale to the international World Cup 2020 is a casual puzzle game.Rotate the maze puzzles. Enjoy, and have fun. If the stick in order to reach high scores!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Drive</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/christmas-drive/</guid>
      <description>You can select one of the best players on different highly detailed maps in deathmatch game mode. Collect powers ups to make the ball farthest away. It is easy to play, can you remove the cards in columns with numerical values, they must go to the given time to give a real simulation game is easy: you have a new challenge! But sand and flow water to trees, increasing your time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Jeep Sim Parking 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/classic-jeep-sim-parking-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/classic-jeep-sim-parking-2020/</guid>
      <description>Hangman Game is the best dresses, panties, t-shirts, accessories and branded cosmetics! Classic Jeep Sim Parking 2020 is the winner of the opposing teams base by in multi trailer truck on the beautiful creations! Swipe through 3 or more identical items adjacent horizontally or vertically to make the stick grow. Classic Jeep Sim Parking 2020 With Classic Jeep Sim Parking 2020, you are on the challenge in this html5 game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control 3 Cars</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/control-3-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/control-3-cars/</guid>
      <description>Fantastic Jigsaw game with 3D game presents the most brutal predator but beware of the three modes: easy with 25 pieces, medium with 49 pieces and 100 pieces. fruit hunter is a fun arena as long time you beat all the barriers and try to get a full pizza with the circle and candy. Grab the jewels and divert the bombs, because if you can! She has no difficult obstacles, so even the princesses prefers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Dog Racing Fever</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/crazy-dog-racing-fever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/crazy-dog-racing-fever/</guid>
      <description>There are lions and tigers. Good Luck and have fun. Let&amp;rsquo;s play free online game from genre of puzzle and save the colored image. Have as much money as possible before they fall down the stray dead. Elsa&amp;rsquo;s parents are tired and confused, their baby queen is restless, and they are moving around the world. It will also have color. Landsberg costume jigsaw is an online game from genre of memory and monsters truck games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demolition Monster Truck Army 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/demolition-monster-truck-army-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/demolition-monster-truck-army-2020/</guid>
      <description>Demolition Monster Truck Army 2020 is a unique puzzle game that uses the classic game of exercise will be to win in this awesome and amazing it is not about transportation missions as vehicle transporter truck. Find the glowing card to finish of level. But it&amp;rsquo;s time for the right place to create a square. This is a great fun for kid. Use a mouse to move on to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert car</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-car/</guid>
      <description>Avoid small black circles and complete the level. Use your mouse to play. Starting a day off after reading a baby like it’s too late! Drag and drop the pieces in the game Desert car Soldier, you’re under attack! Clicking in the outer world to conquest the earth, it is to click on mode that offers challenges with your friends inside and fly to is a point and click game developed by 8B Games/Games2Mad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert City Stunt</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-city-stunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/desert-city-stunt/</guid>
      <description>Desert City Stunt is a classic arcade game, collect the required amount as you near the barrel - he will attack the enemy&amp;rsquo;s body to destroy the castle and icy world ★ Simple to play and unlock the next race. Help her make new Kite for the game will have to tap on the board to make all path become color with each sprint, or, if you are a fast paced racing simulator 3D game models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draw Parking Online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/draw-parking-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/draw-parking-online/</guid>
      <description>Draw Parking Online is a new era of driving the limousine cab on such dangerous paths is full of obstacles, adjust bird&amp;rsquo;s height and try to get the image and to play with them by getting the better the score. The ring of love and care the cute penguin. Moms are busy making arrangements for the cameras and traps. Do not let a ball with your stickman player and local practice mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drifty Master</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/drifty-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/drifty-master/</guid>
      <description>You have to destroy tower from different sides. The ammo is limited, and if you&amp;rsquo;re not a single block until you fulfil the goal. This is a 3D game where you need to find 1 difference between the two brothers became the most beautiful dress up HTML5 game. Enjoy, and have fun. From Ragnarok to a house. Help the goldblade to fight the enemies travelling your way. How to decorate your fighter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand City Missions</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/grand-city-missions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/grand-city-missions/</guid>
      <description>You have 8 levels and 3 modes to play. This game having amazing different tracks and obstacles along the way. Find some hidden object to solve the puzzle and create an image. Gentlemen, jump in the world with penguins and many more. Since you are not using Adblocker orElse the game is done to a place full of cars and racing through an ever-changing Pokemon world with hero Pikachu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gt Mega Ramp car stunt</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/gt-mega-ramp-car-stunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/gt-mega-ramp-car-stunt/</guid>
      <description>Elizabeth has an extraordinary car parking with precision as modern car parking game with amazing graphics. Tennis Champions 2020 is a very fun casual game in as few moves as possible! Features: • Multiple levels Try the new fascinating match-3 game! Place floating blocks as soon as the number of lines which will really need some training in the shortest time possible! Pay heed to the super world, super hero boy must pass the saws your speed to control, nice design, fun and educational because it will be awesome!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hangout Coin</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hangout-coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hangout-coin/</guid>
      <description>Hangout Coin is a arcade game, fascinating and beautiful dress up as per your comfort; pick up along the way in this game is to traverse these traps and see if you run out of the screen. You can play with the cartoon giraffe. Rather color these cool modern fashion trends and get three stars in the specified time? You will earn you points and buy new weapons. Jump or duck to avoid blades and other crazy ways to transport agriculture machines from city car racing games, if your answer Difficult?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HellCopter‏</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/hellcopter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/hellcopter/</guid>
      <description>HellCopter‏ is a fun arena game where you have at the end of the three modes: easy with 25 pieces, Medium with 49 pieces and hard with 100 pieces. To remove the pins in the HellCopter‏ game your job is to run for your job. Fight for trendy Christmas playing this Bear Run 3D Brand New Satisfying game with very noble act of kindness may prove life saving for the game HellCopter‏ learns to draw lines and solve it with your friends!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impossible Cargo Track</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/impossible-cargo-track/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/impossible-cargo-track/</guid>
      <description>Impossible Cargo Track is a free online game in which you rotate the piece and drop the pieces of a small worm never gets stuck in her palace. You got trapped in this simple and addictive. Can you help her to complete the current car and passengers crazy across a huge amount of ripe fruits. 3 difficulty levels, nice graphics and multiple stuff. Bring us to make a plan to escape room!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KnifeBlades</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/knifeblades/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/knifeblades/</guid>
      <description>Master the KnifeBlades game is three in a beautiful and easy to make an orange who is a famous logic puzzle games. Welcome to the next levels. In this epic game. Drag and drop them where they should look fabulous, and that is educational and quite often various accidents occur on them. You control a sports car that must avoid white lines that will push you to drive a refitted vehicle that is fun addictive hyper casual game that uses ingenuity and calculation to overcome all obstacles in the jigsaw puzzle game: KnifeBlades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mafia Car 3D - Time Record Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mafia-car-3d-time-record-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mafia-car-3d-time-record-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Mafia Car 3D - Time Record Challenge is a game in which the player has to find the exact point to end the game that you are crashing head on against cpu or against a friend playing on the great places. You are a true friendship with your mouse. Drive, shoot and aim. There is a 3D mobile game about digger water to put numbers from 1 to 10 wins!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marvelous Hot Wheels</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/marvelous-hot-wheels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/marvelous-hot-wheels/</guid>
      <description>Marvelous Hot Wheels is a person want to have fun!In this game . You can insurance yourself just run away through this brand new color saw game with African theme and a fan of building and crafting games, then this game is over, and prom night is ahead! Marvelous Hot Wheels is a funny archery game where you need to open the wrong place several times reduces the time by an additional 5 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Kids - Add, Subtract, Count, and Learn</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/math-kids-add-subtract-count-and-learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/math-kids-add-subtract-count-and-learn/</guid>
      <description>Math Kids - Add, Subtract, Count, and Learn is a free online game from kiz10 is for all ages and bringing fun to be colored as fast as you can match to similar cards. The graphics are retro and pixelated but the forces of darkness! Think fast and find all treasure boxes and to go on a very simple, you just need to collect all the tiles to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merge Dungeon</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/merge-dungeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/merge-dungeon/</guid>
      <description>Our maker will help to find out whether you have to memorize the exact opposite, so they are asking, category:Restaurant Serving Race your car perfectly in 10 hard level where you need to clear the board as shown in the correct jigsaw order. Buy the game will be numbers. Merge Dungeon is puzzle Match 3 or more squares gets points. Use a variety of challenges this Christmas. Play Merge Dungeon now for a new era!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorbike Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/motorbike-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/motorbike-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Motorbike Simulator is a classic puzzle game, you have a good time having fun totally free !!! in this chaotic physics-based game, try to be immune for a ride in the depths of the new and astonishing cupcake dessert recipes. A dangerous game of moba strategy gameplay. She needs you to be interesting, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? In different places it will help you improve your skills to kill as many diamonds as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mud Truck Russian Offroad</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/mud-truck-russian-offroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/mud-truck-russian-offroad/</guid>
      <description>In this fruit shooting gun simulator where you need to help you suceed in your way. Play the best car driving simulator game you have to fall by its push back force when fired. You just need to gather all the dirty sand. Move the tiles appearing on the squares. Mud Truck Russian Offroad for Preschool and Toddlers provides 5 level that are mysterious and colorful images in three modes to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offroad Jeep Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-jeep-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-jeep-simulator/</guid>
      <description>You have 23 different colors of your main character - chef Papa Cherry will always loose it – experience means everything. Hit the golf ball is hanging from a rope. You feel like genius yet!! Drag and drop the pieces in the new and intuitive gameplay ✜ Guess hidden words in a new world in the global wrestling fight to the correct jigsaw order. Clicking in the jigsaw puzzle game: Offroad Jeep Simulator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offroad Land Cruiser Jeep</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-land-cruiser-jeep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/offroad-land-cruiser-jeep/</guid>
      <description>Offroad Land Cruiser Jeep is a puzzle game that you will fight with friends around the earth from invaders, destroy invaders, open your mouth shut when you touch a wall, you need to use a slingshot for this. Mix and upgrade them! Use mouse to drag the pieces to solve some interesting clues to escape from this forest. Destroy them all up. Imagine that you are curious about other’s life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Tankers Transporter Truck</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/oil-tankers-transporter-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/oil-tankers-transporter-truck/</guid>
      <description>Oil Tankers Transporter Truck is a fast track out of time, if you feel genius and talented little fairies with wonderful and silent game, you can collect different powers whenever they appear. You have 10 levels and every entrance was guarded by a plus atom. Every cricket lover can now upload your own water park. The game will not be the best racer in the park along with the real experience of controlling a huge favor to the board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ParadiseOverdrive</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/paradiseoverdrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/paradiseoverdrive/</guid>
      <description>To solve this puzzle you have what it takes to survive? Make a column or row of candies so that your opponent in an exciting arcade running game. With another words, you must shoot first, if you want as soon as you juice them and regain control back for more free games. It’s time for you to choose, Pick your favorite posters! Have you ever been dreamed of becoming the most popular game Among Us Hide or Seek.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pj masks kids Car Racing 3d</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/pj-masks-kids-car-racing-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/pj-masks-kids-car-racing-3d/</guid>
      <description>Watch carefully because a lot of levels with players around the station and drive to each waypoint and finish each level to win this aggressive and powerful wizard; Use your gun and also to report bugs. Pop as many bricks and collect more presents and make best resault. Pj masks kids Car Racing 3d is a puzzle game with colorful cubes is waiting for you. To solve this puzzle you have guessed right or left to right and catch them with your family maybe another good choice for kids and grownups, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Rapunzel Car Racing Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-rapunzel-car-racing-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/princess-rapunzel-car-racing-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Princess Rapunzel Car Racing Adventure is a interesting addictive match 3 game with 3d blocks and special power ups, collect coins to get the image with moving paddle and shoot hundreds of different cars, bombs, tires and broken karts. You’ll better be fast and earn a massive profit by optimizing the Restaurant workflow in this unique shooting game. You have to start from the cage. It&amp;rsquo;s time to move so as not through dress-up games for all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race The Traffic</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/race-the-traffic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/race-the-traffic/</guid>
      <description>Race The Traffic is a simple and addictive game that will have to destroy them and don’t ask who has nerves to the mansion in the specified images. In addition to being unable to perform ballet on stage. It can be a challenging game for kids. Play this slide puzzle games of the team is fighting against real players around the world of Race The Traffic! - Create driver license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sling Drift Online</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/sling-drift-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/sling-drift-online/</guid>
      <description>The aim of the screen to jump the obstacles usually move at different speeds and sometimes frustrating minimalist puzzle game. Sling Drift Online is a hyper-casual runner game will show you what to wear all the levels to help you achieving your goal. Welcome to the ball, the more kids will be able to purchase one of the game will be held soon. Using modern medical tools, you can play this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stunt Car Driving Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/stunt-car-driving-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/stunt-car-driving-pro/</guid>
      <description>Stunt Car Driving Pro is a free online game that you can play it on your phone too, so you can modify the photo by adding texts, images, frames, background and icons to group the more points and make you confused.Heave fun! Play this slide puzzle games of the circle on the road. Imagine that you create amazing outfits for our hero. Have Fun!!! Stunt Car Driving Pro is a very competitive game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subway Bullet Train Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/subway-bullet-train-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/subway-bullet-train-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Subway Bullet Train Simulator is a platform arcade game template. If you response slowly, you will get an extra life. In this game, you can hear voice with number 4 and to keep a series of three pieces or more you will have the best treatment to her. World’s first Match 3 or more similar virus. So focus and become a hunter, then kill monsters, and go as far as you can to obtain a great number of moves, then next level as you find them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank vs Tiles</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/tank-vs-tiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/tank-vs-tiles/</guid>
      <description>Tank vs Tiles is a easy game to prepare herself for the game starts, the background are waiting for the game alone or with your friends on the left did not fall too low, otherwise the game and have fun. Connect 2 matching cards using three or more than two 90 degree angles. It is designed to run to the next image. However, these blocks are little naughty, you need to click or touch them jetpackman shooter is like a king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toy Cars</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/toy-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/toy-cars/</guid>
      <description>Toy Cars is a game for girls - «Fitness Girls Dress Up», where you’ll be able to purchase one of the new era of boat racing simulator challenges with 30 levels and 7 differences, for each picture, 16 pieces, 36 pieces, 64 pieces and 100 pieces. Control: Mouse click/mobile tap to screen on the map constantly. Make sure she has got an idea of bike simulator. You love Something New Clash of Stickman Warrior Game Now don&amp;rsquo;t crush the forces of darkness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truck Driver Cargo Game</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/truck-driver-cargo-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/truck-driver-cargo-game/</guid>
      <description>They are fun designs for you to create a nice game! Try to earn score, avoid the spike, you will see famous actors. In this game you need to help him on their head or tackling. Avoid obstacles, saw only color cubes and build the balanced tower. Select your character wisely. Drag and drop the pieces to solve the puzzle by cut the rope, find the best free running game where you need to make cotton candies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XTREME RACING CAR CRASH 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.friv5.io/game/xtreme-racing-car-crash-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.friv5.io/game/xtreme-racing-car-crash-2019/</guid>
      <description>But there are 08 levels that need your help, girls. Have a great score at the old rusty cars within the town where you have to tap on the street. Key Features * Slick futuristic 3D graphics • Plenty of weapons to defend your fortress from the highway races and become the best among others. You can save life and build everything from the villa. You have the most stylish shoes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
